<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit.atom"/>
  <title>LUCAS HUGH - The Fit Magazine</title>
  <updated>2021-10-11T11:53:15+01:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LUCAS HUGH</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-irene-forte</id>
    <published>2021-10-11T11:53:15+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-10-11T11:53:15+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-irene-forte"/>
    <title>HIGH PERFORMER : IRENE FORTE</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">We sat down with Irene Forte to discuss her style, wellness routine and skincare favourites. With her ‘Natura e Scienza’ vision, Irene Forte is the founder, leader and driving force behind Irene Forte Skincare. As the Wellness Consultant of Rocco Forte Hotels and an Advisory Board Member of the Global Wellness Summit, Irene has always understood the importance of a holistic approach to beauty. This is reflected in her constant emphasis on nourishing, organic ingredients. However, natural ingredients alone don’t guarantee results, so Irene has married nature with science to make it possible for the latest scientific understanding to drive product performance.</span></i></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Irene_Forte_2_480x480.jpg?v=1633948700" alt=""></p>
<p>Tell me about you / your business?<br><br></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">I'm an Italian that was born / grew up in London. I worked in my family's hotel business for almost a decade before setting up my skincare line, <a href="https://ireneforteskincare.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Irene Forte Skincare</a>. </span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Characterised as ‘Natural Science’, Irene Forte Skincare is all about achieving outstanding results with natural ingredients. Our formulations are shaped by 35 years of skincare research and development thanks to my amazing Scientific Director, Dr. Francesca Ferri. Together, we've introduced novel ingredients in products which have shown outstanding activity in independent clinical trials. For all Irene Forte products, the core ingredients come from Verdura Resort's organic farm in Sicily (a place that lies close to my heart). Alongside these, we've integrated zero-waste upcycled ingredients, made from nutrient-rich plant-based leftovers; all of our ingredients are vegan. Indeed, sustainability is a primary business focus for us and something that I built into the DNA of my business from the beginning. </span></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Irene_Forte_4_480x480.jpg?v=1633948806" alt=""></p>
<p>Describe your style?</p>
<p> I'm a conservative dresser and like to be comfortable. I love high-waisted skirts and flares. I love colours and prints. I also like to be in gym gear whenever it's acceptable! </p>
<p> </p>
<p>How do you workout each week?</p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">I’ve always been relatively ‘sporty’ and I’ve tried not to lose that since leaving school (a long time ago now). I tend to work out 4 times a week. One session will be just cross-trainer because I tend to be short of time. I’m a member of Equinox so I tend to do a mix of different high-Intensity interval training classes there; this includes Tabata, Boxing and Barry’s style running classes. I might also mix this up with some Reformer Pilates at Heartcore and some Barre at Barrecore. On a beautiful day, I’ll run in Kensington Park Gardens.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p>How do you recharge/ clear your head / stay focused ?</p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">I think the most important thing for me is sleep. I sleep 8.5 hours per night. ‘<a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Why-We-Sleep-Science-Dreams/dp/0141983760" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Why We Sleep’ by Matthew Walke</a>r was a great book that helped me understand the importance of sleep. </span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">A healthy and balanced diet is also key for me. I follow a Mediterranean diet, which is widely believed to be the cleanest, healthiest and most balanced diet in the world, associated with good health and longevity. It is not about faddy trends and unsustainable eating habits (just like my skincare). </span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">I also love to have regular treatments. I like all sorts of treatments; they help me unwind, recharge and relax. </span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">And lastly, I would say regular exercise, vital for good health, and for me to stay sane. </span></p>
<p> </p>
<p>What is a trusted quote or advice you live by?</p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Treat others as you would like to be treated. </span></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Where are you dreaming of travelling to and how will you pack?</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Being Italian by blood, I adore travelling to Italy. Be it Rome, Florence, the Tuscan countryside, Puglia, Venice... the list is endless. In particular, I’m extremely attached to Sicily. I fell in love with the island when I worked for our resort, Verdura, for six months in 2006. Its landscapes, culture, food, people, and sense of family are unrivaled. So, I'm dreaming of traveling to Sicily. </p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Irene_Forte_1_480x480.jpg?v=1633948911" alt=""><br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">In terms of what I would pack: </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">- Lots of <a href="https://xhtng2qgiuidsfh8-3001581668.shopifypreview.com/collections/new-in" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Lucas Hugh</a>, as I'm always active there. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">- Some <a href="https://www.lido-lido.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Lido swimwear </a>(sustainable and entirely made in Venice). </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">- Some <a href="https://oliviavonhalle.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Olivia von Halle</a> silk pyjamas; they are my essential travel companions for a good night’s sleep, no matter what season.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">- My new <a href="https://ireneforteskincare.co.uk/products/rigeneranti-essenziali-kit?_pos=1&amp;_sid=4646ad992&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Essenziali Rigeneranti Kit,</a> which contains Irene Forte Skincare's six regenerating hero products. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">- It’s so important to always wear SPF and I never travel without my <a href="https://eltamd.com/products/eltamd-uv-clear-tinted-broad-spectrum-spf-46" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">eltaMD clear tinted</a> broad-spectrum one. It’s a lightly tinted facial sunscreen and is great as a make-up base alternative. What’s more, it's paraben and phthalate-free and is rich in hyaluronic acid and vitamin E – basically skin food.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">- I’m not a big make-up person, but <a href="https://www.rmsbeauty.com/products/un-cover-up" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">RMS’s "Un" Cover-Up concealer</a> is great when paired with my<a href="https://eltamd.com/collections/tinted-sunscreen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Elta-MD tinted facial sunscreen</a>. The concealer is a skin-perfecting, illuminating concealer that I use under my eyes, lightly applying it with my ring finger. I love this because it’s clean and doesn’t dry out the skin under my eyes.</span></p>
<p>Favourite beauty essential or treatment?</p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">I don’t have one favourite beauty essential or treatment. However, I would say there are three beauty products that I can’t live without. They are part of my Irene Forte Skincare Myoxinol™ regime: Hibiscus Serum, Prickly Pear Face Cream and Hibiscus Night Cream. Alongside each other in clinical trials, the Hibiscus Serum, Prickly Pear Face Cream and Hibiscus Night Cream deliver visible wrinkle reduction that gets more and more noticeable the longer the products are used. </span></p>
<p>Do you have a recommended book/ podcast or show?</p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">I love the <a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Shoe-Dog-Memoir-Creator-NIKE/dp/1471146723/ref=sr_1_4?dchild=1&amp;keywords=book+Shoe+Dog+by+Phil+Knight&amp;qid=1633948258&amp;qsid=261-8621873-4094626&amp;s=books&amp;sr=1-4&amp;sres=9124072605%2C9124079553%2C9124068349%2C1471146723%2C9124072559%2C9000357594%2C9123963018%2C9124072575%2C9123963026%2C912407232X%2C9124038245%2C9123979666%2C9123913053%2C9123913037%2C9124072567%2C154841705X&amp;srpt=ABIS_BOOK" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">book Shoe Dog by Phil Knight</a> who created Nike. He is a case in point that success isn’t handed to you, his story is amazing.</span></p>
<p>Favourite pieces from the Lucas Hugh collection? </p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">It's actually the only workout clothing that I wear. It's the absolute best. The <a href="https://xhtng2qgiuidsfh8-3001581668.shopifypreview.com/products/performance-v2-leggings-black?_pos=1&amp;_sid=d85e17b5e&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">performance V2 leggings</a> are the most flattering workout leggings I've ever worn. </span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/autumn-agenda</id>
    <published>2021-09-29T15:02:10+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:05:05+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/autumn-agenda"/>
    <title>AUTUMN AGENDA</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<br>
<p><b>The Reformer RX</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Get ready, set, RX with the new ultimate at home reformer pilates workout. The </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">ergonomic design from Reformer RX uses unique technology to track your work rate and guide your progress, elevating your performance through real time biometric feedback for the optimum workout. The smart reformer is finished with touches of polished steel and flawless elegance getting the best out of you while you train. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">From £4995,<a href="reformrx.com"> reformrx.com</a></span></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Reform_RX_480x480.jpg?v=1632923081" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Frieze Fair</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">The contemporary art fair is coming to London this October. Situated in Regent’s Park, the fair will host emerging artists to industry names. Featuring internationally renowned galleries from around the globe alongside new curated sections, special artist commissions and leading voices from the industry hosting talks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Tickets from £26, 13th - 17th October 2021, <a href="https://www.frieze.com/">frieze.com</a></span></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Frieze_Art_Fair_London_480x480.jpg?v=1632923134" alt=""><br>
<p><b>London Fashion Week</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Going ahead this September 2021, </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">London Fashion Week is the first of the leading four global fashion weeks to fully embrace digital media into its twice yearly showcase, in addition to holding physical events. All designers will be showcasing their latest collections in a newly dedicated digital space as Somerset House where a global audience will be able to tune in to view the collections live. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">16th - 21st September, <a href="https://londonfashionweek.co.uk/schedule">londonfashionweek.co.uk/digitalschedule</a></span></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screenshot_2021-09-29_at_14.58.47_480x480.png?v=1632923968" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Beaverbrook Townhouse</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">From their enchanting estate in Surrey, Beaverbrook transports its quintessential British charm to their new boutique hotel situated on stylish Sloane Street, London overlooking the leafy-green Cadogan Gardens.. The two beautifully restored Georgian townhouses are home to a Japanese restaurant, vibrant bar and 14 suites. Expect impeccable designed rooms by Nicola Harding that pay homage to London’s magnificent historic theatres, brimming with carefully curated posters, illustrations, vintage photography, and bespoke written histories, each theatre’s fascinating story is seamlessly regaled in finely crafted words and pictures.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.beaverbrooktownhouse.co.uk/"><span style="font-weight: 300;">beaverbrooktownhouse.co.uk</span></a></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Beaverbrook_Town_House_480x480.jpg?v=1632923105" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Ham Yard Hotel Yoga</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">In the midst of Soho, London, moments away from Mayfair, the Ham Yard Hotel is hosting a series of yoga sessions on the hotel's Roof Terrace in partnership with Third Space. Set amongst olive trees and meadows of wild flowers with views over the rooftops of Soho, experience a Hatha Yoga class under the expert guidance of one of Third Space's instructors. Bringing balance, strength and a sense of wellbeing the 45-minute sessions will guide you through a series of postures and conscious breathing in combination with mental focus to develop awareness, strength, flexibility and relaxation. Yoga sessions include a healthy brunch to follow the class from avocado and poached eggs on rye to granola, yoghurt and berries or coconut chia seed pots with mango.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">£39 including 45-minute yoga session and brunch. Available Saturday 18th September, 9.15am.  </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.firmdalehotels.com/"><span style="font-weight: 300;">firmdalehotels.com</span></a></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Tech_Knit_Leggings_Black_2204_7f25426d-7202-4191-ba72-fb041fc2f9f0_480x480.jpg?v=1584451120" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Dr. Barbara Sturm’s London Boutique and Spa</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Located in Mayfair, London, Dr. Barbara Sturm’s new London flagship will serve as a place of skincare discovery and advanced-scientific innovations. Offering signature facials where you can enjoy the full suite of Dr. Sturm’s most sought-after facials, alongside new exclusive treatments available for London customers. Additionally, new anti-aging body treatments are available at the spa. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://en.drsturm.com/"><span style="font-weight: 300;">drsturm.com</span></a></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Dr_Barbara_Sturm_Spa_Townhouse_Mayfair_480x480.jpg?v=1632923118" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Nobu Pilates</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Located in the heart of Marylebone,</span><span style="font-weight: 300;"> Nobu Wellness &amp; Fitness is home to the World’s first Nobu Pilates Reformer studio. Headed up by the renowned Marsha Lindsay, Nobu Pilates is an exciting new way to experience the benefits of Pilates with specialised classes for glutes, abs and cardio. Catering for beginners to advanced levels, using state of the art equipment including; Pilates Reformers, Cadillac, Stability Chairs and Barrels. </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">A hybrid of classical Pilates and high-intensity training, Nobu Pilates offers three signature classes: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">Power</span></i><span style="font-weight: 300;">, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">Precision</span></i><span style="font-weight: 300;"> and </span><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">Pure</span></i><span style="font-weight: 300;"> – each combining the core components of traditional Pilates with a fresh and focused flow. Classes of ten or individual sessions are available.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Classes from £35, <a href="https://london-portman.nobuhotels.com/wellness-fitness/">nobuhotels.com</a>, available at </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">Nobu Hotel Portman Square, </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/22+Portman+Square,+London+W1H+7BG/@51.5160933,-0.15913,18.1z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x48761acca2c6f72d:0xb06a22c4fa213e6d!8m2!3d51.5161336!4d-0.1579796"><span style="font-weight: 300;">22 Portman Square, London W1H 7BG</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Nobu_Hotel_London_Launch_Pilates_480x480.jpg?v=1632923177" alt=""></span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/work-out-like-a-warrior</id>
    <published>2021-04-30T12:29:07+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:06:31+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/work-out-like-a-warrior"/>
    <title>WONDER WOMEN WARRIOR</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Jenny Pacey Olympic athlete, Hollywood personal trainer and TV Gladiators 'Enigma' was featured wearing the Lucas Hugh Axis Set on the Front cover of this months Women's Fitness Magazine. In the feature Jenny, founder of <a href="http://www.paceandgo.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Pace &amp; Go" rel="noopener noreferrer">Pace &amp; Go</a>, talks about her journey to becoming the lead cast trainer on the Hollywood movie Wonder Woman 1984, what it was like training Kristen Wigg for her role and reveals the Amazon warrior's work out.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Make sure you grab your copy of </span><a href="https://womensfitness.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Women's Fitness Magazine link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Women's Fitness magazine</a><span> this month to see the full workout and article!</span></p>
<p> </p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Jenny_Pacey_cover_600x600.png?v=1619523098" alt="Jenny Pacey Front cover of Women's Fitness Magazine wearing Lucas Hugh Axis Set in Garnet"></div>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>On the front cover Jenny is wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-sports-bra-garnet" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Sports Bra in Garnet" rel="noopener noreferrer">Axis Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-leggings-garnet" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Leggings Garnet" rel="noopener noreferrer">Axis Leggings</a> in Garnet.</em></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2021-04-27_at_12.25.43_600x600.png?v=1619522774" alt="Women's Fitness Magazine Warrior Work Out wearing Lucas Hugh"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2021-04-27_at_12.27.48_600x600.png?v=1619522906" alt="Jenny Pacey wearing Lucas Hugh Axis Set in Women's Health Warrior Workout"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2021-04-27_at_12.27.58_600x600.png?v=1619522956" alt="Jenny Pacey wearing Lucas Hugh Axis Set in Women's Health Warrior Workout"></div>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em> Above Jenny is wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-sports-bra-cobalt-blue" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Sports Bra in Cobalt Blue" rel="noopener noreferrer">Axis Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-leggings-cobalt-blue" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Leggings in Cobalt Blue">Axis Leggings</a> in Cobalt Blue.</em></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-agenda</id>
    <published>2021-03-26T10:32:05+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:06:58+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-agenda"/>
    <title>Spring Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<blockquote>
<p>"The beautiful spring came, and when nature resumes her loveliness, the human soul is apt to revive also." - Harriet Ann Jacobs</p>
</blockquote>
<p>EXPLORE SOMEWHERE NEW</p>
<p>Apps such as Komoot allow you to find inspiring walks and hikes from the ones on your doorstep to further afield. If you'd rather plan your own adventure the app can make it easier to navigate from your chosen A to B and prepare you for what to expect. </p>
<p>Start planning on <a href="https://www.komoot.com/" target="_blank" title="Komoot Start planning an adventure" rel="noopener noreferrer">Komoot.</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/photo-1586911264581-b2c2155d2429_480x480.jpg?v=1616692641" alt="Spring Day" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>THE BRILLIANCE OF LIFE</p>
<p>We are looking forward to taking a step inside one of Yayoi Kusama's famous infinity rooms on display at the Tate Modern. The Infinity Mirrored Room 'Filled with the Brilliance of Life' is one of Kusama's largest installation to date and is accompanied with a small presentation as well as a second infinity<span> </span>room. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Plan your visit to the</span><span> </span><a href="https://www.tate.org.uk/whats-on/tate-modern/exhibition/yayoi-kusama-infinity-mirror-rooms" target="_blank" title="Tate Modern Yayoi Kusama Infinity rooms" rel="noopener noreferrer">Tate Modern</a> ahead of it's reopening<span>.</span></p>
<p> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/T15206_570381_10_480x480.jpg?v=1616689376" alt="Tate Modern Infinity Room" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>ON PURPOSE BY JAY SHETTY</p>
<p>Jay Shetty's purpose is 'to make wisdom go viral' the former monk's podcast features thoughtful and uplifting talks with a range of people from Jennifer Lopez to monk and mentor Gauranga Das. Episodes cover everything from love and relationships to finding peace and purpose.</p>
<p>Available on a variety of<span> </span><a href="https://jayshetty.me/podcast/" target="_blank" title="Jay Shetty Podcast" rel="noopener noreferrer">podcast platforms</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>EGGSTRAVAGANT CHOCOLATE</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Chocolate stimulates the production of endorphins in our brain and is a great way to give yourself a little happiness boost. </span>Treat yourself to a Vegan Milk Chocolate Egg from Rococo Chocolates. The extra thick and delicious eggs are sustainably sourced and hand crafted in London. </p>
<p>Vegan Easter Egg from <a href="https://www.rococochocolates.com/products/vegan-milk-chocolate-egg/" target="_blank" title="Rococo Chocolate Vegan Easter Egg" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rococo Chocolates</a>. </p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/VeganMilcEgg_2-scaled_480x480.jpg?v=1616689491" alt="Vegan Milk Chocolate Easter Egg Rococo Chocolates" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jenny-wordsworth</id>
    <published>2021-02-12T11:00:50+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:07:36+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jenny-wordsworth"/>
    <title>High Performer: Jenny Wordsworth</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Last February we interviewed endurance sports athlete <a href="http://jennydavis.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Jenny Davis/ Wordsworth website link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jenny Wordsworth</a> who had just completed a gruelling 700 mile solo expedition to the South Pole. Here we share our interview with the corporate lawyer turned professional athlete on what motivates her. </p>
<hr><meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong>You have taken part in some amazing challenges, what experiences led you to leave the world of corporate law to become an elite athlete?</strong> </p>
<p>I've been fortunate to have worked for some excellent firms as my career in corporate law progressed, they were always so supportive of my extra curricular activities of mountaineering, ultra running and skiing. I think it was also of great interest to our clients and they'd usually support my expeditions in the form of sponsorship. I started doing well in ultra  running races (so races of 35miles and over), I took part in a 5 day race through the Dasht-e-Lut desert in Iran and after winning the race returned home to the offer of a pro contract. My boss tells me he knew it was coming, and within weeks I'd signed the contract and resigned from my role as in-house legal counsel. I do still work as a freelance lawyer, especially on projects I find interesting as I found I really missed it.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/A7_08841_480x480.jpg?v=1613035992" alt="Jenny Wordsworth in Antarctica" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></strong></p>
<p><strong>You encountered challenges whilst on your trip, how did you mentally stay strong to be able to push through the physical challenges?</strong></p>
<p>Suffering from a painful open ulcer reperfusion injury on my leg known as 'Polar Thigh' with about 150 miles to go from the South Pole was one of the hardest thing I have ever done. Months later I am still not sure how I was able to keep that mental strength and push on through that level of pain. Until that point I had been on track to break the world speed record but after that leg injury simply reaching the Pole felt like the biggest achievement of my life. I did need two surgeries and a skin graft the week I returned to London, but I'll wear the scars with pride. </p>
<p> What really keeps me going in an expedition is my 'why' - why am I here at all and why am I even attempting to do this in the first place. If your 'why' is genuine and strong enough, you'll get through the tough times. That isn't to say it's easy and this expedition was one of the hardest things I've ever done.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>What advice would you give to those wanting to elevate their fitness routine and to those who are even considering taking on an extreme challenge? </strong></p>
<p>If you’re new to adventure it’s great to approach others with more experience and ask for help, just don’t forget that your unique background and experiences will bring something to the table that those experts won’t have thought of before. Don’t be so intimated by the experience of others that you forget or downplay your own ideas or approach. I mentor several women and it's the most enjoyable aspect of what I do - everyone is willing you on and only want to help you succeed, take advantage of that and get the help where you need it.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<blockquote>
<p><span>"What really keeps me going is my 'why' - If it's genuine and strong enough, you'll get through the tough times".</span><span> </span></p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>What keeps you going and entertained during your challenges? i.e any podcasts etc.</strong></p>
<p>I mostly train without any form of external stimulus, especially for an expedition like the one in Antarctica. This was recommended to me by my coaches and it's also a great way to develop your mental strength. Imagine if your AirPods or iPhone stopped working halfway through your challenge, race or expedition? Then what? I don't like to become reliant on stimulus like that, just in case it isn't then available to me during the event itself. I probably do 80% of my training sessions with no music or podcasts, just focusing on the task at hand and entering into a form of flow state. </p>
<p> For the 44 day expedition in Antarctica though, I did save up podcasts featuring people I find inspirational and so the real treat was being able to listen to them whilst there. My friends also surprised me with a full length recording of The Odyssey by Homer! That kept me going for the whole trip as I'd listen to a small section each day.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is next on your agenda? &amp; how do you decide on your challenges?</strong></p>
<p>I was due to be mountaineering in Nepal followed by a ten day mountain bike race through the mountains of Kyrgyzstan, those were both cancelled of course due to COVID-19. In the future I hope to complete an ocean row, precisely because I know absolutely nothing about ocean rowing and that's exactly what draws me to it. I also have a fear of the sea after a friend passed away at sea when I was younger, I'd like to face that fear and love the sea again. </p>
<p> For me the physical challenge is because I love finding out what my body is capable of, then the mental challenge is always where it gets most interesting and, importantly for me, it's an opportunity to visit parts of the planet I'd never normally set foot on.  </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TNF_High_Res_480x480.jpg?v=1613036138" alt="Jenny Wordsworth in Antartica " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><span></span><br><strong>How do you take time for yourself and recuperate from training?</strong> </p>
<p>Sleep! Rest days and enough sleep are a life priority for me, although it took me years to really learn and respect that. The more I look after my body, the more I get out of it. I often get more than 9 hours sleep a night and I couldn't go without it. </p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What do you look for in your workout gear?</strong></p>
<p>High quality and design. I live in workout gear, day in and day out. It needs to last and it needs to look good, Lucas Hugh has been my go-to for years now as the pieces are simply beautiful, the cut is like no other and I've been unable to destroy any of it which given my training is quite something. They are just the most beautiful pieces and I'm in love.</p>
<p><br><strong>Any recommendations of places to work-out or that you love to refuel/ eat in London?</strong></p>
<p>I still love a good Barry's Bootcamp class, I remember when they first opened in London there wasn't anything like them in town and I love popping by for a seriously hard workout. Otherwise I love any of the group classes at KX in Chelsea, they have a great restaurant there too.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-future-of-wellness-2021</id>
    <published>2021-01-15T12:44:55+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:07:52+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-future-of-wellness-2021"/>
    <title>New for 2021</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>2020 has been an interesting year and many of us have had to find new ways to adapt and evolve in one way or another. At Lucas Hugh we're all about looking to the future, here's what we have got into for 2021. </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/COBALT_BLUE_AXIS_FRONT_WFH_l_480x480.jpg?v=1610119227" alt="Lucas Hugh Work Out From Home" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW ONLINE CLASSES</p>
<p>We are kick starting our year with Heartcore who offer a great range of classes from wake up and wind down to their signature Heartcore class designed to build strength and help you flow through your day. Their unlimited live-stream and on-demand pass has something to suit all schedules, with a new online platform coming soon. </p>
<p>Monthly access £55 a month | <a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" title="Link to Heartcore website">Weare</a><a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" target="_blank" title="Link to Heartcore website" rel="noopener noreferrer">heartcore.com</a><a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" title="Link to Heartcore website"></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>JANUARY CLEANSE</p>
<p>Rebooting our systems after an indulgent holiday season with a Radiance Juice Cleanse. They offer a range of cleanse options delivered to your door with guidance and support pre and post cleanse. </p>
<p>Winter Cleanse from £65 | <a href="https://radiancecleanse.com/programmes/classic-cleanses/" target="_blank" title="Radiance Cleanse website" rel="noopener noreferrer">Radiancecleanse.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/a59e6e815efbf14f069b58a78225e333_3fd50abe-4f83-4df6-b6f8-93cc4d6dcd48_480x480.jpg?v=1610118118" alt="Eat Green" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW GREAT COOKBOOK</p>
<p>With more time spent in our home offices a great way to reconnect with family and loved ones at the end of the day is over a delicious healthy meal. Eat Green by Melissa Hemsley contains a variety of seasonal, sustainable flexitarian recipes to suit the whole family. </p>
<p>Eat Green by Melissa Hemsley | <a href="https://melissahemsley.com/eatgreen/" target="_blank" title="Eat Green Link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Melissahemsley.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW PODCAST</p>
<p>Our favourite investigative journalist took the podcast world by storm last year with Grounded. Now back for a second season we can expect to listen to Louis Theroux speak to high-profile people from a variety of backgrounds. We're enjoying his recent interview with Sia. </p>
<p>Listen now | <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p08ybsww" target="_blank" title="BBC Radio 4 Louis Theroux Grounded ep12. Sia" rel="noopener noreferrer">Grounded with Louis Theroux 12. Sia</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/About-Us-Homepage_copy_480x480.jpg?v=1610550508" alt="Black Tomato Villa" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CURATED ESCAPES</p>
<p>With so many travel restrictions last year many will be looking to find the perfect get away this year. Look no further than Black Tomato who are award winning creators of unique and tailored travel experiences and have a team of experts on hand to create your very own 'bubble' get away. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Jetty, Joali Maldives</span> | <a href="https://www.blacktomato.com/" target="_blank" title="Black Tomato" rel="noopener noreferrer">Blacktomato.com</a></p>
<p>   </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LH-Sustainability-2600x1733-1_480x480.jpg?v=1607096722" alt="Lucas Hugh Sustainability Page Image" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW LUCAS HUGH</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>We are driven to advance the future of activewear, and that means protecting our planet and making sustainable choices for our future world. Since launching in 2010, we have sourced premium Italian fabrics to ensure designs of the highest quality that last, </span>as well as producing in limited quantities to reduce excess. We select sustainable or recycled materials where possible, and from 2021 we plan to increase our use of these materials across all of our collections, with a focus on recycled yarns. As of 2020 all of our Technical Knit will be made with Q’NOVA recycled yarns – an environmentally-sustainable nylon fibre. </p>
<p>New collection launching soon. Follow us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lucashugh/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Instagram" rel="noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a> and sign up to our newsletter for exclusive access to the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/collections/new-in" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh New in page" rel="noopener noreferrer">latest drops</a>.</p>
<p>Treat yourself to some new Lucas Hugh | <a href="lucashugh.com/new-in">Lucashugh.com</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/winter-retreat</id>
    <published>2020-11-20T15:50:41+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:08:12+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/winter-retreat"/>
    <title>Winter Retreat</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Sharing some of our favourite ways to create a home winter retreat.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>SPICED CHAI TEA</p>
<p>Best brewed with milk or your favourite milk alternative, a cup of this spiced chai tea is perfect for winding down after a long day. </p>
<p>Tea by<span> </span><a href="https://www.whittard.co.uk/tea/tea-type/chai-tea" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh The Fit, Winter Retreat article, link to Whittard of Chelsea tea." rel="noopener noreferrer">Whittard of Chelsea</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/pdp-christmas-bottomslot-tea-mobile-i5-2_480x480.jpg?v=1605802413" alt="Lucas Hugh The Fit winter retreat article" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;">  </p>
<p>WILD BERRY &amp; BRAMBLE CANDLE</p>
<p>This warm and fruity scent will fill your space with a comforting and refreshing smell. </p>
<p>Candle from <a href="https://www.jomalone.co.uk/product/27211/80698/home-collection/townhouse-collection/wild-berry-bramble-townhouse-candle?size=300g&amp;utm_source=ran&amp;utm_medium=affiliate&amp;utm_campaign=TnL5HPStwNw&amp;utm_content=10&amp;utm_term=2116208&amp;ranMID=42168&amp;ranEAID=TnL5HPStwNw&amp;ranSiteID=TnL5HPStwNw-7inItKBEMqBpueHUS9.idA" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Winter Retreat Article, Jo Malone" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jo Malone</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>THE MICHELLE OBAMA PODCAST</p>
<p>A down to earth podcast from the former First Lady where she speaks to loved ones about connection.</p>
<p>Listen to <a href="https://open.spotify.com/show/71mvGXupfKcmO6jlmOJQTP" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh The Fit, Winter Retreat article link to The Michelle Obama Podcast" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Michelle Obama Podcast</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Podcasts_For_Women_Hosted_By_Women_-_Michelle_Obama_480x480.jpg?v=1605802282" alt="Lucas Hugh The Fit Winter Retreat article" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>AROMATHERAPY ASSOCIATES ESSENTIAL OILS</p>
<p>A collection of award-winning aromatherapy oils for relaxing, de-stressing and reviving your spirt. Perfect in either the bath or shower. </p>
<p>Aromatherapy oils by <a href="https://www.aromatherapyassociates.com/essential-bath-shower-oils.html" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh The Fit, Winter Retreat Article, essential bath and shower oils." rel="noopener noreferrer">Aromatherapy Associates</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/photo-1532926381893-7542290edf1d_480x480.jpg?v=1605802232" alt="Lucas Hugh The Fit Magazine" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>THE POSITIVE POWER OF NATURE</p>
<p>"Scientific studies point in one direction: nature is not only nice to have; it is a must have for physical health and cognitive function." - Matthew White, author of Last Child in the Woods.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/photo-1507967669805-c23336beea5b_480x480.jpg?v=1605864402" alt="Lucas Hugh The Fit, Winter Retreat article." style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/august-art</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T16:30:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T16:30:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/august-art"/>
    <title>AUTUMN ART</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Autumn is upon us. Here's our round up of the best art exhibitions in the UK, as well as a new online class recommendation to boost your own creativity.</p>
<p>ANISH KAPOOR AT HOUGHTON HALL</p>
<p>One of the most influential sculptors still working today and well known for his adventurous take on modern sculpture. Featuring 24 sculpture and numerous other works by the artist, this exhibition is set across the beautiful grounds and within the house itself.</p>
<p>From now until 1st November, Houghton Hall, Norfolk, PE31 6TY | <a href="https://www.houghtonhall.com/art-and-exhibitions/anish-kapoor-at-houghton-hall/" target="_blank" title="Link to Anish Kapoor at Houghton Hall exhibition tickets." rel="noopener noreferrer">houghtonhall.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/03-Anish-Kapoor_large.jpg?v=1599651738" alt="Anish Kapoor Exhibition" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>ANDY WARHOL AT THE TATE MODERN</p>
<p>Iconic and instantly recognisable the Tate Modern has extended its retrospective Warhol exhibition till mid November. The exhibition features iconic pop works such as Marilyn Monroe and Campbell's soup cans as well as works never before seen in the UK. Alternatively, the Tate has also published online an exhibition guide for you to enjoy from the comfort of your home. </p>
<p>From now until 15th November, Tate Modern, Bankside, London, SE1 9TG | <a href="https://www.tate.org.uk/whats-on/tate-modern/exhibition/andy-warhol?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIi53Hifrb6wIVWeJ3Ch1YewlBEAAYASAAEgKxvPD_BwE" title="Andy Warhol at the Tate Modern">tate.org.uk</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ANDY_WARHOLE_large.jpg?v=1599652363" alt="Andy Warhol Exhibition image, Tate Modern. " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>BREATH IS INVISIBLE </p>
<p>A public art project in Notting Hill acknowledging the ability of art to say things we cannot express with words, addressing issues of inequality and injustice. The third instalment, opening on the 15th September, is featuring works from photographer and artist Joy Gregory, who will be exploring the narrative and origins of plants and their relationships with humans and ecology. </p>
<p>From now until 16th October, 236 Westbourne Grove, London, W11 2RH | <a href="https://breathisinvisible.com/" target="_blank" title="Breath is Invisible website" rel="noopener noreferrer">breathisinvisable.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>FEELING INSPIRED?</p>
<p>There is said to be a link between creativity and exercise. We recommend trying out Heartcore's newest online class 'The Heartcore Class' hosted by founder Jess Schuring. It's a great way to get your body moving, build your inner strength and get your creative thinking flowing. </p>
<p>Various dates and times available to book online | <a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Heartcore website" rel="noopener noreferrer">heartcore.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Pilates-Stuido-in-Chelsea-Heartcore_large.jpg?v=1599658005" alt="Heartcore Studio Class" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/genius-design-transcends-time</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T16:23:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T16:31:36+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/genius-design-transcends-time"/>
    <title>PODCAST</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Anjhe Marcus, CO-CEO and Creative Director of Lucas Hugh, speaks to Andrea Alexa Smith about advanced technical fabric application and designing to enhance and envelop the female form.</p>
<p>Available on a variety of podcast apps &amp; online |<span> </span><a href="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1128056/5315833-anjhe-marcus-of-lucas-hugh-the-future-forward-visionary-behind-the-training-uniforms-for-the-hunger-games-catching-fire" target="_blank" title="Podcast Link to Genius Design Transcends Time, Anjhe Marcus of Lucas Hugh" rel="noopener noreferrer">Listen here</a></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Lucas_Hugh13_large.jpg?v=1599649064" alt="Lucas Hugh Genius Design Transcends Time Podcast" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/time-to-explore</id>
    <published>2020-06-26T10:46:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-06-26T10:46:05+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/time-to-explore"/>
    <title>TIME TO EXPLORE</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>With lock down easing it's a perfect time to explore, rediscover your local area or take that day trip. Here's our </span><span>recommendations...</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/time-to-explore">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Whilst the last couple of month have been difficult, there is light at the tunnel. With lock down easing it's a perfect time to explore, rediscover your local area or take that day trip. Here's our </span>recommendations...</p>
<p>LONDON</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>North - </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/estersn16/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Esters</a><span> offers a click and collect service on a range of baked goods. Perfect for picking up some lunch or a sweet treat. </span><span>Esters, </span><a href="https://www.google.co.uk/maps/place/Esters/@51.560102,-0.0802557,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x48761c63b6591db3:0x718f5037fc079036" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">55 Kynaston Road, N16 0EB</a><br><br><span>West - The newly opened </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/supermarketofdreams/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Supermarket of Dreams</a><span> offers a range of artisan produce and collaborates with a range of top chefs such as Ottolenghi and the team at Kricket. Supermarket of Dreams, </span><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/126+Holland+Park+Ave,+Notting+Hill,+London+W11+4UE/@51.5065924,-0.2106377,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x48760fe653026fb7:0xa7e393c997ad5aa7!8m2!3d51.5065924!4d-0.208449" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">126 Holland Park Ave, W11 4UE</a><br><br><span>South-East - </span><a href="https://26grains.com/restaurant/XNKj5RAAAM9xcmw0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Stoney Street</a><span> by 26 Grains prides itself on sourcing fresh top quality food prepared for you to takeaway. Stoney Street, </span><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/2+Stoney+St,+London+SE1+9AA/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x4876035778116445:0xf671147cb031227?sa=X&amp;ved=2ahUKEwic49ep55rqAhVgTRUIHR0VBQ0Q8gEwAHoECAsQAQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">2-3 Stoney Street, SE1 9AA</a></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ARTICLE_IMAGE_LAYOUT.22_large.jpg?v=1593163973" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Model Wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/halo-track-pants-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, Halo Track Pants," rel="noopener noreferrer">Halo Track pant</a>s.</p>
<p><span>STAYCATION</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>The Cotswolds - <a href="https://www.broadwaydeli.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Broadway Deli</a> in the centre of the Cotswolds is offering deliveries from their shop and other things from the village. Broadway Deli, <a href="https://www.google.com/maps?ll=52.035833,-1.861055&amp;z=15&amp;t=m&amp;hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;mapclient=embed&amp;cid=6882172791820397977" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">29 High Street WR12 7DP</a><br><br>Cornwall - Situated right on the beach <a href="http://www.gyllybeach.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gylly Beach Cafe</a> is the perfect place to grab a coffee and take a stroll. Gylly Beach Cafe, <a href="http://www.gyllybeach.com/contact/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cliff Road, Falmouth, TR11 4PA</a><br><br>Peak District - From the end of June <a href="https://www.instagram.com/riverside_kitchen_bakewell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Riverside Kitchen</a> are offering a click &amp; collect service on a range of tasty goods. Riverside Kitchen, opening soon in Bakewell, Peak District.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ARTICLE_IMAGE_LAYOUT.2_large.jpg?v=1593164069" alt="Lucas Hugh, Performance V2 Leggings" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Model wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/performance-v2-leggings-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, Performance V2 Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">Performance V2 Leggings</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home</id>
    <published>2020-04-07T11:26:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-07T11:26:10+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home"/>
    <title>Workout at Home</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Lucas Hugh share the home workout's they are tuning into.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>RELAX YOUR MIND</p>
<p>Re:Mind Studio is living streaming a range of their classes daily. A great way to calm the mind. View the timetable<span> </span><a href="https://remindstudio.com/timetable#/schedule/site/1" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Re:Mind Studio" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<p>£11 per session |<span> </span><a href="https://remindstudio.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, home workouts, remind studio" rel="noopener noreferrer">Re:mind studio</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/REMIND_STUDIO_b4d3d934-410c-45e0-8dff-9e9de60196d2_large.jpg?v=1585915157" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Re:Mind Studio " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>IF YOU LIKE TO SWITCH UP YOUR CLASSES</p>
<p>Heartcore is offering up everything from Yin Yoga to HIIT, so matter what your feeling there is guaranteed to be a class to suit you. </p>
<p>Live Stream passes available from £5 | <a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Heartcore" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heartcore </a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-04-03_at_15.00.06_large.png?v=1585922631" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Heartcore" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>PERSONAL TRAINING</p>
<p>If personal training is your preference take advantage of Twenty Two Training's virtual consultation and training sessions, tailored to you. </p>
<p>A variety of block options available from £40 per session | <a href="https://twentytwotraining.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit magazine, Twenty Two Training, Home Workouts" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twenty Two Training</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/maxresdefault_large.jpg?v=1585920852" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home workouts, Twenty Two Training" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>EQUIPMENT AT THE READY</p>
<p>If you have a set of dumbbells (or even just bottles of water), a pilates ring, exercise band and resistant bands then you're ready to take on Epoch's <span>Online </span>Dynamic Mat Pilates Class. </p>
<p>Classes daily from £10 | <a href="https://epochfitness.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Epoch Fitness" rel="noopener noreferrer">Epoch Fitness</a></p>
<p>THE STREAMING EXPERTS</p>
<p>Liz &amp; Clary from Hilliard Studio Method are no strangers to online classes and their online streaming service boasts over 3,000 minutes of video. Watch anytime, anywhere; perfect if you require a little more flexibility in your daily routine.</p>
<p>Subscribe from $20.38/ per month | <a href="https://stream.hilliardstudiomethod.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit magazine, Home workouts, Hilliard Studio Method" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hilliard Studio Method</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/hilliard2-770x513_large.jpg?v=1585921715" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Work out, Hilliard Studio Method" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/home-luxuries</id>
    <published>2020-04-07T11:25:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-07T11:37:09+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/home-luxuries"/>
    <title>HOME LUXURIES</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Sharing some of our favourite luxuries to enjoy at home. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/home-luxuries">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Sharing some of our favourite home luxuries.</p>
<p>BIG SUR AFTER RAIN</p>
<p>With top notes of coastal rain, eucalyptus and base notes of wet wood. This candle gives off a refreshing scent enough to believe you've been whisked away to California. </p>
<p>Candle by <a href="https://dsanddurga.com/products/big-sur-after-rain">D.S. &amp; Durga</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/caa22f9ab578acf497bfd3cadef5a075_large.jpg?v=1585911875" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Luxuries, Big Sur After The Rain Candle" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>DAINTREE AHA BRIGHTENING MASK</p>
<p>This multi-tasing face mask works as a spot treatment or as full-face treatment. The mask has a unique blend of Australian super fruits that help to lift dead skin cells and brighten the skin for a radiant complexion. </p>
<p>Face mask by <a href="https://drroebucks.com/collections/masks/products/daintree">Dr Roebuck's</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/1d1de97970af4e9ba6bd41377b0ba5d5_large.jpg?v=1585911957" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Face Mask, Home Luxuires" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>PERUVIAN SINGLE ORIGIN DARK CHOCOLATE EASTER EGG</p>
<p>Truly indulge with this elegantly classic, ethically sourced dark chocolate egg</p>
<p>Easter egg by <a href="https://www.rococochocolates.com/products/peruvian-single-origin-dark-chocolate-easter-egg/">Rococo Chocolates</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ETElUPDXkAEyexr_large.jpg?v=1585913117" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>BIRD OF PARADISE</p>
<p>This air purifying house plant blooms with some of the most beautiful flowers, sure to brighten up any space. Requires light watering, bright light &amp; a little humidity.</p>
<p>If based in London order the Reggie from <a href="https://www.patchplants.com/gb/en/">Patch Plants</a></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>LILA ZODA SILK PYJAMA</p>
<p>Fun and comfortable an ultimate luxury, these silk pyjama's feel divine. </p>
<p>Silk pyjama's from <a href="https://oliviavonhalle.com/collections/pyjamas/products/lila-zoda-silk-pyjama">Olivia Von Halle </a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-04-03_at_12.48.54_large.png?v=1585914571" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted</id>
    <published>2020-03-23T10:17:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-03-23T10:22:37+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted"/>
    <title>STAYING LIFTED</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>The Lucas Hugh team shares a round up of how they are keeping spirits lifted this month.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Some online resources for keeping spirits lifted this month from our team at Lucas Hugh. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>LEARN: HIGHBROW</p>
<p>At Highbrow you can find dozens of topics<span> </span>to learn about such as personal growth, history and coding. Learning comes in the format of a short daily email, over the course of 10 days. </p>
<p>Offer a free 30-day trial or sign up from $10 a month |<span> </span><a href="https://gohighbrow.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The fit, blog, Highbrow, learning" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gohighbrow.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>LISTEN: THE TONY ROBBINS PODCAST</p>
<p>Tony interviews some of the most successful people in the world, sharing their individual insights into what it means to be successful. We recommend 'Start small, think big, scale quickly'<em> </em>with SPANX founder Sara Blakely. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.tonyrobbins.com/podcasts/start-small-think-big-scale-quickly/" target="_blank" title="Sara Blakely, Tony Robbins, Spanx, lucas hugh, the fit, fit magazine" rel="noopener noreferrer">Listen here in conversation with Sara Blakely</a> | <a href="https://www.tonyrobbins.com/podcasts/" target="_blank" title="Tony Robbins, Podcast, Lucas Hugh," rel="noopener noreferrer">Tonyrobbins.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/FEATUREDQUOTE-1200X628-copy-550x288_large.jpg?v=1584958298" alt="Tony Robbins, Sara Blakely, Spanx founder, Podcast, Lucas Hugh The Fit Magazine"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>FOOD: GREEN KITCHEN STORIES</p>
<p>A vegetarian focused food blog with a vast range of nourishing and delicious looking recipes to choose from.  </p>
<p><a href="https://greenkitchenstories.com/" target="_blank" title="Food, blog, Lucas Hugh, Health, Wellness, Green Kitchen Stories" rel="noopener noreferrer">Greenkitchenstories.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Cauliflower_pasta_pesto_1-800x533-1_large.jpg?v=1584449750" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>HEALTH: CONTENT BEAUTY &amp; WELLBEING</p>
<p>This specially curated department store prides its self on finding the best natural, organic, sustainable products to enhance health &amp; wellbeing. Their website clearly talks through all certifications to help demystify the the wellness world. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.contentbeautywellbeing.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Content, Content beauty &amp; wellbeing, Health, wellbeing, " rel="noopener noreferrer">Contentbeautywellbeing.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-03-17_at_12.43.31_large.png?v=1584450286" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>EXERCISE: HEARTCORE</p>
<p>Workout Studio's may have had to temporarily close their doors however you can still enjoy your favourite studio's work out's from the comfort of your home. We are keeping an eye-out on Instagram for great tips from the team at Heartcore. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Heartcore, Workout, health, wellness, fitness" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heartcore.co.uk</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Tech_Knit_Leggings_Black_2204_large.jpg?v=1584451003" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Above Lauren is pictured wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-sports-bra-white" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit Sports Bra" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-7-8-leggings-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit 7/8 Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit 7/8 Leggings</a>. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-spring-agenda</id>
    <published>2020-02-28T11:41:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-02-28T11:50:42+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-spring-agenda"/>
    <title>YOUR SPRING AGENDA</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Jump into spring with this round up from the Lucas Hugh team.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-spring-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>VISIT: CARS: ACCELERATING THE MODERN WORLD</p>
<p>We often look to concept car design for inspiration at Lucas Hugh. Till April the V&amp;A will guide you through the history of the car and how it has shaped the modern world.</p>
<p>From now till 19<span style="font-size: 12.5px;">th </span>April 2020, V&amp;A Museum, Cromwell Road, London, SW7 2RL | <a href="https://www.vam.ac.uk/exhibitions/cars">www.vam.ac.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>EAT: MADERA AT TREE HOUSE LONDON</p>
<p>Experience experiential dining and elevated Mexican cuisine in the heart of London. Madera boasts organically sourced food and a range of gluten-free, vegan and vegetarian options served across breakfast, lunch, dinner and weekend brunch.</p>
<p>Madera At Treehouse London, 14-15 Langham Place, London, W1B 2QS |<span> </span><a href="https://www.maderalondon.com/">maderalondon.com</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/JLau_MaderaMadera29239_large.jpg?v=1582800827" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p>WATCH: THE GOOP LAB</p>
<p>Gwyneth Paltrow takes on the role of lead guinea pig in these 30-minute Netflix episodes where topics from diet, to energy healing and psychedelics are investigated and questioned by the team behind the ever intriguing Goop world.</p>
<p>Available to watch on Netflix now | <a href="https://goop.com/the-goop-lab-netflix/" target="_blank" title="goop, netflix, wellness, goop lab, watch, spring" rel="noopener noreferrer">Goop.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-02-26_at_16.50.21_large.png?v=1582801463" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p>WORKOUT: TWENTYTWO TRAINING</p>
<p>Top celebrity trainer Dalton Wong and his team at Twentytwo Training offer a private workout space in west London. Dalton's key training method incorporates the use of gliders and mini bands, simple, yet effective.</p>
<p> Twentytwo Training, 22b Elvaston Mews, Kensington, London, SW7 5HZ | <a href="https://twentytwotraining.com/" target="_blank" title="twentytwo training, game of thrones, dalton wong, lucas hugh" rel="noopener noreferrer">twentytwotraining.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/AnjheDalton_28_copy_2_large.jpg?v=1582808782" alt=""></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Above Dalton Wong and Anjhe Marcus, Lucas Hugh's Co-CEO and Creative Director. Anjhe is wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-sleeveless-t-shirt-maroon" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit Sleeveless T-shirt</a> in Maroon and the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/torque-leggings-garnet" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Torque Leggings</a> in Garnet. </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-ski</id>
    <published>2020-02-28T11:40:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-02-28T11:40:19+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-ski"/>
    <title>SPRING SKI</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[The Lucas Hugh teams round up of the best Ski destinations with the finest added extras.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-ski">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Our round up of ski destinations with the finest added extras... </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TSCHUGGEN_SWITZERLAND_2_large.png?v=1582802194" style="float: none;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TSCHUGGEN_SWITZERLAND_medium.jpeg?v=1582802223" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><strong>SPA HOTEL: TSCHUGGEN GRAND HOTEL, SWITZLERLAND</strong></p>
<p>After you have taken in the breath-taking sail inspired architecture of the Tschuggen Bergoase Spa, you could find yourself relaxing in the mountain sauna, in the rock grotto or in an indulging in a private spa treatment. If skiing has taken its toll be sure to get the Skier massage, one of the spas signature treatments, which consists of a mountain pine bath followed by a relaxing yet rejuvenating leg massage.</p>
<p><a href="https://tschuggen.ch/en/spa" target="_blank" title="spa, ski, the fit, lucas hugh, switzerland" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Tschuggen Bergoase Spa</a> at the <a href="https://tschuggen.ch/en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Tschuggen Grand Hotel, Tschuggentorweg 1, CH-7050 Arosa, Switzerland</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/der_seehof_skiliciou_04545728030c1c21513617835_medium.jpg?v=1582802288" alt=""> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/der_seehof_terrasse_0045728030c1c21513617711_large.jpg?v=1582804200" alt=""></p>
<p>GASTRO HOTEL: DER SEEHOF, AUSTRIA </p>
<p>Considered to hold one of the best restaurants in Austria. Head chef and co-owner Sepp Schellhorn creates regional, responsibly sourced, delicious food for restaurant HECHT! Enjoy breakfast during the first rays of sun and come down from the mountains to indulge in fresh food after a day on the slopes. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.derseehof.at/en/restaurant-cuisine-goldegg.html" target="_blank" title="foodie, gastro, lucas hugh, ski, skiing, Austria" rel="noopener noreferrer">HECHT! Restaurant</a> at the <a href="https://www.derseehof.at/en/start.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Der Seehof hotel, Hofmark 8, 5622 Goldegg Am See, Austria</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Deplar_12-slide_large.jpg?v=1582804261" alt=""> <strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/667_1_medium.jpg?v=1582804280" alt=""></strong></p>
<p>PURE LUXURY: DEPLAR FARM, ICELAND</p>
<p>With floor-to-ceiling windows and surrounded by nature, Deplar Farm consists of 13 en-suite bedrooms, two helipads, geothermal pools, and a ‘gear room’ stocked with all the sporting gear you would need, plus much more. You can hire just a room or go all out and rent the whole converted sheep farm. With the two helipads on site this is the perfect place for the more adventurous skier with regular heli-skiing available, otherwise sit back and enjoy the tranquillity of the farm.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.mrandmrssmith.com/luxury-hotels/deplar-farm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Deplar Farm, Deplar 570, Fljot, skagafjörôur, Iceland</a></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/guide-to-the-new-decade</id>
    <published>2019-12-20T10:52:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-20T10:52:33+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/guide-to-the-new-decade"/>
    <title>Guide to Wellness in 2020</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Lucas Hugh guide to Wellness in 2020.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/guide-to-the-new-decade">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>2020. A new decade. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>The future is about slowing down, optimising the self through restorative self-care and working towards a better future. </span></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Lucas Hugh Kubrick One Piece" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Kubric_Onepiece_326_copy_large.jpg?v=1574869132" style="float: none;"></p>
<p>LEARN: DEVELOPING A SELF PRACTICE </p>
<p>Stretch London has a workshop that promises you you'll walk away having the confidence to roll out your Yoga Mat and flow through your own practice at home or wherever your 2020 adventures take you. </p>
<p>Jan 25th, Book online | Stretch, Broadway Market, 6B Ada Street, London, E8 4QU | <a href="https://stretch-london.com/workshops?mobile=false&amp;options%5Bids%5D=4416&amp;options%5Bsite_id%5D=26803&amp;version=0" title="Stretch, London, Yoga, Workshop, 2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">stretch-london.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Panasonic Shot" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/SHOT-angle_hi-6_large.jpg?v=1574866297" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>ADVANCED TAILORING: PANASONIC SHOT DEVICE</p>
<p>Panasonic's Balance of Being collection consists of six devices that hint at the future of wellness tech. The Shot device is designed to conduct a skin analysis &amp; creates a bespoke smoothie from fresh frozen fruit &amp; vegetables based on the result to improve a person's inner &amp; outer beauty. We are a little skeptical but intrigued. </p>
<p>Balance of Being | <a href="https://panasonic.net/design/works/ifa2019/" target="_blank" title="Panasonic, 2020, future, Balance of being" rel="noopener noreferrer">panasonic.net</a></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Stretch Lab" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2019-11-27_at_11.19.14_large.png?v=1574866246" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><br>RESTORE: IN A STRETCHING CLASS</p>
<p>HIIT Classes are great for achieving our fitness goals but how we recover is just as important. ReCOVER &amp; Stretch Lab in the US &amp; UK offer assisted stretching classes to help your body recover and get you ready to go again in the new year. </p>
<p>360 7th Avenue, 4th Floor, NY 10001 |<span> </span><a href="https://www.recover.nyc/" title="Stretch, ReCover, 2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Recover.nyc</a></p>
<p>18 Wells Street, London, W1T 3PG |<span> </span><a href="https://www.stretch-lab.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="2020, Stretch Lab" rel="noopener noreferrer">stretch-lab.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="FF 91, Faraday Future" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ff-91-gallery21_large.jpg?v=1574866347" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CHOOSE BETTER: FF 91</p>
<p>Reimagining transport Faraday Future have developed the FF 91 car which is environmentally &amp; sustainably forward thinking without compromising on comfort or style. We are starting to make small steps for a better world. </p>
<p>Available to reserve | <a href="https://www.ff.com/us/ff-91/" target="_blank" title="ff, 2020, sustainable, Faraday Future, car" rel="noopener noreferrer">ff.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Aman, Resort, Wellness" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thismintymoment_dsc08605_b_high_res_12611_1_large.jpg?v=1574866404" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>DISCOVER: Aman Resorts</p>
<p>Take anything from 3-14 days on an Aman Wellness Retreat where immersive programs are designed to transform your body and mind. Expect expert guidance and uniquely tailored programs across their different resorts around the world. Whether it's stress management, detoxing, sport rehab or even looking for spiritual connection Aman will help you embark on your journey.</p>
<p>Various Locations | <a href="https://www.aman.com/wellness" target="_blank" title="aman, wellness, 2020, retreat" rel="noopener noreferrer">aman.com</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-winter-agenda</id>
    <published>2019-11-20T12:49:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-06T12:10:50+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-winter-agenda"/>
    <title>Your Winter Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Our guide of things to do this Winter.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-winter-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>LISTEN: INTELLIGENCE SQUARED PODCAST</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>For thought provoking debates on a variety of subjects look no further than the Intelligence squared podcast, great for those Sunday morning runs through the park.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Available on a variety of podcast apps &amp; online | <a href="https://www.intelligencesquared.com/podcasts/">intelligencesquared.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>RESET: RE:MIND STUDIO </p>
<p>The end of the year can get pretty busy, Re:Mind's studio is specially designed to be an escape from the hustle &amp; bustle of the city. Rediscover your calm at one of their classes.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><a href="https://shop.remindstudio.com/">Re:Mind Studio</a>, Eccleston Yards, 25A Eccleston Place, London, SW1W 9NF  |</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Remind-2_large.jpg?v=1573469216" alt="RE:MIND STUDIO" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>VISIT: MOVING TO MARS, DESIGN MUSEUM</p>
<p>At Lucas Hugh we are constantly inspired by the future. The Design museum has created a multi-sensory exhibition to get you thinking about the possibilities of future life Mars.</p>
<p>Design Museum, 224-238 Kensington High Street, London, W8 6AG |  <a href="https://designmuseum.org/">designmuseum.org</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Mars Design Museum" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Design_Museum_mars_large.jpeg?v=1573469337" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>REFUEL: HAGEN ESPRESSO BAR</p>
<p>Discover the best coffee on the King's Road right next door to our Boutique, grab a coffee and come in browse our in-store exclusives.</p>
<p>Hagen, 151 Kings Road, London SW3 5TX |  <a href="http://www.thehagenproject.com/">thehagenproject.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/2f99fc1c091d57758a8506d6e04c509d_large.jpg?v=1573469482" alt="Hagen Expresso Bar" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel-autumn-edition</id>
    <published>2019-09-13T13:29:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-02-28T11:47:36+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel-autumn-edition"/>
    <title>Fit Travel: Autumn Edition</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>From city breaks to island escapes, The Fit team recommends their favourite places and activities for fit travel this autumn.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel-autumn-edition">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/3722291-1163911_0_41_1600_800_1400_700.rc_grande.jpg?v=1568201928" style="float: none;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/FullSizeRender_medium.jpg?v=1568201967" style="float: none; margin-top: 30px; margin-bottom: 30px;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>A round-up of some of the places we recommend adding to your Autumn travel list.</span></p>
<p><strong>CITY: BARCELONA</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: Hotel The Serras</strong></p>
<p>Placed in the Gothic quarter this 5-star boutique hotel overlooks the new luxury Port Vell. Expect to find Michelin-starred chefs, a rooftop terrace &amp; cocktail pool, all to be enjoyed whilst taking in the scenic view of luxury yachts moored in the harbour. </p>
<p><a href="https://hoteltheserrasbarcelona.com/" target="_blank" title="Hotel The Serras" rel="noopener noreferrer">Passeig de Colom, 9, 08002 Barcelona, Spain</a></p>
<p><strong>Try: PB:Training</strong></p>
<p>Take your morning workout to the beach with <a href="https://www.pbtraining.online/" target="_blank" title="PB:Training" rel="noopener noreferrer">PB:Training</a>; group fitness classes focus on strength &amp; conditioning or fat burning. Alternatively, opt for a personal training session tailored to your needs.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/10f5b300f9b2f185cd850668d91c2e8a_medium.jpg?v=1568217493" style="float: none; margin-bottom: 45px;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/img-1542352325-9133-8358-C13F9158-C303-C093-A4B2820BAB179ABA__FocalPointCropWzQyMCw5NjAsNDksNTQsNzUsImpwZyIsNjUsMi41XQ_grande.jpg?v=1568202260" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>BEACH: NORTH ISLAND, NEW ZEALAND</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: Eagle's Nest Hotel</strong></p>
<p>Sat atop its own private ridgeline, the Eagle's Nest hotel &amp; retreat provides spectacular views of the Bay of Islands. They can even provide personal trainers &amp; spa therapists, this is the ultimate luxury stay. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><a href="http://www.eaglesnest.co.nz/" title="Eagles Nest New Zealand Luxury Retreat"><span>60 Tapeka Road, Russell 0242, Bay of Islands, New Zealand</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Try: Take a road trip &amp; dig your own natural spa</strong></p>
<p>Find hot water bubbling through the golden sands of <a href="https://www.thecoromandel.com/activities/must-do/hot-water-beach/" target="_blank" title="Hot Water Beach" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hot Water Beach</a> &amp; take a dip in your own natural hot spa pool either side of low-tide. </p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/435bb1d7c41722a69741f251376f6277_grande.jpg?v=1568199237" style="float: none;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ec64ecb48d16e2995c0bb6b03f382a38_medium.jpg?v=1568199277" style="float: none; margin-bottom: 120px;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>COUNTRYSIDE: UNITED KINGDOM</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: The Newt in Somerset</strong></p>
<p>In the beautiful English countryside you will find this newly opened Georgian family home. Since 1785 the estate has previously been home to seven generations of the Hobhouse family, including Arthur Hobhouse who happens to be the founder of the National Parks so you can expect the grounds to be spectacular.</p>
<p><a href="https://thenewtinsomerset.com/" target="_blank" title="The Newt Somerset" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bruton, Somerset, BA7 7NG, United Kingdom</a></p>
<p><strong>Try: Total relaxation</strong></p>
<p>After a morning stroll through the countryside head to the <a href="https://thenewtinsomerset.com/spa" target="_blank" title="The Newt In Somerset" rel="noopener noreferrer">spa</a> &amp; enjoy an ancient Hammam treatment which will relieve stress, increase circulation &amp; help ease &amp; relax any tired muscles.</p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/right-slider-ondeestamos4_medium.jpg?v=1568202563" style="float: none; margin-bottom: 125px;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Azores_Holidays.Sete_Cidades.Sao_Miguel.Azores.www_.azorschoice.com__Large_grande.jpg?v=1568202586" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>ISLAND: THE AZORES, PORTUGAL</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: Terra Nostra Garden Hotel</strong></p>
<p>Situated on the island of São Miguel next to the famous 1775 Terra Nostra Gardens this hotel is considered to be one of the best in the Azores. The hotel provides 24-hour access to the gardens where you can relax &amp; take in the lush surroundings.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span><a href="https://terranostra-gardenhotel.com/?utm_source=google-my-business&amp;utm_medium=organicsearch&amp;utm_campaign=tngh_gmb" target="_blank" title="Terra Nostra Garden Hotel" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rua Padre José Jacinto Botelho 5, 9675-061 Furnas, Portugal</a></span></p>
<p><strong>Try: Hiking</strong></p>
<p>The island has many walking <a href="http://trails.visitazores.com/en/islands/sao-miguel-0" title="Azores Trails" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">trails</a> for exploring the volcanic landscape. Staff at the Terra Nostra Hotel are friendly &amp; on hand to advise on local routes &amp; tours of the island.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-autumn-agenda</id>
    <published>2019-09-13T13:22:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-10-07T15:06:15+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-autumn-agenda"/>
    <title>YOUR AUTUMN AGENDA</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Your Autumn itinerary, made.</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-autumn-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>READ: THE MORNING MIND: USE YOUR BRAIN TO MASTER YOUR DAY AND SUPERCHARGE YOUR LIFE </p>
<p>Based on research from neuroscience &amp; medical experts this is a book that will certainly get you thinking about how you can make the most of your mornings and start your day off right, even on those mornings when the sun is hiding. </p>
<p>Written by Dr. Rob Carter III &amp; DR. Kirti Salwe Carter. Published by AMACOM | <a href="https://www.themorningmind.com/" target="_blank" title="The Morning Mind " rel="noopener noreferrer">themorningmind.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>SWEAT: IN AN ELEMENT HOT YOGA CLASS, SOMA HOUSE</p>
<p>Soma House, the luxury east London members fitness studio, have developed their own hot yoga classes based around three elements; Earth, Fire, and Water. Cool down after your class with a complimentary cold essential oil infused face cloth, don’t forget to wear your <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-hotties-black" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit Hotties">Technical Knit Hotties</a>.</p>
<p>Soma House London, Old Spitalfields Market, 8 Upper St, Horner Square, London, E1 6EW  | <a href="https://soma.house/" target="_blank" title="Soma House" rel="noopener noreferrer">soma.house</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/1.Clubhouse-SOMA_HOUSE_large.jpg?v=1566466246" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p>VISIT: ANTHONY GORMLEY, ROYAL ACADEMY</p>
<p>Said to be his most ambitious exhibition in over 10 years, Anthony Gormley one of the UK’s most <span>celebrated</span> sculptors is taking centre stage at the Royal Academy for 11 weeks with a display of classic works alongside all new installations. </p>
<p>From 21st Sept till 3rd Dec 2019, Royal Academy, Burlington House, Piccadilly, London, W1J 0BD | <a href="https://www.royalacademy.org.uk/exhibition/antony-gormley" title="Royal Academy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">royalacademy.org.uk</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/cw-35436-914x520_large.jpg?v=1566403575" alt=""> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p>EAT: DAYLESFORD, BROMPTON CROSS</p>
<p>Daylesford opened their fourth outpost last year. Stop by to experience truly fresh, organic food, straight from the farm in their café or do a spot of shopping in their farm shop. Being all about nature they have even installed a tree felled from their Cotswolds farm in the centre of their store!</p>
<p>Daylesford, 76-82 Sloane Avenue, Brompton Cross, London, SW3 3DZ | <a href="https://www.daylesford.com/locations/brompton-cross-sw3/" target="_blank" title="Daylesford" rel="noopener noreferrer">daylesford.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/NW-Daylesford-Organic-Brompton-Cross_large.jpg?v=1566465903" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-little-black-book-of-health-and-fitness</id>
    <published>2019-06-24T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:09:06+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-little-black-book-of-health-and-fitness"/>
    <title>The Little Black Book of Health and Fitness</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>BEAUTY EDITOR </span><a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/meet-susannah-taylor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SUSANNAH TAYLOR</a><span> REVEALS THE WELLBEING EXPERTS WHO HELPED HER STAY ON TOP OF HER GAME. </span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-little-black-book-of-health-and-fitness">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>BEAUTY EDITOR SUSANNAH TAYLOR REVEALS THE WELLBEING EXPERTS WHO HELPED HER STAY ON TOP OF HER GAME. </p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>The boom in all things fitness and health in the last 5 years has meant a recent explosion of wellbeing ‘experts’. Thanks to social media, everyone can build a public profile now which is a wonderful empowering tool. However I would advise against taking every ‘expert’s’ word as Gospel – someone may have 100k followers, but their advice may not be 100% correct.</p>
<p>Thanks to my job, I have access to many wellness gurus, and below are the ones that I really trust, who have invaluable experience under their belts and whose advice and training is researched, thorough and relevant. Some may not have a huge following on social media, but that’s because a true pro isn’t about Instagram stats, flashing a six pack, or taking Belfies, it’s about knowledge, experience and how they translate it to you.</p>
<p>These people, in my opinion, know their stuff:</p>
<p> </p>
<p><span class="s1"><b>FITNESS</b></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Joslyn Thompson-Rule</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">A Nike Global Master Trainer for good reason - what Joslyn doesn’t know about fitness or fuelling for fitness isn’t worth knowing. Someone who puts her knowledge and integrity above creating ridiculous poses on Instagram, she is one of the most knowledgeable people I know in the fitness world. Creator of the Women in Fitness Summit which she hosted last year, her aim is to bring proper expert knowledge and advice to the wellness industry. A badass herself, she is a Crossfit competitor, strength coach, mama and all-around cool chick.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/joslynthompsonrule/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@Joslynthompsonrule</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><strong><span class="s1">Dalton Wong</span></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Dalton Wong started out his career in rehabilitation so he, therefore, understands the functioning and structure of the human body like no one else. A stickler for good form whilst exercising, he is often called upon by Hollywood stars, whipping them into shape for demanding roles with his calm, un-shouty manner.</p>
<p class="p3"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/dalton_wong22/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s2"><span class="s1">@dalton_wong22</span></span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s2"><a href="http://www.twentytwotraining.com"><span class="s3">www.twentytwotraining.com</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>David Kingsbury</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Lululemon ambassador David Kingsbury is an excellent personal trainer and Pilates specialist. A keen sportsman, David’s rugby career was struck by injury, but rehabilitation taught him the importance of a structured training regime and led him into the world of personal training (lucky us!). David’s approach is extremely thorough and his knowledge of the body, how to strengthen it and how to prevent or work with injury is exceptional. Today he works out of his studio near Notting Hill.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/dk_opus/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@dk_opus</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s2"><a href="http://www.opusfitness.co.uk"><span class="s3">www.opusfitness.co.uk</span></a></span></p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LBB__1_large.jpg?v=1555428260" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><br>FITNESS AND NUTRITION</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Louise Parker</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">I have personally witnessed the transformative effects of the Louise Parker Method with friends of mine that have done it. It uses a four pillar approach: Think Successfully, Eat Beautifully, Workout Intelligently and Live Well to get results. The go-to trainer for many a film star (and some say the Royal family) Louise has a real, common sense, no gimmicks approach to transforming your body and health and a deep understanding of the female body and the demands on us ladies (she has had three children herself). With trainers and nutritionists in-house that can liaise with you wherever you are in the world, she also has two books so you can learn about her method for a fraction of the price. The Louise Parker Method: Lean for Life and The Louise Parker Method: Lean for Life cookbook</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/louiseparkermethod/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@louiseparkermethod</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s4"><a href="http://www.louiseparker.com">www.louiseparker.com</a></span></p>
<p class="p1"><strong><span class="s1">James Duigan of Bodyism</span></strong></p>
<p class="p1">James Duigan is one of the best-known names in health and fitness. A gentle but clever man whose motto is ‘Be kind’, he and his Bodyism team place as much importance on positivity and your mindset as getting your body in shape. Having first arrived from Australia homeless and sleeping on London’s night buses, he has come a loooong way to the Bodyism home where he now resides in Notting Hill. James’ Clean and Lean books are, in my opinion, the original and still the best, simplest way to eat and exercise for good health.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/jamesduigan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s2">@jamesduigan</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s4"><a href="http://www.bodyism.com">www.bodyism.com</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>NUTRITION</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Amelia Freer </b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Nutritional therapist Amelia Freer has a refreshing view on how we eat. Firmly anti-diet, she encourages people to nourish themselves, rather than restrict. Well known for Sam Smith’s makeover, Amelia is hugely knowledgeable about the human body and how eating the correct foods can change how we feel and function, working with other experts to test for dietary deficiencies as well as a psychotherapist who specialises in food-related issues if you need it. Above all Amelia loves fresh, nutritious food, straight from the ground (you should see her veggie patch!) to feed the body mind and soul and her books, Eat Nourish Glow, Cook Nourish Glow and Nourish &amp; Glow: the 10 Day plan all reflect that.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ameliafreer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@ameliafreer </span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="http://ameliafreer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1"><span class="s3">amelia</span>freer.com</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>James Collins</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">James is a leading sport and exercise nutritionist and is President of the Royal Society of Medicine’s Food and Health Forum. Currently working as a consultant with European football, James also applies his knowledge of the sporting elite to non-athletes especially those of us with a fitness or health goal in mind. A regular columnist for the Telegraph, he speaks a lot of sense.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/jamescollinspn/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@jamescollinspn</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="http://jamescollinsnutrition.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">jamescollinsnutrition.com</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Anthony Warner – aka The Angry Chef</strong></p>
<p>Fed up of reading about nutrition from people in a g-string bikini or a pair of Speedos? The Angry Chef has your back. A chef for 25 years, the Angry Chef is not a nutritionist and nor does he pretend to be but he writes absolutely brilliant articles questioning the truth about peoples claims surrounding food. Things that make him angry: people making unscientific claims about the health benefits of diets, recipes and ingredients, people who present themselves as experts without the qualifications to back themselves up, and food manufacturers making false claims about their products etc. His hilarious, no bullsh*t writing is much needed in our ‘everyone is an expert’ age.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.angry-chef.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.angry-chef.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>YOGA</b></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Mercedes Sieff</b></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mercedes is one of the UK’s leading Vinyasa Flow Yoga instructors and one half of the award-winning Yeotown Retreat and Yeotown Kitchen on London’s chic Chiltern Street. Teaching a popular weekly class at London’s Triyoga, her classes involve bold, creative sequencing, and encourages students to explore more contemporary, challenging asanas. A wise soul who is authentic in everything she does she is also a qualified positive psychology coach.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/mercedessieff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@mercedessieff</span></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.yeotown.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">yeotown.com</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Tara Lee </b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Tara has been practising yoga for over 20 years, and if you know yoga, you’ll know that experience means a lot on the yoga mat. Specialising in Vinyasa Flow, pregnancy and postnatal yoga, Tara is also a teacher of teachers and runs intensive courses for teachers a few times a year. Teaching a dynamic form of yoga Tara is influenced by many styles including Ashtanga, Sivananda and Para yoga, and her students rave about a stronger, leaner, more flexible body as well as an increased sense of well-being as a result. I have found her postnatal DVD invaluable post birth.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/taraleeyoga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@taraleeyoga</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s2"> <a href="http://www.taraleeyoga.com"><span class="s3">www.taraleeyoga.com</span></a></span></p>
<p><strong>Tass Cambitzi</strong></p>
<p>If you think Yoga is all about lying on the floor taking a few easy stretches and a few deep breaths, then get yourself to Tass Cambitzi’s Power Yoga class at Triyoga in Shoreditch or Soho Farmhouse in Oxfordshire. In this tough Vinyasa Flow workout, Tass will challenge you way beyond your personal limitations. With a strong, precise flow of sun salutations, core work, inversions (she’ll have you attempting head and handstands in no time), Tass is a stickler for correct form and function, believing that building a stronger body will create a steady mind. One of the most exhilarating classes I have ever been to (all set to a great new soundtrack every time) it has become a highlight of my week and has done more for my body than any gym workout ever could.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/alignedwith/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@alignedwith</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.alignedwith.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.alignedwith.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Nicole Page-Croft</strong></p>
<p>There is a magnetic aura of worldly-wise spirituality that surrounds Oxfordshire-based Nicole. Originally from Australia but brought up in South-East Asia she has been practising yoga for 20 years and teaching for more than 12. With a degree from Oxford University and two Diplomas in Buddhist philosophy under her Yogi belt, she is adept at translating her learnings into practical teachings for modern life (I have been on Nicole’s retreats and we all hang on her every word). A fountain of knowledge in pre and postnatal yoga and birth, her book The Good Birth Companion is a must for expectant mothers and her Dynamic Flow class is playful, challenging and cleverly suits everyone from beginners to the very advanced.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.nicolecroftyoga.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.nicolecroftyoga.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3>PILATES</h3>
<p><strong>Chloe Hodgson</strong></p>
<p>Visit Soho Farmhouse in Oxfordshire on a Friday morning at 10.25, and you can expect to be mown down by a small army super chic, legging’d ladies all making a beeline for Chloe Hodgson’s 10.30amPilates class. Packed out every week, the Stott trained, steel-stomached Chloe delivers impeccably precise instructions guaranteed to strengthen nearly every muscle in your body. The results are a firmer bod and stronger core which will not only enhance your usual fitness regime (and create a tight, toned body) but will prevent injury and help bolster your body to bear the brunt of everyday life.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/chloespilates/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@chloespilates</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.chloespilates.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.chloespilates.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>MEDITATION</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Jillian Lavender</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">If you want to learn how to meditate, forget the books and the apps, just speak to Jillian Lavender from the London Meditation Centre who is a total authority on the subject. Back in 1995 Jillian once had a job as the CEO of a publishing company so she knows what it’s like to live a manic lifestyle. Close to burnout, Jillian started meditating and felt her anxiety fall away, so she decided to train as a teacher. Having dedicated her life to teaching Vedic meditation (the oldest form there is), Jillian’s course will help you understand very clearly how to do meditation and what it can do for you. It’s the best 8 hours I ever spent.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/londonmeditationcentre/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@londonmeditationcentre</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s4"><a href="http://www.londonmeditationcentre.com">www.londonmeditationcentre.com</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>LIFE COACHING</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Jacqueline Hurst</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Jacqueline will fix you. Having struggled in life when she was younger with drugs, alcohol, anorexia and anxiety, she went on a mission to change her mindset and in the process transformed her life. Today, as a life coach and hypnotherapist she sees clients with all manner of problems, from weight issues, eating/ body image issues, to addictions, and low confidence. Straight talking and to the point, she has an innate understanding of people and pour psyche and is on a life mission to help people turn their lives around. She rocks.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/jacqueline_hurst_/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@jacqueline_hurst_ </span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="http://www.jacquelinehurst.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">www.jacqualinehurst.com</span></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>For more insight on health and beauty in London, follow <a href="http://www.instagram.com/susannahtaylor_" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@susannahtaylor_</a></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/a-trip-of-ones-own</id>
    <published>2019-06-10T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-10T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/a-trip-of-ones-own"/>
    <title>A Trip of One&apos;s Own</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Francesca White discusses the joys of solo travel. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/a-trip-of-ones-own">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3>Travelling alone doesn't have to be lonely.</h3>
<p>The first time I went travelling by myself was to Spain, about seven years ago. I was headed to a gorgeous, off-the-beaten-track farmhouse, two hours south of Cadiz. It was only when I turned the key in the ignition of the hire car that I released I didn’t know how to drive on the other side of the road. Or have a map.</p>
<p>When I finally arrived, the relief of having made in it one piece hit me like a tidal wave. The air smelled different, of flowers and smoke; the views across scrubby, undulating hills were endless. I appreciated it all the more for having got there under my own steam.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashuh_thefit_travelling_solo-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555503114" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>It’s amazing how much you learn about yourself when you travel solo. Every encounter is highly charged. Like the time I tried to park on a narrow, near-vertiginous road in the local town for supper. (I never made it to supper). Or when I arrived at a bar that had been recommended for its quiet location, only to find it in full, fiesta swing. At that moment, I was painfully aware of being alone.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>It’s amazing how much you learn about yourself - every encounter is highly charged.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>But there were moments of brilliance, too. Like stumbling upon the most gorgeous fruit market, en route to the beach, where I remained for the rest of the day. Or eating breakfast on my tiny patio in the sun (that bread basket lives on in my memory).</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/travelsolo-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555503117" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Travelling alone gives you free rein to wander endlessly – or to sit in a café and people-watch behind big sunglasses. It leads to unexpected conversations - with taxi drivers and shopkeepers. It encourages you to sit in a restaurant and order food in a foreign language – or to lose yourself in a book whilst your prawns go cold. It is an adventure; a chance to cultivate a relationship with yourself, and to discover a part of you that you didn’t know existed. Which is what travel is all about, isn’t it?</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/reclaiming-my-attention-span</id>
    <published>2019-06-04T12:38:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-04T12:38:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/reclaiming-my-attention-span"/>
    <title>Reclaiming My Attention Span</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Beauty Editor Madeleine Spencer realises her relationship with her phone is less than healthy.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/reclaiming-my-attention-span">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>I realised things had to change over Christmas. Riddled with a cold which wiped me out, I spent more time lying prone on my phone than with my family. While the distraction from the relentless cough was merciful, looking back, I can’t recall what absorbed me: a picture on Instagram by my favourite blogger? A meaty op-ed on the #metoo movement? A cutesy video of a friend’s baby?</p>
<p>Whatever held my attention captive didn’t remain embedded in my memory, and that’s when I decided that my phone wasn’t giving me anything but a kick of dopamine with every like or comment.</p>
<p>I started with rules. I vowed to switch my phone to airplane mode overnight for at least nine hours. Preferably twelve. I also decided that I would have a tea and do some stretches in the morning before checking social media to give my mind some quiet time without the possibility of FOMO. When eating out, rather than have my phone face down on the table like a baby monitor, it had to remain in my bag, unchecked.</p>
<p>At first, the compulsion to check my phone was the hardest. My hands reached for it and my brain kept looping round to ‘look at phone mode’. It was as if it had been programmed to check, check, and check again. When my phone was in another room, I knew it was there, pulsing, living, a porthole to other lives. And I ignored it.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefit_phonerelationship-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555501060" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<blockquote>
<p>My hands reached for it and my brain kept looping round to ‘look at phone mode’.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>After a few weeks, I was reading more, and as my voracious appetite for books returned, so too did my attention span. Following the twists and turns of a character’s life unpunctuated by phone, breaks became a fun pastime, a thing to do for hours. I felt more engaged IRL, too, and found myself enjoying others in the flesh far more than I had in years. In short, I felt more like my core self than I had in a long time.</p>
<p>I am by no means there yet. In an absolutely ideal world, I’d check my phone once daily, twice at most. As a journalist, that’s not a reality, but adjusting my relationship with my phone has been undoubtedly positive and I fully intend on keeping mental - not electronic - tabs on my phone usage going forward.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-ella-wroath</id>
    <published>2019-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-ella-wroath"/>
    <title>High Performer: Ella Wroath</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Founder of Soul Circus, the annual yoga and wellness festival based in the Cotswolds.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-ella-wroath">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Breezing in from France in floaty florals ahead of a pop-up event at Equinox Kensington, I couldn’t have foreseen the open-hearted insights <a href="https://www.soulcircus.yoga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Soul Circus festival</a> founder Ella Wroath was about to share.</p>
<p>Moving to Cheltenham after a break-up, Ella spotted a gap in the market to build a community around hot yoga and so, along with her sister, she founded Ella and Fleur Hot Yoga.</p>
<p>From there, she and husband Roman went on to create Soul Circus three years ago, the first UK festival to fuse yoga and music now held annually in the Cotswolds.</p>
<p>Hearing the story of her journey to this point, I was struck by the bravery it took for Ella to go with her gut feeling and make some tough decisions, not least to run the first Soul Circus festival just 6 weeks after the birth of her first son.</p>
<p>How did it all start? Well, ‘I got sacked basically’, Ella confesses, ‘I got fired pretty much from everywhere because I couldn’t work for other people – I kept thinking what’s wrong with me? …It transpired that I needed to go and do my own thing’.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/EllaWroath_TheFit_large.jpg?v=1555423982" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Realising the need to find a career that made her happier, Ella discovered yoga. With a background in dance, yoga offered the balance she was seeking between an innate need for movement and the desire to help people; a deep-seated feeling she uncovered whilst working in a role in welfare.</p>
<p>Winding back further, the turning point for Ella was taking a job dancing in the parade at Disneyland Paris aged 18. A bold decision given that work relocation and travel was much less common amongst her peers at the time.</p>
<p>‘I got back from that and I thought – if I can just go to Paris and work at Disneyland, then I can go anywhere. That changed my mindset’ she says thoughtfully.</p>
<p>Ella went on to work a ski season in Europe, teach English in Japan and then move to London. ‘If an opportunity arises, I just go for it,’ she enthuses, ‘I like the unknown and there’s also that innate feeling that everything will always be alright’.</p>
<p>What drives her to keep facing new challenges? As the eldest of five siblings and now a mother of two, Ella wants to show her children ‘that you don’t have to be scared of things. You can be brave and positive and try new things because you’ll always be fine - watch mummy and daddy do ridiculous things and figure it out as we go!’</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/soulcircus_large.jpg?v=1555423980" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>‘The chance to try something new, to learn, to create something that’s never happened before’ gives Ella purpose. Watching Faithless DJ live during a yoga class at Soul Circus last year, Ella was struck by the special moment they had created finding joy in the excitement of their guests, and the thought that ‘this has never happened anywhere else in the world’.</p>
<p>Just as things began to feel comfortable in Cheltenham, last year Roman and Ella decided they needed a change and so moved to rural France. ‘We’re encouraged to grind, grind, grind and then retire, but by that point you’ve missed your entire life – so we decided we’d try to have mini-retirements along the way’.</p>
<p>Ella’s sense of courage and adventure is infectious; I have a feeling that whatever she goes on to do next, it certainly won’t be boring!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/running-well</id>
    <published>2019-05-23T11:18:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-23T11:18:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/running-well"/>
    <title>Running Well</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>How keeping a regular running schedule helps journalist Rosie Green.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/running-well">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Thud, thud, thud. I can feel the mud underfoot, the gentle mist on my face, the welcome sunlight on my skin.  I can feel the ache in my legs and the blood pounding in my ears. Running is when I am most connected to, and most in awe of, my body. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">The link between running and mental wellbeing has gone from hokey to hard fact. Research now shows physical activity 100% improves our mood. It certainly improves my relationship with myself. On, and after, a run I am charged with possibility.  I can write the novel, set up the business, deal with that deadline! Self-doubt is quashed, anxiety contained.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_running_thefit-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555577665" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">If I don’t run I’m generally cross with myself. I start berating myself for being lumpen and lazy. I feel less attractive. When I look in the mirror I am disappointed. It’s taken me a decade to realise that skipping one run doesn’t have any real effect on my appearance, but that self-dissatisfaction clouds how I view my reflection.  It would take longer than we have here to untangle all my self-esteem issues, but when the feel-good exercise hormones are circulating in my body, there’s little room left for any self-loathing. Put simply, if I run I like myself better. End of.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Running is the only time I really think deeply, where there’s enough space and silence for thoughts to fully form and evolve. I don’t run with music, I don’t want another person’s viewpoint to cloud my thoughts. Even when I think there is no time for a run, if I go, the world somehow keeps turning and I feel a million times brighter at the end of it.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Truth is, I’ve never regretted a run.  And how many things can you say that about?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Now, if you’ll excuse me…</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-mimi-xu</id>
    <published>2019-05-22T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-mimi-xu"/>
    <title>High Performer: Mimi Xu</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>"I get bored if I just do one thing – there are so many layers of things you can do in life."</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-mimi-xu">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p>Wide-eyed and effervescent, even before coffee, I’m immediately in awe of <a href="https://www.instagram.com/mimixumusic/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mimi Xu’s</a> passion and drive. DJ, producer, composer, artist - Mimi has become a respected name in fashion, music and art around the world.</p>
<p>During her teens, Mimi rejected her background in classical piano realizing that ‘it was about playing what you’ve been told to well’, but limits creativity. ‘Only later I realised I could use what I knew from before, but I needed to liberate myself from that to see it.’</p>
<p>Stepping into the unknown and seeing purpose with hindsight was a theme apparent in all we discussed.</p>
<p>Mimi stepped away from classical music and into fashion, later combining her passions for fashion, music and composition. She moved cities several times, curating shows for top designers around the globe, never knowing the outcome but always taking the leap. Does she ever get scared? ‘Not really. There are so many fears, but if you keep thinking about things you’d never do anything’</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thefit_mimixu_profile-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555576702" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>There’s not a hint of self-importance to Mimi, she continually shifts the focus from herself to her work, lighting up as she discusses the purpose behind her projects.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s the beauty of experimentation – start with a frame and see what comes.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>By her own admission, Mimi is a workaholic. ‘I get bored if I just do one thing – there are so many layers of things you can do in life you just have to be very organized’.</p>
<p>Mimi divides her time between commissioned work and creative projects. One such project is<a href="https://www.instagram.com/awkwardmoments_series/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Awkward Moments</a>; a mixed media series with the intention of ‘breaking barriers between audience and performers, getting people involved to feel what we feel’.</p>
<p>In the second instalment, much to her surprise, all 50 performers and guests ended up naked. She shared a story of a friend battling cancer who left having forgotten his anxiety with new-found body confidence. The whole group felt empowered. ‘I never thought I was capable of doing that’ she says, the excitement of the unknown spurring her on.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/mimi_xu_-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555576738" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>‘That’s the beauty of experimentation – start with a frame and see what comes… Art is not about certainty, that’s cinema, experimentation is what I like – living in the moment is what interests me in live performance’</p>
<p>For Mimi, success is not about being popular, ‘I’m not making mainstream work, it’s not for everyone’ she explains, ‘for me, success is about feeling I’ve pushed boundaries and made the next step.’</p>
<p>‘I think you have to see outside of the box even if you work a 9-5, do your own thing and make it interesting, otherwise, your life can pass by really fast.’</p>
<p>It’s clear that Mimi grasps opportunities with both hands, and enjoys every step of the journey.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/creative-reflections</id>
    <published>2019-05-15T15:44:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:09:05+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/creative-reflections"/>
    <title>Creative Reflections</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[From a two-time Oscar-winning costume designer to the director of an explosive documentary following Vivienne Westwood, Bridget Arsenault asks four of the film industry’s most-accomplished women to reflect on a pivotal moment in their careers.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/creative-reflections">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>From a two-time Oscar-winning costume designer to the director of an explosive documentary following Vivienne Westwood, Bridget Arsenault asks four of the film industry’s most-accomplished women to reflect on a pivotal moment in their careers.</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong>Having never been to film school, Quinn Shephard got her education on set, from as young as five, starring in shows like Hostages alongside Toni Collette and The Blacklist. Now only 23 years old, at 20, Quinn wrote, directed, starred in and produced her first feature film, Blame.</strong></p>
<p>I think I began my career by breaking the status quo, which was very daunting… I set out to do something that was pretty unprecedented for multiple reasons: my age, my level of experience, and even our budget level for the film. I constantly get people asking how I did what I did at my age, and I usually just answer “I don’t know, it’s just who I am!” It’s not like I woke up every day like “wow, I’m shattering boundaries.” I just did what I always wanted to do.</p>
<p><strong>Jenny Beavan, OBE has won two Academy Awards and received nominations an additional eight times, including for her work on Gosford Park, The King’s Speech and The Remains of the Day. Most recently Jenny triumphed in 2016 for her Costume Design on Mad Max: Fury Road, which also gained her the BAFTA. When Jenny accepted her BAFTA host Stephen Fry made a cutting remark about her appearance. Jenny has beautifully harnessed this moment and negativity to propel her career forward.</strong></p>
<p>Having worked predominately on period pieces, being offered and accepting the job to design the costumes for Mad Max: Fury Road felt quite revolutionary in its own right. Working on that film opened up so many new avenues both in work and life. In work: now I’m offered a hugely greater diversity of projects and life as a ‘feminist’, although I am not sure I am a very good one, but apparently, I am some kind of role model to young women!! Looking back, I wouldn’t approach any of it any differently. I would have accepted the job - such s fantastic opportunity, and the aftermath was unexpected, but I am quite happy now with the way it turned out!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/creative_reflections_TheFit-1_large.jpg?v=1555425843" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p><strong>Lorna Tucker started her work in film in her 20s, primarily behind the camera producing tour videos and music promos. Her feature-length debut came only this year with Westwood: Punk, Icon, Activist, which premiered at the 2018 Sundance Film Festival. Lorna’s second documentary Amá, which will be released later this year, examines the issue of sterilisation abuses of Native American women in the United States and their fight for reproductive rights. It was co-produced by Colin Firth.</strong></p>
<p>A pivotal moment was saying no to Vivienne Westwood when she told me to re-edit elements of the film. For better or for worse, I knew I had to retain complete creative and editorial control, and I'm super proud of the results! Unfortunately, I knew that when I said no to her there would be consequences because of who she is and how powerful she is. Since Westwood was released, Vivienne's team have reached out to the fashion world and I've now been blacklisted by much of the industry and several fashion magazines have said they won't review the film or interview me due to their loyalty to Vivienne. It's a real shame, but I had to stay true to my vision and retain my integrity. The final edit of Westwood is not only an authentic and honest portrait of Vivienne, but it's also a true representation of my vision as a film-maker.</p>
<p><strong>Set designer Stella Fox has worked on everything from the mega-blockbuster Star Wars: The Force Awakens to Jane Campion’s John Keats biopic Bright Star. Stella’s work has taken her as far afield as Jordan, Budapest, Istanbul, Italy, Azerbaijan, the UAE and Malta. By no means restricted to film, one of her most notable projects was Channel 4’s sci-fi series Misfits, which won a BAFTA for production design in 2011.</strong></p>
<p>A few years after working on Star Wars: The Force Awakens, I was given the opportunity to join the same team on Star Wars: Episode VIII as an assistant set decorator. I imagine the majority of people would’ve jumped at the chance, but I turned it down. I wanted to stick to my guns as a decorator in my own right rather than assisting. I think this was a turning point in my career. I am now an established set decorator and have gone on to head up a wide variety of independent feature films and television series, including Entebbe starring Rosamund Pike and Danny Boyle’s new TV show Trust. It was incredibly tempting at the time to jump at the opportunity offered up to me rather than venturing forth on my own. However, I wouldn’t change a thing.</p>
<p><em>A longtime journalist and the former Associate Editor at Vanity Fair UK, <a href="https://www.bridgetarsenault.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bridget</a> has written for a number of respected publications, including Forbes, British Vogue, Departures, Travel+Leisure, House &amp; Garden and Architectural Digest.</em></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel</id>
    <published>2019-05-10T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:09:27+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel"/>
    <title>Fit Travel</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>From city breaks to mountain retreats, The Fit team recommends their favourite places and activities for fit travel.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Travel is for experiencing new cultures, places and, for us, fitness. This summer, take a vacation from your usual regime and try something a little different, you’ll be better for it.</span></p>
<p><span>CITY - PARIS</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Stay: Le Bristol</p>
<p>A family-run hotel that is equal parts classic and modern Parisian. Inside the rooms are spacious (hard to find in Paris) and each of the restaurants boasts two Michelin stars.</p>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.oetkercollection.com/fr/destinations/le-bristol-paris/?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=local&amp;utm_campaign=lebristolparis" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">112 Rue du Faubourg Saint-Honoré, 8th, Paris, France</a></strong></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Try: Dynamo Cycling</p>
<p>Burn off last night's cheese plate at a <a href="https://lucashugh.myshopify.com/products/performance-v2-capri-leggings-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">high-intensity</a> spin class led by top French instructors. Just don't forget to brush up on your French phrases before you go: "climb = montée" "resistance on = résistance sur"</p>
<p><strong><a href="http://24%20Rue%20Chauchat,%2075009%20Paris,%20France" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">24 Rue Chauchat, 75009 Paris, France</a></strong></p>
<p><strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Paris_Dynamo_LucasHugh_large.jpg?v=1554985498" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></strong></p>
<p> BEACH - MONTAUK</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Stay: The Surf Lodge</p>
<p>A simple and chic waterside retreat with sunbleached walls, fresh seafood and a laidback vibe, The Sufe Lodge is everything you want from beach break.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.thesurflodge.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">183 Edgemere St, Montauk, NY 11954, USA</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thesurflodge_baristudio_lucashugh_large.jpg?v=1554985540" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Try: Physiculture</p>
<p>You don't have to go far to keep fit at The Surf Lodge. During the summer season, the lodge hosts 'Physiculture' a line up of health and wellness programmes including expert panel discussions and Bari Studio <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/shop/all-clothing/kubrick-7-8-legging" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">sculpt</a> classes.</p>
<p>MOUNTAINS - ATLAS MOUNTAINS</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Stay: Kasbah Bab Ourika</p>
<p>A magical eco-friendly stay with unforgettable views across lush mountains to the wide dessert beyond. Settle into a book on one of the sun-baked terraces by day and walk the landscaped gardens by night to take in the breathtaking sky full of stars.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.kasbahbabourika.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Ourika valley, Tnine Ourika, Maroccco</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Kasbah_morrocco_lucashugh_large.jpg?v=1554985633" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Try: Mountain Meditation</p>
<p>Take to the Kasbah's rooftop for a <a href="https://lucashugh.myshopify.com/products/stirrup-technical-knit-leggings-marine" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">yoga</a> session in truly enchanting surrounds. Reset and realign in the total serenity of the Ourika Valley.</p>
<p>ISLAND - BA OF ISLANDS, NZ</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Stay: Eagles Nest</p>
<p>Comprised of five individual villas, this 75-acre estate sits atop a private peninsula overlooking the iconic Bay of Islands. Each villa has it's own heated infinity lap pool and once you tire of that, access to one of the estate's secluded pristine beaches.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.eaglesnest.co.nz/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">60 Tapeka Rd, Russell 0242, New Zealand</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/russel_nz_lucashugh_large.jpg?v=1554985583" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Try: An Overnight Hike</p>
<p>Take on the Cape Brett Walkway which travels 16km along the ridge of Cape Brett Peninsula all the way to the lighthouse at its end. Wear your <a href="https://lucashugh.myshopify.com/products/performance-v2-leggings-black" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">best gear</a> as the track is all hills - and be prepared to stay overnight in the DOC hut, it's an experience!</p>
<p><a href="https://www.doc.govt.nz/parks-and-recreation/places-to-go/northland/places/cape-brett-and-whangamumu-area/things-to-do/cape-brett-track/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cape Brett Walkway</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/take-a-break</id>
    <published>2019-04-21T17:58:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:17:27+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/take-a-break"/>
    <title>Take A Break</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Go on, treat yourself.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/take-a-break">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>We’ve curated a list of places and spaces where the only agenda is to take a break from the daily grind, because everyone is allowed to be selfish, occasionally.</p>
<h3><span>STOP AND SMELL THE FLOWERS</span></h3>
<p><span>One of the best things about London is the sheer amount of green space available and <em><a href="https://www.kew.org/">Kew Gardens</a> </em>is one of the most generous on offer. Take a day to meander, breath the fresh air and bask in the enormity of it all.</span></p>
<h3><span> </span></h3>
<h3><span>FACE FIRST</span></h3>
<p>Give your face ultimate treat and book yourself in for '<a href="https://www.lanesboroughclubandspa.com/the-spa/facials/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Method</a>' facial at The Lanesborough. Performed by renowned Facialist, Anastasia Achilleos, you’ll leave with not only glowing skin but a complete mood reset.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_magazine_take_a_break-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555510728" alt=""></span></h3>
<h3><span>SWEAT IT OUT</span></h3>
<p><span>Take yourself to the brink and back with <a href="https://www.metaboliclondon.com/about-our-classes/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Meta-Row</a> at Metabolic London. An intense, full body workout guaranteed to leave you feeling elated. Plus, bonus bragging rights that you were into indoor rowing before it became a ‘Thing."</span></p>
<h3><span> </span></h3>
<h3><span>SIMPLE PLEASURES</span></h3>
<p><span>Sometimes the best things come from the simplest of activities. Reserve yourself some time on Sunday morning and take yourself to your favourite local cafe. </span>Read the weekend papers over eggs and coffee, and always get the brownie for later.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/surface-skin</id>
    <published>2019-04-21T17:58:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:17:33+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/surface-skin"/>
    <title>Surface Skin</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>How one beauty editor realised her relationship with her skin was more than surface deep.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/surface-skin">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>BY <a href="https://www.instagram.com/madeleinelovesthis/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Madeleine Spencer</a></p>
<p>After my first sleepover at my husband’s, I snuck into the bathroom, a Laura Mercier compact stashed in my hand, ready to conceal my spots. Then, it was inconceivable to me to bare my skin in front of someone I fancied. Scratch that - I wouldn’t go barefaced in front of anyone bar the very few who weren’t shocked that under my foundation lay scars and bumps and redness galore because of the acne that’s plagued my adult life.</p>
<p>I don’t use the word plagued lightly. Spots are more than an inconvenience, an issue that antibiotics or a cracking cleanser may clear. Spots - of all varieties be it deep, pulsating, painful ones, little red ones that gather heat, or just tiny blackheads populating a nose - often come with a side of shame, a hint of assumed culpability. I would feel the need to explain them, to apologise for their presence.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefi_surfaceskin-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555500925" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>My job as a Beauty Editor only served to compound this embarrassment; I felt fraudulent to be doling out advice when covered in bumps and pits.</p>
<p>I had a eureka moment after seeing a facialist who didn’t ask me anything about the products I used - she asked me about my hormones, about my stress levels. She took me out of the equation, which, ironically, served to forge a better relationship between me and my skin; suddenly, it wasn’t my fault - it was the result of my PCOS (Polycystic ovary syndrome) combined with a busy life.</p>
<p>Since then, I’ve come to regard my skin as an organ that is doing its very best under trying circumstances, not as some manifestation of some flaw in me.</p>
<p>As I type, my face is free of make-up. My husband is about to come home from work with two friends, and I fully intend to socialise nude of face, despite the three rather prominent spots on my chin. Those spots, they’re not me. I live under them.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/age-is-just-a-number</id>
    <published>2019-04-18T09:31:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:19:43+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/age-is-just-a-number"/>
    <title>Age is Just a Number</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Are the over 40’s now as hip as 20-year-olds?  </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/age-is-just-a-number">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Susannah Taylor asks the question, is age now irrelevant in modern society?</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Last August, the cult US beauty and health magazine Allure magazine released a statement saying they were changing their narrative around growing older and that they were banning the phrase ‘anti-ageing.’ Editor, Michelle Lee explained the decision, saying “Whether we know it or not we are subtly reinforcing the message that ageing is a condition we need to battle.” It was the beginning of an avalanche of other beauty businesses following suit who are, as a result, now putting a more positive spin on the inevitability and brilliance of age.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">This turn-around by the beauty industry hasn’t landed out of thin air – it’s reflective of the way women over 40 now live life today. As a fit 42-year-old myself, the term ‘middle-aged’ feels like the ultimate insult. I don’t wear support knickers or sensible shoes with soft soles (apart from my Nike Fly-Knits or YSL trainers), and I don’t have a predictable over-40 easy-style haircut. I’m fitter than I’ve ever been in my life (and probably look better in a bikini for it) and I often wear leggings and trainers like my 11-year-old daughter does yet somehow never feel like mutton dressed as lamb. I don’t do coffee mornings, Tupperware parties or elasticated waistbands. Hell, I don’t even iron my sheets let alone my husband’s boxer shorts like my mother before me.</span></p>
<blockquote>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">The generation gap, it seems is closing, we forty-plus women look, feel and live differently than our forbearers. </span></p>
</blockquote>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">We wear jeans and trainers to work, spend as much time as our daughters on Instagram and shop with them in &amp;OtherStories. For the first time in history more women are having children in their forties than under 20 (I am one of them, I am currently pregnant) and a recent study of more than 500 women by marketing agency SuperHuman found that 80 percent felt that society’s assumptions about ‘middle-aged’ women does not represent how we actually live our lives.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">For too long it feels that the focus has been on Team Millennial, but this perception is shifting and the ‘The Perennials’ are claiming ground especially in the workplace. Statistics estimate that by 2020 up to a third of the UK workforce will be 50 plus and control 80 percent of the wealth. Alice Olins of The Step-up Club, a business that helps women find career success says, “</span><span class="s2">We’re living longer and staying younger than ever before, so it’s not surprising that barriers around age at work are coming down. Now that we're likely to work into our 70s, at 40 we’re not even halfway through our careers.”</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s2"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_magazine_ageless-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555576415" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Photo by Mario Sorrenti, Prada Fall '18, Isabelle Marant Fall '18. At 44, Amber Valetta continues to dominate the modelling world. </span></h5>
<p> Whilst we may be working longer, however, doesn’t mean we don’t wish for the crease-free skin, and grey-less hair we had in our 20s explains <a href="https://www.instagram.com/nadinebaggott/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nadine Baggott</a>, a 55-year-old journalist and YouTuber for beauty grown-ups, but “With age comes a wisdom and a sense of peace with your imperfections, and that is truly powerful.” We are a generation ultimately comfortable in our own skin, and that is coolness personified, surely.</p>
<p>_</p>
<p>For more insight on health and beauty in London, follow <a href="http://www.instagram.com/susannahtaylor_" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@susannahtaylor_</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
