<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/tagged/contributors.atom"/>
  <title>LUCAS HUGH - The Fit Magazine</title>
  <updated>2021-10-11T11:53:15+01:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LUCAS HUGH</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jenny-wordsworth</id>
    <published>2021-02-12T11:00:50+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:07:36+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jenny-wordsworth"/>
    <title>High Performer: Jenny Wordsworth</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Last February we interviewed endurance sports athlete <a href="http://jennydavis.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Jenny Davis/ Wordsworth website link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jenny Wordsworth</a> who had just completed a gruelling 700 mile solo expedition to the South Pole. Here we share our interview with the corporate lawyer turned professional athlete on what motivates her. </p>
<hr><meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong>You have taken part in some amazing challenges, what experiences led you to leave the world of corporate law to become an elite athlete?</strong> </p>
<p>I've been fortunate to have worked for some excellent firms as my career in corporate law progressed, they were always so supportive of my extra curricular activities of mountaineering, ultra running and skiing. I think it was also of great interest to our clients and they'd usually support my expeditions in the form of sponsorship. I started doing well in ultra  running races (so races of 35miles and over), I took part in a 5 day race through the Dasht-e-Lut desert in Iran and after winning the race returned home to the offer of a pro contract. My boss tells me he knew it was coming, and within weeks I'd signed the contract and resigned from my role as in-house legal counsel. I do still work as a freelance lawyer, especially on projects I find interesting as I found I really missed it.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/A7_08841_480x480.jpg?v=1613035992" alt="Jenny Wordsworth in Antarctica" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></strong></p>
<p><strong>You encountered challenges whilst on your trip, how did you mentally stay strong to be able to push through the physical challenges?</strong></p>
<p>Suffering from a painful open ulcer reperfusion injury on my leg known as 'Polar Thigh' with about 150 miles to go from the South Pole was one of the hardest thing I have ever done. Months later I am still not sure how I was able to keep that mental strength and push on through that level of pain. Until that point I had been on track to break the world speed record but after that leg injury simply reaching the Pole felt like the biggest achievement of my life. I did need two surgeries and a skin graft the week I returned to London, but I'll wear the scars with pride. </p>
<p> What really keeps me going in an expedition is my 'why' - why am I here at all and why am I even attempting to do this in the first place. If your 'why' is genuine and strong enough, you'll get through the tough times. That isn't to say it's easy and this expedition was one of the hardest things I've ever done.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>What advice would you give to those wanting to elevate their fitness routine and to those who are even considering taking on an extreme challenge? </strong></p>
<p>If you’re new to adventure it’s great to approach others with more experience and ask for help, just don’t forget that your unique background and experiences will bring something to the table that those experts won’t have thought of before. Don’t be so intimated by the experience of others that you forget or downplay your own ideas or approach. I mentor several women and it's the most enjoyable aspect of what I do - everyone is willing you on and only want to help you succeed, take advantage of that and get the help where you need it.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<blockquote>
<p><span>"What really keeps me going is my 'why' - If it's genuine and strong enough, you'll get through the tough times".</span><span> </span></p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>What keeps you going and entertained during your challenges? i.e any podcasts etc.</strong></p>
<p>I mostly train without any form of external stimulus, especially for an expedition like the one in Antarctica. This was recommended to me by my coaches and it's also a great way to develop your mental strength. Imagine if your AirPods or iPhone stopped working halfway through your challenge, race or expedition? Then what? I don't like to become reliant on stimulus like that, just in case it isn't then available to me during the event itself. I probably do 80% of my training sessions with no music or podcasts, just focusing on the task at hand and entering into a form of flow state. </p>
<p> For the 44 day expedition in Antarctica though, I did save up podcasts featuring people I find inspirational and so the real treat was being able to listen to them whilst there. My friends also surprised me with a full length recording of The Odyssey by Homer! That kept me going for the whole trip as I'd listen to a small section each day.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is next on your agenda? &amp; how do you decide on your challenges?</strong></p>
<p>I was due to be mountaineering in Nepal followed by a ten day mountain bike race through the mountains of Kyrgyzstan, those were both cancelled of course due to COVID-19. In the future I hope to complete an ocean row, precisely because I know absolutely nothing about ocean rowing and that's exactly what draws me to it. I also have a fear of the sea after a friend passed away at sea when I was younger, I'd like to face that fear and love the sea again. </p>
<p> For me the physical challenge is because I love finding out what my body is capable of, then the mental challenge is always where it gets most interesting and, importantly for me, it's an opportunity to visit parts of the planet I'd never normally set foot on.  </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TNF_High_Res_480x480.jpg?v=1613036138" alt="Jenny Wordsworth in Antartica " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><span></span><br><strong>How do you take time for yourself and recuperate from training?</strong> </p>
<p>Sleep! Rest days and enough sleep are a life priority for me, although it took me years to really learn and respect that. The more I look after my body, the more I get out of it. I often get more than 9 hours sleep a night and I couldn't go without it. </p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What do you look for in your workout gear?</strong></p>
<p>High quality and design. I live in workout gear, day in and day out. It needs to last and it needs to look good, Lucas Hugh has been my go-to for years now as the pieces are simply beautiful, the cut is like no other and I've been unable to destroy any of it which given my training is quite something. They are just the most beautiful pieces and I'm in love.</p>
<p><br><strong>Any recommendations of places to work-out or that you love to refuel/ eat in London?</strong></p>
<p>I still love a good Barry's Bootcamp class, I remember when they first opened in London there wasn't anything like them in town and I love popping by for a seriously hard workout. Otherwise I love any of the group classes at KX in Chelsea, they have a great restaurant there too.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/genius-design-transcends-time</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T16:23:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T16:31:36+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/genius-design-transcends-time"/>
    <title>PODCAST</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Anjhe Marcus, CO-CEO and Creative Director of Lucas Hugh, speaks to Andrea Alexa Smith about advanced technical fabric application and designing to enhance and envelop the female form.</p>
<p>Available on a variety of podcast apps &amp; online |<span> </span><a href="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1128056/5315833-anjhe-marcus-of-lucas-hugh-the-future-forward-visionary-behind-the-training-uniforms-for-the-hunger-games-catching-fire" target="_blank" title="Podcast Link to Genius Design Transcends Time, Anjhe Marcus of Lucas Hugh" rel="noopener noreferrer">Listen here</a></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Lucas_Hugh13_large.jpg?v=1599649064" alt="Lucas Hugh Genius Design Transcends Time Podcast" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-the-month-of-active-recovery</id>
    <published>2018-10-03T22:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:29:20+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-the-month-of-active-recovery"/>
    <title>Welcome to the Month of Active Recovery</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center;"><meta charset="utf-8"></div>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Editor's Letter</em></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-the-month-of-active-recovery">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/the-fit-guide-london/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">London Summer</a> – officially the best on record and for most, this has meant a whirlwind of non-stop travel, roof-top bars and lounging in the park. But all good things must come to an end and not surprisingly, October feels like the ‘transitional month.’ Not yet Winter but cool enough to don a coat and rejoice (perhaps over-enthusiastically) whenever the sun graces us with her ever-dwindling presence. But rather than accept my impending fate of binge-watching Netflix, I have challenged myself to embrace the ‘transition’.</p>
<p>Which is why, this month on The Fit it is all about<span> </span><em>active recovery</em>– a time to welcome a slower pace, yet still live in the moment and make the most of what this city has to offer. And let’s face it we have no excuses; with Frieze, London Literature Festival and Restaurant Month all falling in October there is plenty to enrich the mind and body- in a slow, steady and in-doors kind-of-way. </p>
<br>
<p><span>Carla Calder, Editor</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-out-of-the-office-month</id>
    <published>2018-08-01T01:09:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:29:14+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-out-of-the-office-month"/>
    <title>Welcome To Out Of The Office Month</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Editor’s Letter</em></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-out-of-the-office-month">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<p><img class="left-col" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thefit_lucashugh_holiday_edLetter-768x768.jpg?v=1552266729" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>The UK is in the middle of, weatherwise anyway, one of the sunniest summers on record and as a perennially rainy country, everyone is at once unsettled and ecstatic. Torn between climate change concern and the want to get out and enjoy the somehow endless sun we have added a further layer of anxiety to already anxious times. This month is OOO month on The Fit not just because it’s August and it seems just about everyone you email has theirs on, but also because we all need a holiday. Whether it’s long-haul, short-haul or no-haul make like the rest of them set your out of office on and leave your anxieties at the door. Just remember to refuse the plastic straw in your 3 PM mojito.<br></span><br><a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/fit-travel/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>Need some travel inspiration? From city breaks to mountain retreats, we recommend our favourite places for fit travel.<br></span></a><br><a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/the-holiday-workout/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>Keen to keep fit while you’re OOO? We’ve found three workouts you can do, anywhere, anytime.</span></a></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><br><span>Lucy Korn, Editor</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/madeleine-spencer</id>
    <published>2018-04-19T13:19:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:22:47+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/madeleine-spencer"/>
    <title>Madeleine Spencer</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Meet our April contributor, Beauty Editor, Madeleine Spencer.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/madeleine-spencer">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>WHAT DO YOU DO?</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>I’m a freelance journalist and broadcaster, focussing on beauty, health (both physical and mental), and travel. When I’m not writing or consulting for brands, I can mostly be found wielding a brush as a make-up artist or presenting videos for various platforms.</p>
<p>WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</p>
<p>I don’t have a simple answer to this question: my mum and dad come from Austria and Hungary respectively so school holidays were invariably spent in one or the other, and though I grew up in North London and spent some time at school in the Midlands, my parents have had a restaurant on Westbourne Grove for over 50 years now that we spend a lot of time at as a family. I live nearby so West London feels as good a home as any, but I think I, like many children of immigrants, have assigned emotions and memories to certain places without truly feeling like any of them are ‘home.’ For me, Salzburg and the lakes surrounding it resonate with me on an emotional level, while my way of living has been fostered by spending a lot of time in West London.<br>In short, whenever I am in one place, a part of my heart always yearns for another.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_madspencer_contributor-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555503903" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT STATE OF MIND?</p>
<p>Hopeful. I find spring invariably engenders a more positive mindset, and the idea of travelling to sunnier spots makes me feel more vibrant and energetic - even before the trip itself.</p>
<p>HOW DO YOU KEEP PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY FIT?</p>
<p>The two are inextricably entwined in my view. I walk my dog as often as possible in the park, and doing so helps me to reach a decent step count and to see the seasons, which I find helps my sense of well-being enormously. I like to stretch out and do a series of yoga poses in the morning which, again, has an impact on my mind, imbuing me with a sense of calm with which to start the day. When I am struggling with panic attacks or stress, as I do periodically, I go to see a psychiatrist. I strongly believe that there is only so much you can do alone on that side of things and that, just as you’d see a doctor if a bone in your body was broken, tending to mental health sometimes requires the intervention of a professional.</p>
<p>WHO ARE YOUR HEROES?</p>
<p>Kylie Minogue for her unfaltering grace and work ethic, Elvis for the sheer magic he brought to everything he did, and my Dad for his unassailably positive attitude.</p>
<p>WHAT DOES SUCCESS MEAN TO YOU?</p>
<p>It means feeling energised by what you’re doing at work and outside of it, and to be able to look back on the week and to feel like your contribution has been a good one, that perhaps you’ve entertained or made someone feel less alone, less isolated. I don’t think success can ever be enjoyed or achieved alone, but equally too much rubbernecking at what other people are doing and the comparison seems to me to be the antithesis of success.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/rosie-green-1</id>
    <published>2018-04-02T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:21:10+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/rosie-green-1"/>
    <title>Rosie Green</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Get to know our April contributor, Rosie Green.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/rosie-green-1">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT DO YOU DO?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">I’m a journalist, mainly writing about beauty, wellbeing and spas.  It’s not bad!</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">South Oxfordshire, with my husband, two children and assorted guinea pigs.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT STATE OF MIND?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Overloaded, but grateful.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">HOW DO YOU KEEP PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY FIT?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Running - either alone or with friends.<b>  </b>And TRX.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHO ARE YOUR HEROES?</span></p>
<p class="p1"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_rosiegreen-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555513901" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">NHS staff</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT DOES SUCCESS MEAN TO YOU?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Happiness.</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/samantha-freedman</id>
    <published>2018-03-11T16:45:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:20:31+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/samantha-freedman"/>
    <title>Samantha Freedman</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Get to know our March contributor, Beauty Editor, Samantha Freedman.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/samantha-freedman">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>WHAT DO YOU DO?</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span><span class="s1">I’m a beauty editor and expert, I’ve been in the industry for just over 10 years so it’s pretty safe to say I know my stuff when it comes to what works. </span></span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><span>Belsize Park, London- my flat is small, cosy and I wouldn’t swap it for anywhere else in the world- apart from the beach, of course. </span></span></p>
<p><span></span><span class="s1">WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT STATE OF MIND?</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span class="s1"><span>Happy, content and grateful.</span></span></p>
<p><span class="s1"><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/SAM_FREEDMAN_LUCASHUGH_large.jpg?v=1555515862" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></span></p>
<p><span class="s1">HOW DO YOU KEEP PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY FIT?</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span class="s1"><span>I keep physically fit by spinning, I love the release, the energy in the class and most of all the music. To keep mental fit I don't rely on apps, instead, I clean and declutter - it does my brain the world of good.</span></span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHO ARE YOUR HEROES?</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><span>My parents. I call them ten times a day. </span><i><span> </span></i></span></p>
<p><span class="s1">WHAT DOES SUCCESS MEAN TO YOU?</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span class="s1"><span>Feeling an amazing sense of achievement. Whether it is carrying all my shopping up the stairs (there are </span><i><span>a lot</span></i><span> of stairs), or writing a phenomenal piece that gets picked up and circulated around the world...</span></span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/vicky-ellison</id>
    <published>2018-03-07T16:15:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:20:42+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/vicky-ellison"/>
    <title>Vicky Ellison</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Get to know our monthly 'High Performers' columnist, Equinox's Vicky Ellison. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/vicky-ellison">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>WHAT DO YOU DO?</span></p>
<p><span>I’m the Marketing Director for Equinox in the UK, a columnist for Well To Do Global, and now, excitingly, Lucas Hugh.</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</span></p>
<p><span>London, a north London girl at heart but moved to the dark side (aka south of the river) and loving that too!</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT STATE OF MIND?</span></p>
<p>At the risk of sounding cheesy… grateful.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">HOW DO YOU KEEP PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY FIT?</span></p>
<p>I’m lucky to have a very patient and talented personal trainer and a fantastic Pilates coach at Equinox Kensington. I love to run outside when I can or take a yoga class. I used to be very unfit and overweight, but the enjoyment I find now in exercise has been pretty transformative. Starting a meditation practice last year has been a bit of a life changer; I use the app Calm every day. I’m also a huge fan of reading in the bath if I get time, and any opportunity to book in some pampering!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/VICKY_ELLISON_LUCASHUGH-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555514295" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHO ARE YOUR HEROES?</span></p>
<p>Again hoping not to sound like a cliché but, my mum! She teaches me the importance of being kind, grateful and to always do my best. Also Michelle Obama, Ellen DeGeneres - strong, driven women who lead by example; achieving so much with positivity, humility, grace and a smile.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT DOES SUCCESS MEAN TO YOU?</span></p>
<p>A sense of personal accomplishment, a feeling of being respected for what I do, while making time for the people that I love.</p>
<h3 class="p1"> </h3>
<h3 class="p4"> </h3>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/francesca-white</id>
    <published>2018-03-05T16:15:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:21:02+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/francesca-white"/>
    <title>Francesca White</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Get to know our March contributor, Tatler's Health and Beauty Director, Francesca White.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/francesca-white">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3 class="p1"><em><span class="s1"><b></b></span></em></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><span>WHAT DO YOU DO?</span></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">I am the Health &amp; Beauty Director for Tatler, where I write about everything from fitness to cosmetic surgery. No two days are the same - I’m so fortunate to do a job that continually inspires me. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><span>WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</span></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Marylebone - it's local and neighbourhood-y, but super-central. Brunch at La Fromagerie, coffee at Monocle, wandering around the Conran Shop and dinner at Chiltern Firehouse is the perfect weekend. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><span>WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT STATE OF MIND?</span></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Half planning, half dreaming. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">HOW DO YOU KEEP PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY FIT?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">I exercise 4-5 times per week; a mixture of resistance-based workouts for strengthening, and yoga, to stretch. And I read a lot - usually in the bath, with a coffee. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHO ARE YOUR HEROES?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">My mother, because she is unshakable and showed me the value of hard work. My grandmother, because she taught me that you can be whoever you want to be. </span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><span>WHAT DOES SUCCESS MEAN TO YOU?</span></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Excitement for the opportunities that each day brings.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-the-fit</id>
    <published>2018-02-27T09:36:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:19:31+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-the-fit"/>
    <title>Welcome to The Fit</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Lucas Hugh's online magazine for the life that surrounds you. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/welcome-to-the-fit">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">I am beyond excited to welcome you to the debut issue of The Fit, home of all things Lucas Hugh. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">The decision to create our own magazine was an easy one, we wanted to create a space where we could expand the Lucas Hugh world beyond the product. The Fit is an extension of our website but the aim is for it to feel like an autonomous platform, a place for interesting conversation, expert opinion and stylish advice. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_welcome_thefit-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555576497" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Updated weekly and written by a series of notable contributors, our articles are organized around four categories, Performance, Style, Culture and Self - all words that have meaning to the Lucas Hugh woman. For March, on the heels of International Women’s Day and with the global cultural conversation as it stands, women are at the center of each of our stories.</span><span class="s1"> </span>Today, columnist Vicky Ellison interviews inspiring artist, Kelly Anna for our monthly <a href="https://lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kelly-anna" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">High Performers</a> column, Francesca White reminds us that it’s ok to be <a href="https://lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-benefit-of-occasional-selfishness" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">occasionally selfish </a>and Susannah Taylor asks, <a href="https://lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/age-is-just-a-number" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">is age irrelevant in modern society?</a></p>
<p class="p1">I hope you enjoy The Fit, it was, after all, built with you in mind.</p>
<p class="p1"><img class="alignnone size-thumbnail wp-image-1961" src="https://www.lucashugh.com/wp-content/uploads/Screen-Shot-2018-03-09-at-11.11.42-150x76.png" alt="" width="150" height="76"></p>
<p class="p1">Anjhe Mules, Founder and Creative Director</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/susannah-taylor</id>
    <published>2017-02-22T15:40:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:21:16+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/susannah-taylor"/>
    <title>Susannah Taylor</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Get to know our March contributor, Beauty and Health Editor, Susannah Taylor.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/susannah-taylor">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><i></i></span></h3>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1">WHAT DO YOU DO?</span></p>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1">I’m a beauty and health editor, I put together publications (online and in print) on beauty and health, write articles and style shoots. I also creatively consult with brands creating content and visuals.  I have been doing <i>this</i> for about 20 years. I was the beauty and health editor at Glamour and then Vogue and then I started up <a href="http://getthegloss.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s2">getthegloss.com</span></a>.</span></p>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1">WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">North Oxfordshire in a house I love with my two children (nearly three children, I’m almost 9 months pregnant!), Bella 10, Oscar 9 and my lovely husband Chris.</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">WHAT IS YOUR CURRENT STATE OF MIND?</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">I’m waiting for a baby to arrive which is a strange time. Frantically trying to finish all my work and nesting like a crazy person before she makes an appearance. Generally, I feel quite on top of things though and happy with my career and what I’ve achieved….I started working from home more last year (I was commuting into London before) and it has changed my life.</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/SUSANNAH_TAYLOR_LUCASHUGH-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555512707" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">HOW DO YOU KEEP PHYSICALLY AND MENTALLY FIT?</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">Physically I am pretty active. When I’m not pregnant I do yoga, go to the gym and go to classes (spinning, boxing, swimming I like to mix it up else things get boring). Throughout pregnancy, I have exercised and gone to the gym weekly but I have really changed my routine to stay away from anything that gets my heart rate too high or leaves me gasping for breath. I’ve been doing a lot of yoga and strength exercises instead. I started getting properly fit through at about 37 which was a revelation for me.</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">To keep mentally fit I exercise physically! I find the best thing for staying sane and clearing my head and minimising worries is exercise - I love pushing myself out of my comfort zone. If I’m very stressed then I have this app called Calm which I listen to - it’s absolutely brilliant and has lots of meditations you tune in to whether you are stressed, anxious, can’t sleep etc. I also learnt to meditate properly with a brilliant woman called Jillian Lavender at The London Meditation centre who has taught me Vedic meditation where you say a mantra over and over again in your head (although currently, I have to admit I’ve fallen off the bandwagon) it’s the oldest form of meditation there is. </span>I try to minimise stress generally these days. Once upon a time, I thrived on it - now I try everything not to be stressed.</p>
<p class="p4">WHO ARE YOUR HEROES?</p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">I’m not inspired by the latest Instagram hit who has, say 100,000 followers or celebs that walk the red carpet wearing a £500,000 dress. I’m inspired by people who do great things in life, people that could be my best friends. One person I love is Bryony Gordon, a mental health campaigner, and marathon runner. She doesn’t fit a size 10 ideal or the usual fitness inspo but is doing amazing things to help change the conversation about mental health. One of my besties is Nicola Elliott and she is also an inspiration - she co-founded Neom and did it from scratch with no money in the bank and remains super down-to-earth. She’s brilliant, very real, a very clever spark and makes me laugh like no one on earth. Anyone fake is not my hero.</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">WHAT DOES SUCCESS MEAN TO YOU?</span></p>
<p class="p4"><span class="s1">Success means health and happiness. It’s not about the money - money doesn’t make anyone happy and I’ve seen it destroy people and I’ve seen it turn people into monsters.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
