<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/tagged/culture.atom"/>
  <title>LUCAS HUGH - The Fit Magazine</title>
  <updated>2021-10-11T11:53:15+01:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LUCAS HUGH</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/autumn-agenda</id>
    <published>2021-09-29T15:02:10+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:05:05+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/autumn-agenda"/>
    <title>AUTUMN AGENDA</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<br>
<p><b>The Reformer RX</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Get ready, set, RX with the new ultimate at home reformer pilates workout. The </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">ergonomic design from Reformer RX uses unique technology to track your work rate and guide your progress, elevating your performance through real time biometric feedback for the optimum workout. The smart reformer is finished with touches of polished steel and flawless elegance getting the best out of you while you train. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">From £4995,<a href="reformrx.com"> reformrx.com</a></span></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Reform_RX_480x480.jpg?v=1632923081" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Frieze Fair</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">The contemporary art fair is coming to London this October. Situated in Regent’s Park, the fair will host emerging artists to industry names. Featuring internationally renowned galleries from around the globe alongside new curated sections, special artist commissions and leading voices from the industry hosting talks. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Tickets from £26, 13th - 17th October 2021, <a href="https://www.frieze.com/">frieze.com</a></span></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Frieze_Art_Fair_London_480x480.jpg?v=1632923134" alt=""><br>
<p><b>London Fashion Week</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Going ahead this September 2021, </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">London Fashion Week is the first of the leading four global fashion weeks to fully embrace digital media into its twice yearly showcase, in addition to holding physical events. All designers will be showcasing their latest collections in a newly dedicated digital space as Somerset House where a global audience will be able to tune in to view the collections live. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">16th - 21st September, <a href="https://londonfashionweek.co.uk/schedule">londonfashionweek.co.uk/digitalschedule</a></span></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screenshot_2021-09-29_at_14.58.47_480x480.png?v=1632923968" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Beaverbrook Townhouse</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">From their enchanting estate in Surrey, Beaverbrook transports its quintessential British charm to their new boutique hotel situated on stylish Sloane Street, London overlooking the leafy-green Cadogan Gardens.. The two beautifully restored Georgian townhouses are home to a Japanese restaurant, vibrant bar and 14 suites. Expect impeccable designed rooms by Nicola Harding that pay homage to London’s magnificent historic theatres, brimming with carefully curated posters, illustrations, vintage photography, and bespoke written histories, each theatre’s fascinating story is seamlessly regaled in finely crafted words and pictures.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.beaverbrooktownhouse.co.uk/"><span style="font-weight: 300;">beaverbrooktownhouse.co.uk</span></a></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Beaverbrook_Town_House_480x480.jpg?v=1632923105" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Ham Yard Hotel Yoga</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">In the midst of Soho, London, moments away from Mayfair, the Ham Yard Hotel is hosting a series of yoga sessions on the hotel's Roof Terrace in partnership with Third Space. Set amongst olive trees and meadows of wild flowers with views over the rooftops of Soho, experience a Hatha Yoga class under the expert guidance of one of Third Space's instructors. Bringing balance, strength and a sense of wellbeing the 45-minute sessions will guide you through a series of postures and conscious breathing in combination with mental focus to develop awareness, strength, flexibility and relaxation. Yoga sessions include a healthy brunch to follow the class from avocado and poached eggs on rye to granola, yoghurt and berries or coconut chia seed pots with mango.</span></p>
<br>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">£39 including 45-minute yoga session and brunch. Available Saturday 18th September, 9.15am.  </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.firmdalehotels.com/"><span style="font-weight: 300;">firmdalehotels.com</span></a></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Tech_Knit_Leggings_Black_2204_7f25426d-7202-4191-ba72-fb041fc2f9f0_480x480.jpg?v=1584451120" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Dr. Barbara Sturm’s London Boutique and Spa</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Located in Mayfair, London, Dr. Barbara Sturm’s new London flagship will serve as a place of skincare discovery and advanced-scientific innovations. Offering signature facials where you can enjoy the full suite of Dr. Sturm’s most sought-after facials, alongside new exclusive treatments available for London customers. Additionally, new anti-aging body treatments are available at the spa. </span></p>
<p><a href="https://en.drsturm.com/"><span style="font-weight: 300;">drsturm.com</span></a></p>
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Dr_Barbara_Sturm_Spa_Townhouse_Mayfair_480x480.jpg?v=1632923118" alt=""><br>
<p><b>Nobu Pilates</b></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Located in the heart of Marylebone,</span><span style="font-weight: 300;"> Nobu Wellness &amp; Fitness is home to the World’s first Nobu Pilates Reformer studio. Headed up by the renowned Marsha Lindsay, Nobu Pilates is an exciting new way to experience the benefits of Pilates with specialised classes for glutes, abs and cardio. Catering for beginners to advanced levels, using state of the art equipment including; Pilates Reformers, Cadillac, Stability Chairs and Barrels. </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">A hybrid of classical Pilates and high-intensity training, Nobu Pilates offers three signature classes: </span><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">Power</span></i><span style="font-weight: 300;">, </span><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">Precision</span></i><span style="font-weight: 300;"> and </span><i><span style="font-weight: 300;">Pure</span></i><span style="font-weight: 300;"> – each combining the core components of traditional Pilates with a fresh and focused flow. Classes of ten or individual sessions are available.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;">Classes from £35, <a href="https://london-portman.nobuhotels.com/wellness-fitness/">nobuhotels.com</a>, available at </span><span style="font-weight: 300;">Nobu Hotel Portman Square, </span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/22+Portman+Square,+London+W1H+7BG/@51.5160933,-0.15913,18.1z/data=!4m5!3m4!1s0x48761acca2c6f72d:0xb06a22c4fa213e6d!8m2!3d51.5161336!4d-0.1579796"><span style="font-weight: 300;">22 Portman Square, London W1H 7BG</span></a></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 300;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Nobu_Hotel_London_Launch_Pilates_480x480.jpg?v=1632923177" alt=""></span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-agenda</id>
    <published>2021-03-26T10:32:05+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:06:58+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-agenda"/>
    <title>Spring Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<blockquote>
<p>"The beautiful spring came, and when nature resumes her loveliness, the human soul is apt to revive also." - Harriet Ann Jacobs</p>
</blockquote>
<p>EXPLORE SOMEWHERE NEW</p>
<p>Apps such as Komoot allow you to find inspiring walks and hikes from the ones on your doorstep to further afield. If you'd rather plan your own adventure the app can make it easier to navigate from your chosen A to B and prepare you for what to expect. </p>
<p>Start planning on <a href="https://www.komoot.com/" target="_blank" title="Komoot Start planning an adventure" rel="noopener noreferrer">Komoot.</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/photo-1586911264581-b2c2155d2429_480x480.jpg?v=1616692641" alt="Spring Day" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>THE BRILLIANCE OF LIFE</p>
<p>We are looking forward to taking a step inside one of Yayoi Kusama's famous infinity rooms on display at the Tate Modern. The Infinity Mirrored Room 'Filled with the Brilliance of Life' is one of Kusama's largest installation to date and is accompanied with a small presentation as well as a second infinity<span> </span>room. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Plan your visit to the</span><span> </span><a href="https://www.tate.org.uk/whats-on/tate-modern/exhibition/yayoi-kusama-infinity-mirror-rooms" target="_blank" title="Tate Modern Yayoi Kusama Infinity rooms" rel="noopener noreferrer">Tate Modern</a> ahead of it's reopening<span>.</span></p>
<p> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/T15206_570381_10_480x480.jpg?v=1616689376" alt="Tate Modern Infinity Room" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>ON PURPOSE BY JAY SHETTY</p>
<p>Jay Shetty's purpose is 'to make wisdom go viral' the former monk's podcast features thoughtful and uplifting talks with a range of people from Jennifer Lopez to monk and mentor Gauranga Das. Episodes cover everything from love and relationships to finding peace and purpose.</p>
<p>Available on a variety of<span> </span><a href="https://jayshetty.me/podcast/" target="_blank" title="Jay Shetty Podcast" rel="noopener noreferrer">podcast platforms</a>.</p>
<p> </p>
<p>EGGSTRAVAGANT CHOCOLATE</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Chocolate stimulates the production of endorphins in our brain and is a great way to give yourself a little happiness boost. </span>Treat yourself to a Vegan Milk Chocolate Egg from Rococo Chocolates. The extra thick and delicious eggs are sustainably sourced and hand crafted in London. </p>
<p>Vegan Easter Egg from <a href="https://www.rococochocolates.com/products/vegan-milk-chocolate-egg/" target="_blank" title="Rococo Chocolate Vegan Easter Egg" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rococo Chocolates</a>. </p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/VeganMilcEgg_2-scaled_480x480.jpg?v=1616689491" alt="Vegan Milk Chocolate Easter Egg Rococo Chocolates" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-future-of-wellness-2021</id>
    <published>2021-01-15T12:44:55+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:07:52+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-future-of-wellness-2021"/>
    <title>New for 2021</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>2020 has been an interesting year and many of us have had to find new ways to adapt and evolve in one way or another. At Lucas Hugh we're all about looking to the future, here's what we have got into for 2021. </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/COBALT_BLUE_AXIS_FRONT_WFH_l_480x480.jpg?v=1610119227" alt="Lucas Hugh Work Out From Home" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW ONLINE CLASSES</p>
<p>We are kick starting our year with Heartcore who offer a great range of classes from wake up and wind down to their signature Heartcore class designed to build strength and help you flow through your day. Their unlimited live-stream and on-demand pass has something to suit all schedules, with a new online platform coming soon. </p>
<p>Monthly access £55 a month | <a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" title="Link to Heartcore website">Weare</a><a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" target="_blank" title="Link to Heartcore website" rel="noopener noreferrer">heartcore.com</a><a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" title="Link to Heartcore website"></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>JANUARY CLEANSE</p>
<p>Rebooting our systems after an indulgent holiday season with a Radiance Juice Cleanse. They offer a range of cleanse options delivered to your door with guidance and support pre and post cleanse. </p>
<p>Winter Cleanse from £65 | <a href="https://radiancecleanse.com/programmes/classic-cleanses/" target="_blank" title="Radiance Cleanse website" rel="noopener noreferrer">Radiancecleanse.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/a59e6e815efbf14f069b58a78225e333_3fd50abe-4f83-4df6-b6f8-93cc4d6dcd48_480x480.jpg?v=1610118118" alt="Eat Green" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW GREAT COOKBOOK</p>
<p>With more time spent in our home offices a great way to reconnect with family and loved ones at the end of the day is over a delicious healthy meal. Eat Green by Melissa Hemsley contains a variety of seasonal, sustainable flexitarian recipes to suit the whole family. </p>
<p>Eat Green by Melissa Hemsley | <a href="https://melissahemsley.com/eatgreen/" target="_blank" title="Eat Green Link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Melissahemsley.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW PODCAST</p>
<p>Our favourite investigative journalist took the podcast world by storm last year with Grounded. Now back for a second season we can expect to listen to Louis Theroux speak to high-profile people from a variety of backgrounds. We're enjoying his recent interview with Sia. </p>
<p>Listen now | <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p08ybsww" target="_blank" title="BBC Radio 4 Louis Theroux Grounded ep12. Sia" rel="noopener noreferrer">Grounded with Louis Theroux 12. Sia</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/About-Us-Homepage_copy_480x480.jpg?v=1610550508" alt="Black Tomato Villa" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CURATED ESCAPES</p>
<p>With so many travel restrictions last year many will be looking to find the perfect get away this year. Look no further than Black Tomato who are award winning creators of unique and tailored travel experiences and have a team of experts on hand to create your very own 'bubble' get away. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Jetty, Joali Maldives</span> | <a href="https://www.blacktomato.com/" target="_blank" title="Black Tomato" rel="noopener noreferrer">Blacktomato.com</a></p>
<p>   </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LH-Sustainability-2600x1733-1_480x480.jpg?v=1607096722" alt="Lucas Hugh Sustainability Page Image" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW LUCAS HUGH</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>We are driven to advance the future of activewear, and that means protecting our planet and making sustainable choices for our future world. Since launching in 2010, we have sourced premium Italian fabrics to ensure designs of the highest quality that last, </span>as well as producing in limited quantities to reduce excess. We select sustainable or recycled materials where possible, and from 2021 we plan to increase our use of these materials across all of our collections, with a focus on recycled yarns. As of 2020 all of our Technical Knit will be made with Q’NOVA recycled yarns – an environmentally-sustainable nylon fibre. </p>
<p>New collection launching soon. Follow us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lucashugh/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Instagram" rel="noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a> and sign up to our newsletter for exclusive access to the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/collections/new-in" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh New in page" rel="noopener noreferrer">latest drops</a>.</p>
<p>Treat yourself to some new Lucas Hugh | <a href="lucashugh.com/new-in">Lucashugh.com</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/august-art</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T16:30:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T16:30:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/august-art"/>
    <title>AUTUMN ART</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Autumn is upon us. Here's our round up of the best art exhibitions in the UK, as well as a new online class recommendation to boost your own creativity.</p>
<p>ANISH KAPOOR AT HOUGHTON HALL</p>
<p>One of the most influential sculptors still working today and well known for his adventurous take on modern sculpture. Featuring 24 sculpture and numerous other works by the artist, this exhibition is set across the beautiful grounds and within the house itself.</p>
<p>From now until 1st November, Houghton Hall, Norfolk, PE31 6TY | <a href="https://www.houghtonhall.com/art-and-exhibitions/anish-kapoor-at-houghton-hall/" target="_blank" title="Link to Anish Kapoor at Houghton Hall exhibition tickets." rel="noopener noreferrer">houghtonhall.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/03-Anish-Kapoor_large.jpg?v=1599651738" alt="Anish Kapoor Exhibition" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>ANDY WARHOL AT THE TATE MODERN</p>
<p>Iconic and instantly recognisable the Tate Modern has extended its retrospective Warhol exhibition till mid November. The exhibition features iconic pop works such as Marilyn Monroe and Campbell's soup cans as well as works never before seen in the UK. Alternatively, the Tate has also published online an exhibition guide for you to enjoy from the comfort of your home. </p>
<p>From now until 15th November, Tate Modern, Bankside, London, SE1 9TG | <a href="https://www.tate.org.uk/whats-on/tate-modern/exhibition/andy-warhol?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIi53Hifrb6wIVWeJ3Ch1YewlBEAAYASAAEgKxvPD_BwE" title="Andy Warhol at the Tate Modern">tate.org.uk</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ANDY_WARHOLE_large.jpg?v=1599652363" alt="Andy Warhol Exhibition image, Tate Modern. " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>BREATH IS INVISIBLE </p>
<p>A public art project in Notting Hill acknowledging the ability of art to say things we cannot express with words, addressing issues of inequality and injustice. The third instalment, opening on the 15th September, is featuring works from photographer and artist Joy Gregory, who will be exploring the narrative and origins of plants and their relationships with humans and ecology. </p>
<p>From now until 16th October, 236 Westbourne Grove, London, W11 2RH | <a href="https://breathisinvisible.com/" target="_blank" title="Breath is Invisible website" rel="noopener noreferrer">breathisinvisable.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>FEELING INSPIRED?</p>
<p>There is said to be a link between creativity and exercise. We recommend trying out Heartcore's newest online class 'The Heartcore Class' hosted by founder Jess Schuring. It's a great way to get your body moving, build your inner strength and get your creative thinking flowing. </p>
<p>Various dates and times available to book online | <a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Heartcore website" rel="noopener noreferrer">heartcore.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Pilates-Stuido-in-Chelsea-Heartcore_large.jpg?v=1599658005" alt="Heartcore Studio Class" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/time-to-explore</id>
    <published>2020-06-26T10:46:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-06-26T10:46:05+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/time-to-explore"/>
    <title>TIME TO EXPLORE</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>With lock down easing it's a perfect time to explore, rediscover your local area or take that day trip. Here's our </span><span>recommendations...</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/time-to-explore">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Whilst the last couple of month have been difficult, there is light at the tunnel. With lock down easing it's a perfect time to explore, rediscover your local area or take that day trip. Here's our </span>recommendations...</p>
<p>LONDON</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>North - </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/estersn16/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Esters</a><span> offers a click and collect service on a range of baked goods. Perfect for picking up some lunch or a sweet treat. </span><span>Esters, </span><a href="https://www.google.co.uk/maps/place/Esters/@51.560102,-0.0802557,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m2!3m1!1s0x48761c63b6591db3:0x718f5037fc079036" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">55 Kynaston Road, N16 0EB</a><br><br><span>West - The newly opened </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/supermarketofdreams/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Supermarket of Dreams</a><span> offers a range of artisan produce and collaborates with a range of top chefs such as Ottolenghi and the team at Kricket. Supermarket of Dreams, </span><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/126+Holland+Park+Ave,+Notting+Hill,+London+W11+4UE/@51.5065924,-0.2106377,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x48760fe653026fb7:0xa7e393c997ad5aa7!8m2!3d51.5065924!4d-0.208449" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">126 Holland Park Ave, W11 4UE</a><br><br><span>South-East - </span><a href="https://26grains.com/restaurant/XNKj5RAAAM9xcmw0" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Stoney Street</a><span> by 26 Grains prides itself on sourcing fresh top quality food prepared for you to takeaway. Stoney Street, </span><a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/2+Stoney+St,+London+SE1+9AA/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x4876035778116445:0xf671147cb031227?sa=X&amp;ved=2ahUKEwic49ep55rqAhVgTRUIHR0VBQ0Q8gEwAHoECAsQAQ" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">2-3 Stoney Street, SE1 9AA</a></p>
<p><span> </span></p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ARTICLE_IMAGE_LAYOUT.22_large.jpg?v=1593163973" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Model Wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/halo-track-pants-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, Halo Track Pants," rel="noopener noreferrer">Halo Track pant</a>s.</p>
<p><span>STAYCATION</span></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>The Cotswolds - <a href="https://www.broadwaydeli.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Broadway Deli</a> in the centre of the Cotswolds is offering deliveries from their shop and other things from the village. Broadway Deli, <a href="https://www.google.com/maps?ll=52.035833,-1.861055&amp;z=15&amp;t=m&amp;hl=en-GB&amp;gl=GB&amp;mapclient=embed&amp;cid=6882172791820397977" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">29 High Street WR12 7DP</a><br><br>Cornwall - Situated right on the beach <a href="http://www.gyllybeach.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gylly Beach Cafe</a> is the perfect place to grab a coffee and take a stroll. Gylly Beach Cafe, <a href="http://www.gyllybeach.com/contact/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cliff Road, Falmouth, TR11 4PA</a><br><br>Peak District - From the end of June <a href="https://www.instagram.com/riverside_kitchen_bakewell/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Riverside Kitchen</a> are offering a click &amp; collect service on a range of tasty goods. Riverside Kitchen, opening soon in Bakewell, Peak District.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ARTICLE_IMAGE_LAYOUT.2_large.jpg?v=1593164069" alt="Lucas Hugh, Performance V2 Leggings" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Model wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/performance-v2-leggings-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, Performance V2 Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">Performance V2 Leggings</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home</id>
    <published>2020-04-07T11:26:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-07T11:26:10+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home"/>
    <title>Workout at Home</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Lucas Hugh share the home workout's they are tuning into.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>RELAX YOUR MIND</p>
<p>Re:Mind Studio is living streaming a range of their classes daily. A great way to calm the mind. View the timetable<span> </span><a href="https://remindstudio.com/timetable#/schedule/site/1" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Re:Mind Studio" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<p>£11 per session |<span> </span><a href="https://remindstudio.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, home workouts, remind studio" rel="noopener noreferrer">Re:mind studio</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/REMIND_STUDIO_b4d3d934-410c-45e0-8dff-9e9de60196d2_large.jpg?v=1585915157" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Re:Mind Studio " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>IF YOU LIKE TO SWITCH UP YOUR CLASSES</p>
<p>Heartcore is offering up everything from Yin Yoga to HIIT, so matter what your feeling there is guaranteed to be a class to suit you. </p>
<p>Live Stream passes available from £5 | <a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Heartcore" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heartcore </a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-04-03_at_15.00.06_large.png?v=1585922631" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Heartcore" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>PERSONAL TRAINING</p>
<p>If personal training is your preference take advantage of Twenty Two Training's virtual consultation and training sessions, tailored to you. </p>
<p>A variety of block options available from £40 per session | <a href="https://twentytwotraining.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit magazine, Twenty Two Training, Home Workouts" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twenty Two Training</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/maxresdefault_large.jpg?v=1585920852" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home workouts, Twenty Two Training" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>EQUIPMENT AT THE READY</p>
<p>If you have a set of dumbbells (or even just bottles of water), a pilates ring, exercise band and resistant bands then you're ready to take on Epoch's <span>Online </span>Dynamic Mat Pilates Class. </p>
<p>Classes daily from £10 | <a href="https://epochfitness.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Epoch Fitness" rel="noopener noreferrer">Epoch Fitness</a></p>
<p>THE STREAMING EXPERTS</p>
<p>Liz &amp; Clary from Hilliard Studio Method are no strangers to online classes and their online streaming service boasts over 3,000 minutes of video. Watch anytime, anywhere; perfect if you require a little more flexibility in your daily routine.</p>
<p>Subscribe from $20.38/ per month | <a href="https://stream.hilliardstudiomethod.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit magazine, Home workouts, Hilliard Studio Method" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hilliard Studio Method</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/hilliard2-770x513_large.jpg?v=1585921715" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Work out, Hilliard Studio Method" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted</id>
    <published>2020-03-23T10:17:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-03-23T10:22:37+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted"/>
    <title>STAYING LIFTED</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>The Lucas Hugh team shares a round up of how they are keeping spirits lifted this month.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Some online resources for keeping spirits lifted this month from our team at Lucas Hugh. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>LEARN: HIGHBROW</p>
<p>At Highbrow you can find dozens of topics<span> </span>to learn about such as personal growth, history and coding. Learning comes in the format of a short daily email, over the course of 10 days. </p>
<p>Offer a free 30-day trial or sign up from $10 a month |<span> </span><a href="https://gohighbrow.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The fit, blog, Highbrow, learning" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gohighbrow.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>LISTEN: THE TONY ROBBINS PODCAST</p>
<p>Tony interviews some of the most successful people in the world, sharing their individual insights into what it means to be successful. We recommend 'Start small, think big, scale quickly'<em> </em>with SPANX founder Sara Blakely. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.tonyrobbins.com/podcasts/start-small-think-big-scale-quickly/" target="_blank" title="Sara Blakely, Tony Robbins, Spanx, lucas hugh, the fit, fit magazine" rel="noopener noreferrer">Listen here in conversation with Sara Blakely</a> | <a href="https://www.tonyrobbins.com/podcasts/" target="_blank" title="Tony Robbins, Podcast, Lucas Hugh," rel="noopener noreferrer">Tonyrobbins.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/FEATUREDQUOTE-1200X628-copy-550x288_large.jpg?v=1584958298" alt="Tony Robbins, Sara Blakely, Spanx founder, Podcast, Lucas Hugh The Fit Magazine"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>FOOD: GREEN KITCHEN STORIES</p>
<p>A vegetarian focused food blog with a vast range of nourishing and delicious looking recipes to choose from.  </p>
<p><a href="https://greenkitchenstories.com/" target="_blank" title="Food, blog, Lucas Hugh, Health, Wellness, Green Kitchen Stories" rel="noopener noreferrer">Greenkitchenstories.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Cauliflower_pasta_pesto_1-800x533-1_large.jpg?v=1584449750" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>HEALTH: CONTENT BEAUTY &amp; WELLBEING</p>
<p>This specially curated department store prides its self on finding the best natural, organic, sustainable products to enhance health &amp; wellbeing. Their website clearly talks through all certifications to help demystify the the wellness world. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.contentbeautywellbeing.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Content, Content beauty &amp; wellbeing, Health, wellbeing, " rel="noopener noreferrer">Contentbeautywellbeing.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-03-17_at_12.43.31_large.png?v=1584450286" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>EXERCISE: HEARTCORE</p>
<p>Workout Studio's may have had to temporarily close their doors however you can still enjoy your favourite studio's work out's from the comfort of your home. We are keeping an eye-out on Instagram for great tips from the team at Heartcore. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Heartcore, Workout, health, wellness, fitness" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heartcore.co.uk</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Tech_Knit_Leggings_Black_2204_large.jpg?v=1584451003" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Above Lauren is pictured wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-sports-bra-white" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit Sports Bra" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-7-8-leggings-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit 7/8 Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit 7/8 Leggings</a>. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-spring-agenda</id>
    <published>2020-02-28T11:41:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-02-28T11:50:42+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-spring-agenda"/>
    <title>YOUR SPRING AGENDA</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Jump into spring with this round up from the Lucas Hugh team.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-spring-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>VISIT: CARS: ACCELERATING THE MODERN WORLD</p>
<p>We often look to concept car design for inspiration at Lucas Hugh. Till April the V&amp;A will guide you through the history of the car and how it has shaped the modern world.</p>
<p>From now till 19<span style="font-size: 12.5px;">th </span>April 2020, V&amp;A Museum, Cromwell Road, London, SW7 2RL | <a href="https://www.vam.ac.uk/exhibitions/cars">www.vam.ac.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>EAT: MADERA AT TREE HOUSE LONDON</p>
<p>Experience experiential dining and elevated Mexican cuisine in the heart of London. Madera boasts organically sourced food and a range of gluten-free, vegan and vegetarian options served across breakfast, lunch, dinner and weekend brunch.</p>
<p>Madera At Treehouse London, 14-15 Langham Place, London, W1B 2QS |<span> </span><a href="https://www.maderalondon.com/">maderalondon.com</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/JLau_MaderaMadera29239_large.jpg?v=1582800827" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p>WATCH: THE GOOP LAB</p>
<p>Gwyneth Paltrow takes on the role of lead guinea pig in these 30-minute Netflix episodes where topics from diet, to energy healing and psychedelics are investigated and questioned by the team behind the ever intriguing Goop world.</p>
<p>Available to watch on Netflix now | <a href="https://goop.com/the-goop-lab-netflix/" target="_blank" title="goop, netflix, wellness, goop lab, watch, spring" rel="noopener noreferrer">Goop.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-02-26_at_16.50.21_large.png?v=1582801463" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p>WORKOUT: TWENTYTWO TRAINING</p>
<p>Top celebrity trainer Dalton Wong and his team at Twentytwo Training offer a private workout space in west London. Dalton's key training method incorporates the use of gliders and mini bands, simple, yet effective.</p>
<p> Twentytwo Training, 22b Elvaston Mews, Kensington, London, SW7 5HZ | <a href="https://twentytwotraining.com/" target="_blank" title="twentytwo training, game of thrones, dalton wong, lucas hugh" rel="noopener noreferrer">twentytwotraining.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/AnjheDalton_28_copy_2_large.jpg?v=1582808782" alt=""></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Above Dalton Wong and Anjhe Marcus, Lucas Hugh's Co-CEO and Creative Director. Anjhe is wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-sleeveless-t-shirt-maroon" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit Sleeveless T-shirt</a> in Maroon and the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/torque-leggings-garnet" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Torque Leggings</a> in Garnet. </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-ski</id>
    <published>2020-02-28T11:40:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-02-28T11:40:19+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-ski"/>
    <title>SPRING SKI</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[The Lucas Hugh teams round up of the best Ski destinations with the finest added extras.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/spring-ski">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Our round up of ski destinations with the finest added extras... </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TSCHUGGEN_SWITZERLAND_2_large.png?v=1582802194" style="float: none;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TSCHUGGEN_SWITZERLAND_medium.jpeg?v=1582802223" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><strong>SPA HOTEL: TSCHUGGEN GRAND HOTEL, SWITZLERLAND</strong></p>
<p>After you have taken in the breath-taking sail inspired architecture of the Tschuggen Bergoase Spa, you could find yourself relaxing in the mountain sauna, in the rock grotto or in an indulging in a private spa treatment. If skiing has taken its toll be sure to get the Skier massage, one of the spas signature treatments, which consists of a mountain pine bath followed by a relaxing yet rejuvenating leg massage.</p>
<p><a href="https://tschuggen.ch/en/spa" target="_blank" title="spa, ski, the fit, lucas hugh, switzerland" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Tschuggen Bergoase Spa</a> at the <a href="https://tschuggen.ch/en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Tschuggen Grand Hotel, Tschuggentorweg 1, CH-7050 Arosa, Switzerland</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/der_seehof_skiliciou_04545728030c1c21513617835_medium.jpg?v=1582802288" alt=""> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/der_seehof_terrasse_0045728030c1c21513617711_large.jpg?v=1582804200" alt=""></p>
<p>GASTRO HOTEL: DER SEEHOF, AUSTRIA </p>
<p>Considered to hold one of the best restaurants in Austria. Head chef and co-owner Sepp Schellhorn creates regional, responsibly sourced, delicious food for restaurant HECHT! Enjoy breakfast during the first rays of sun and come down from the mountains to indulge in fresh food after a day on the slopes. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.derseehof.at/en/restaurant-cuisine-goldegg.html" target="_blank" title="foodie, gastro, lucas hugh, ski, skiing, Austria" rel="noopener noreferrer">HECHT! Restaurant</a> at the <a href="https://www.derseehof.at/en/start.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Der Seehof hotel, Hofmark 8, 5622 Goldegg Am See, Austria</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Deplar_12-slide_large.jpg?v=1582804261" alt=""> <strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/667_1_medium.jpg?v=1582804280" alt=""></strong></p>
<p>PURE LUXURY: DEPLAR FARM, ICELAND</p>
<p>With floor-to-ceiling windows and surrounded by nature, Deplar Farm consists of 13 en-suite bedrooms, two helipads, geothermal pools, and a ‘gear room’ stocked with all the sporting gear you would need, plus much more. You can hire just a room or go all out and rent the whole converted sheep farm. With the two helipads on site this is the perfect place for the more adventurous skier with regular heli-skiing available, otherwise sit back and enjoy the tranquillity of the farm.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.mrandmrssmith.com/luxury-hotels/deplar-farm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Deplar Farm, Deplar 570, Fljot, skagafjörôur, Iceland</a></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/guide-to-the-new-decade</id>
    <published>2019-12-20T10:52:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-12-20T10:52:33+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/guide-to-the-new-decade"/>
    <title>Guide to Wellness in 2020</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Lucas Hugh guide to Wellness in 2020.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/guide-to-the-new-decade">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>2020. A new decade. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>The future is about slowing down, optimising the self through restorative self-care and working towards a better future. </span></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Lucas Hugh Kubrick One Piece" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Kubric_Onepiece_326_copy_large.jpg?v=1574869132" style="float: none;"></p>
<p>LEARN: DEVELOPING A SELF PRACTICE </p>
<p>Stretch London has a workshop that promises you you'll walk away having the confidence to roll out your Yoga Mat and flow through your own practice at home or wherever your 2020 adventures take you. </p>
<p>Jan 25th, Book online | Stretch, Broadway Market, 6B Ada Street, London, E8 4QU | <a href="https://stretch-london.com/workshops?mobile=false&amp;options%5Bids%5D=4416&amp;options%5Bsite_id%5D=26803&amp;version=0" title="Stretch, London, Yoga, Workshop, 2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">stretch-london.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Panasonic Shot" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/SHOT-angle_hi-6_large.jpg?v=1574866297" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>ADVANCED TAILORING: PANASONIC SHOT DEVICE</p>
<p>Panasonic's Balance of Being collection consists of six devices that hint at the future of wellness tech. The Shot device is designed to conduct a skin analysis &amp; creates a bespoke smoothie from fresh frozen fruit &amp; vegetables based on the result to improve a person's inner &amp; outer beauty. We are a little skeptical but intrigued. </p>
<p>Balance of Being | <a href="https://panasonic.net/design/works/ifa2019/" target="_blank" title="Panasonic, 2020, future, Balance of being" rel="noopener noreferrer">panasonic.net</a></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Stretch Lab" src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2019-11-27_at_11.19.14_large.png?v=1574866246" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><br>RESTORE: IN A STRETCHING CLASS</p>
<p>HIIT Classes are great for achieving our fitness goals but how we recover is just as important. ReCOVER &amp; Stretch Lab in the US &amp; UK offer assisted stretching classes to help your body recover and get you ready to go again in the new year. </p>
<p>360 7th Avenue, 4th Floor, NY 10001 |<span> </span><a href="https://www.recover.nyc/" title="Stretch, ReCover, 2020" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Recover.nyc</a></p>
<p>18 Wells Street, London, W1T 3PG |<span> </span><a href="https://www.stretch-lab.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="2020, Stretch Lab" rel="noopener noreferrer">stretch-lab.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="FF 91, Faraday Future" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ff-91-gallery21_large.jpg?v=1574866347" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CHOOSE BETTER: FF 91</p>
<p>Reimagining transport Faraday Future have developed the FF 91 car which is environmentally &amp; sustainably forward thinking without compromising on comfort or style. We are starting to make small steps for a better world. </p>
<p>Available to reserve | <a href="https://www.ff.com/us/ff-91/" target="_blank" title="ff, 2020, sustainable, Faraday Future, car" rel="noopener noreferrer">ff.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Aman, Resort, Wellness" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thismintymoment_dsc08605_b_high_res_12611_1_large.jpg?v=1574866404" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>DISCOVER: Aman Resorts</p>
<p>Take anything from 3-14 days on an Aman Wellness Retreat where immersive programs are designed to transform your body and mind. Expect expert guidance and uniquely tailored programs across their different resorts around the world. Whether it's stress management, detoxing, sport rehab or even looking for spiritual connection Aman will help you embark on your journey.</p>
<p>Various Locations | <a href="https://www.aman.com/wellness" target="_blank" title="aman, wellness, 2020, retreat" rel="noopener noreferrer">aman.com</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-winter-agenda</id>
    <published>2019-11-20T12:49:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-06T12:10:50+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-winter-agenda"/>
    <title>Your Winter Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Our guide of things to do this Winter.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-winter-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>LISTEN: INTELLIGENCE SQUARED PODCAST</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>For thought provoking debates on a variety of subjects look no further than the Intelligence squared podcast, great for those Sunday morning runs through the park.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Available on a variety of podcast apps &amp; online | <a href="https://www.intelligencesquared.com/podcasts/">intelligencesquared.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>RESET: RE:MIND STUDIO </p>
<p>The end of the year can get pretty busy, Re:Mind's studio is specially designed to be an escape from the hustle &amp; bustle of the city. Rediscover your calm at one of their classes.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><a href="https://shop.remindstudio.com/">Re:Mind Studio</a>, Eccleston Yards, 25A Eccleston Place, London, SW1W 9NF  |</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Remind-2_large.jpg?v=1573469216" alt="RE:MIND STUDIO" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>VISIT: MOVING TO MARS, DESIGN MUSEUM</p>
<p>At Lucas Hugh we are constantly inspired by the future. The Design museum has created a multi-sensory exhibition to get you thinking about the possibilities of future life Mars.</p>
<p>Design Museum, 224-238 Kensington High Street, London, W8 6AG |  <a href="https://designmuseum.org/">designmuseum.org</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Mars Design Museum" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Design_Museum_mars_large.jpeg?v=1573469337" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>REFUEL: HAGEN ESPRESSO BAR</p>
<p>Discover the best coffee on the King's Road right next door to our Boutique, grab a coffee and come in browse our in-store exclusives.</p>
<p>Hagen, 151 Kings Road, London SW3 5TX |  <a href="http://www.thehagenproject.com/">thehagenproject.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/2f99fc1c091d57758a8506d6e04c509d_large.jpg?v=1573469482" alt="Hagen Expresso Bar" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel-autumn-edition</id>
    <published>2019-09-13T13:29:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-02-28T11:47:36+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel-autumn-edition"/>
    <title>Fit Travel: Autumn Edition</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>From city breaks to island escapes, The Fit team recommends their favourite places and activities for fit travel this autumn.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/fit-travel-autumn-edition">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/3722291-1163911_0_41_1600_800_1400_700.rc_grande.jpg?v=1568201928" style="float: none;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/FullSizeRender_medium.jpg?v=1568201967" style="float: none; margin-top: 30px; margin-bottom: 30px;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>A round-up of some of the places we recommend adding to your Autumn travel list.</span></p>
<p><strong>CITY: BARCELONA</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: Hotel The Serras</strong></p>
<p>Placed in the Gothic quarter this 5-star boutique hotel overlooks the new luxury Port Vell. Expect to find Michelin-starred chefs, a rooftop terrace &amp; cocktail pool, all to be enjoyed whilst taking in the scenic view of luxury yachts moored in the harbour. </p>
<p><a href="https://hoteltheserrasbarcelona.com/" target="_blank" title="Hotel The Serras" rel="noopener noreferrer">Passeig de Colom, 9, 08002 Barcelona, Spain</a></p>
<p><strong>Try: PB:Training</strong></p>
<p>Take your morning workout to the beach with <a href="https://www.pbtraining.online/" target="_blank" title="PB:Training" rel="noopener noreferrer">PB:Training</a>; group fitness classes focus on strength &amp; conditioning or fat burning. Alternatively, opt for a personal training session tailored to your needs.</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/10f5b300f9b2f185cd850668d91c2e8a_medium.jpg?v=1568217493" style="float: none; margin-bottom: 45px;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/img-1542352325-9133-8358-C13F9158-C303-C093-A4B2820BAB179ABA__FocalPointCropWzQyMCw5NjAsNDksNTQsNzUsImpwZyIsNjUsMi41XQ_grande.jpg?v=1568202260" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>BEACH: NORTH ISLAND, NEW ZEALAND</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: Eagle's Nest Hotel</strong></p>
<p>Sat atop its own private ridgeline, the Eagle's Nest hotel &amp; retreat provides spectacular views of the Bay of Islands. They can even provide personal trainers &amp; spa therapists, this is the ultimate luxury stay. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><a href="http://www.eaglesnest.co.nz/" title="Eagles Nest New Zealand Luxury Retreat"><span>60 Tapeka Road, Russell 0242, Bay of Islands, New Zealand</span></a></p>
<p><strong>Try: Take a road trip &amp; dig your own natural spa</strong></p>
<p>Find hot water bubbling through the golden sands of <a href="https://www.thecoromandel.com/activities/must-do/hot-water-beach/" target="_blank" title="Hot Water Beach" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hot Water Beach</a> &amp; take a dip in your own natural hot spa pool either side of low-tide. </p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/435bb1d7c41722a69741f251376f6277_grande.jpg?v=1568199237" style="float: none;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ec64ecb48d16e2995c0bb6b03f382a38_medium.jpg?v=1568199277" style="float: none; margin-bottom: 120px;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>COUNTRYSIDE: UNITED KINGDOM</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: The Newt in Somerset</strong></p>
<p>In the beautiful English countryside you will find this newly opened Georgian family home. Since 1785 the estate has previously been home to seven generations of the Hobhouse family, including Arthur Hobhouse who happens to be the founder of the National Parks so you can expect the grounds to be spectacular.</p>
<p><a href="https://thenewtinsomerset.com/" target="_blank" title="The Newt Somerset" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bruton, Somerset, BA7 7NG, United Kingdom</a></p>
<p><strong>Try: Total relaxation</strong></p>
<p>After a morning stroll through the countryside head to the <a href="https://thenewtinsomerset.com/spa" target="_blank" title="The Newt In Somerset" rel="noopener noreferrer">spa</a> &amp; enjoy an ancient Hammam treatment which will relieve stress, increase circulation &amp; help ease &amp; relax any tired muscles.</p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/right-slider-ondeestamos4_medium.jpg?v=1568202563" style="float: none; margin-bottom: 125px;"> <img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Azores_Holidays.Sete_Cidades.Sao_Miguel.Azores.www_.azorschoice.com__Large_grande.jpg?v=1568202586" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>ISLAND: THE AZORES, PORTUGAL</strong></p>
<p><strong>Stay: Terra Nostra Garden Hotel</strong></p>
<p>Situated on the island of São Miguel next to the famous 1775 Terra Nostra Gardens this hotel is considered to be one of the best in the Azores. The hotel provides 24-hour access to the gardens where you can relax &amp; take in the lush surroundings.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span><a href="https://terranostra-gardenhotel.com/?utm_source=google-my-business&amp;utm_medium=organicsearch&amp;utm_campaign=tngh_gmb" target="_blank" title="Terra Nostra Garden Hotel" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rua Padre José Jacinto Botelho 5, 9675-061 Furnas, Portugal</a></span></p>
<p><strong>Try: Hiking</strong></p>
<p>The island has many walking <a href="http://trails.visitazores.com/en/islands/sao-miguel-0" title="Azores Trails" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">trails</a> for exploring the volcanic landscape. Staff at the Terra Nostra Hotel are friendly &amp; on hand to advise on local routes &amp; tours of the island.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-autumn-agenda</id>
    <published>2019-09-13T13:22:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-10-07T15:06:15+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-autumn-agenda"/>
    <title>YOUR AUTUMN AGENDA</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Your Autumn itinerary, made.</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-autumn-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>READ: THE MORNING MIND: USE YOUR BRAIN TO MASTER YOUR DAY AND SUPERCHARGE YOUR LIFE </p>
<p>Based on research from neuroscience &amp; medical experts this is a book that will certainly get you thinking about how you can make the most of your mornings and start your day off right, even on those mornings when the sun is hiding. </p>
<p>Written by Dr. Rob Carter III &amp; DR. Kirti Salwe Carter. Published by AMACOM | <a href="https://www.themorningmind.com/" target="_blank" title="The Morning Mind " rel="noopener noreferrer">themorningmind.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>SWEAT: IN AN ELEMENT HOT YOGA CLASS, SOMA HOUSE</p>
<p>Soma House, the luxury east London members fitness studio, have developed their own hot yoga classes based around three elements; Earth, Fire, and Water. Cool down after your class with a complimentary cold essential oil infused face cloth, don’t forget to wear your <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-hotties-black" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit Hotties">Technical Knit Hotties</a>.</p>
<p>Soma House London, Old Spitalfields Market, 8 Upper St, Horner Square, London, E1 6EW  | <a href="https://soma.house/" target="_blank" title="Soma House" rel="noopener noreferrer">soma.house</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/1.Clubhouse-SOMA_HOUSE_large.jpg?v=1566466246" alt=""></p>
<p> </p>
<p>VISIT: ANTHONY GORMLEY, ROYAL ACADEMY</p>
<p>Said to be his most ambitious exhibition in over 10 years, Anthony Gormley one of the UK’s most <span>celebrated</span> sculptors is taking centre stage at the Royal Academy for 11 weeks with a display of classic works alongside all new installations. </p>
<p>From 21st Sept till 3rd Dec 2019, Royal Academy, Burlington House, Piccadilly, London, W1J 0BD | <a href="https://www.royalacademy.org.uk/exhibition/antony-gormley" title="Royal Academy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">royalacademy.org.uk</a></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/cw-35436-914x520_large.jpg?v=1566403575" alt=""> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p>EAT: DAYLESFORD, BROMPTON CROSS</p>
<p>Daylesford opened their fourth outpost last year. Stop by to experience truly fresh, organic food, straight from the farm in their café or do a spot of shopping in their farm shop. Being all about nature they have even installed a tree felled from their Cotswolds farm in the centre of their store!</p>
<p>Daylesford, 76-82 Sloane Avenue, Brompton Cross, London, SW3 3DZ | <a href="https://www.daylesford.com/locations/brompton-cross-sw3/" target="_blank" title="Daylesford" rel="noopener noreferrer">daylesford.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/NW-Daylesford-Organic-Brompton-Cross_large.jpg?v=1566465903" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/reclaiming-my-attention-span</id>
    <published>2019-06-04T12:38:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-06-04T12:38:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/reclaiming-my-attention-span"/>
    <title>Reclaiming My Attention Span</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Beauty Editor Madeleine Spencer realises her relationship with her phone is less than healthy.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/reclaiming-my-attention-span">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>I realised things had to change over Christmas. Riddled with a cold which wiped me out, I spent more time lying prone on my phone than with my family. While the distraction from the relentless cough was merciful, looking back, I can’t recall what absorbed me: a picture on Instagram by my favourite blogger? A meaty op-ed on the #metoo movement? A cutesy video of a friend’s baby?</p>
<p>Whatever held my attention captive didn’t remain embedded in my memory, and that’s when I decided that my phone wasn’t giving me anything but a kick of dopamine with every like or comment.</p>
<p>I started with rules. I vowed to switch my phone to airplane mode overnight for at least nine hours. Preferably twelve. I also decided that I would have a tea and do some stretches in the morning before checking social media to give my mind some quiet time without the possibility of FOMO. When eating out, rather than have my phone face down on the table like a baby monitor, it had to remain in my bag, unchecked.</p>
<p>At first, the compulsion to check my phone was the hardest. My hands reached for it and my brain kept looping round to ‘look at phone mode’. It was as if it had been programmed to check, check, and check again. When my phone was in another room, I knew it was there, pulsing, living, a porthole to other lives. And I ignored it.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefit_phonerelationship-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555501060" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<blockquote>
<p>My hands reached for it and my brain kept looping round to ‘look at phone mode’.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>After a few weeks, I was reading more, and as my voracious appetite for books returned, so too did my attention span. Following the twists and turns of a character’s life unpunctuated by phone, breaks became a fun pastime, a thing to do for hours. I felt more engaged IRL, too, and found myself enjoying others in the flesh far more than I had in years. In short, I felt more like my core self than I had in a long time.</p>
<p>I am by no means there yet. In an absolutely ideal world, I’d check my phone once daily, twice at most. As a journalist, that’s not a reality, but adjusting my relationship with my phone has been undoubtedly positive and I fully intend on keeping mental - not electronic - tabs on my phone usage going forward.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/creative-reflections</id>
    <published>2019-05-15T15:44:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:09:05+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/creative-reflections"/>
    <title>Creative Reflections</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[From a two-time Oscar-winning costume designer to the director of an explosive documentary following Vivienne Westwood, Bridget Arsenault asks four of the film industry’s most-accomplished women to reflect on a pivotal moment in their careers.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/creative-reflections">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>From a two-time Oscar-winning costume designer to the director of an explosive documentary following Vivienne Westwood, Bridget Arsenault asks four of the film industry’s most-accomplished women to reflect on a pivotal moment in their careers.</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong>Having never been to film school, Quinn Shephard got her education on set, from as young as five, starring in shows like Hostages alongside Toni Collette and The Blacklist. Now only 23 years old, at 20, Quinn wrote, directed, starred in and produced her first feature film, Blame.</strong></p>
<p>I think I began my career by breaking the status quo, which was very daunting… I set out to do something that was pretty unprecedented for multiple reasons: my age, my level of experience, and even our budget level for the film. I constantly get people asking how I did what I did at my age, and I usually just answer “I don’t know, it’s just who I am!” It’s not like I woke up every day like “wow, I’m shattering boundaries.” I just did what I always wanted to do.</p>
<p><strong>Jenny Beavan, OBE has won two Academy Awards and received nominations an additional eight times, including for her work on Gosford Park, The King’s Speech and The Remains of the Day. Most recently Jenny triumphed in 2016 for her Costume Design on Mad Max: Fury Road, which also gained her the BAFTA. When Jenny accepted her BAFTA host Stephen Fry made a cutting remark about her appearance. Jenny has beautifully harnessed this moment and negativity to propel her career forward.</strong></p>
<p>Having worked predominately on period pieces, being offered and accepting the job to design the costumes for Mad Max: Fury Road felt quite revolutionary in its own right. Working on that film opened up so many new avenues both in work and life. In work: now I’m offered a hugely greater diversity of projects and life as a ‘feminist’, although I am not sure I am a very good one, but apparently, I am some kind of role model to young women!! Looking back, I wouldn’t approach any of it any differently. I would have accepted the job - such s fantastic opportunity, and the aftermath was unexpected, but I am quite happy now with the way it turned out!</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/creative_reflections_TheFit-1_large.jpg?v=1555425843" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p><strong>Lorna Tucker started her work in film in her 20s, primarily behind the camera producing tour videos and music promos. Her feature-length debut came only this year with Westwood: Punk, Icon, Activist, which premiered at the 2018 Sundance Film Festival. Lorna’s second documentary Amá, which will be released later this year, examines the issue of sterilisation abuses of Native American women in the United States and their fight for reproductive rights. It was co-produced by Colin Firth.</strong></p>
<p>A pivotal moment was saying no to Vivienne Westwood when she told me to re-edit elements of the film. For better or for worse, I knew I had to retain complete creative and editorial control, and I'm super proud of the results! Unfortunately, I knew that when I said no to her there would be consequences because of who she is and how powerful she is. Since Westwood was released, Vivienne's team have reached out to the fashion world and I've now been blacklisted by much of the industry and several fashion magazines have said they won't review the film or interview me due to their loyalty to Vivienne. It's a real shame, but I had to stay true to my vision and retain my integrity. The final edit of Westwood is not only an authentic and honest portrait of Vivienne, but it's also a true representation of my vision as a film-maker.</p>
<p><strong>Set designer Stella Fox has worked on everything from the mega-blockbuster Star Wars: The Force Awakens to Jane Campion’s John Keats biopic Bright Star. Stella’s work has taken her as far afield as Jordan, Budapest, Istanbul, Italy, Azerbaijan, the UAE and Malta. By no means restricted to film, one of her most notable projects was Channel 4’s sci-fi series Misfits, which won a BAFTA for production design in 2011.</strong></p>
<p>A few years after working on Star Wars: The Force Awakens, I was given the opportunity to join the same team on Star Wars: Episode VIII as an assistant set decorator. I imagine the majority of people would’ve jumped at the chance, but I turned it down. I wanted to stick to my guns as a decorator in my own right rather than assisting. I think this was a turning point in my career. I am now an established set decorator and have gone on to head up a wide variety of independent feature films and television series, including Entebbe starring Rosamund Pike and Danny Boyle’s new TV show Trust. It was incredibly tempting at the time to jump at the opportunity offered up to me rather than venturing forth on my own. However, I wouldn’t change a thing.</p>
<p><em>A longtime journalist and the former Associate Editor at Vanity Fair UK, <a href="https://www.bridgetarsenault.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bridget</a> has written for a number of respected publications, including Forbes, British Vogue, Departures, Travel+Leisure, House &amp; Garden and Architectural Digest.</em></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/for-the-love-of-london</id>
    <published>2019-04-11T11:30:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:27:40+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/for-the-love-of-london"/>
    <title>For the Love of London</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Elizabeth Bennet discovers the grass isn't always greener on the other side.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/for-the-love-of-london">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Whatever the trip away, there is always one phrase I look forward to hearing on my return: “we are now making our descent into London.” Every time I fly over the snaking river, sprawling parks, and the ever-changing skyline of skyscraper buildings, I take comfort in knowing that I’m home. I was born and brought up in London and have lived here for the majority of my life. Our capital city may get a bad rep - too expensive, too busy, too unfriendly - and while it isn’t without its fair share of problems, I still believe it’s one of the greatest cities on earth. Something I had forgotten until I left for three months earlier this year.</p>
<p>When my relationship ended at the beginning of January, I embraced the Eat, Pray, Love cliche and packed my bags for a solo trip to Asia. I was desperate to get away from London and the constant reminders of my past life that were following me round like a bad smell. I went on a retreat in Sri Lanka, trekked in the Himalayas of Nepal and explored technicolour India and its historic palaces. It was everything I hoped for. But one thing surprised me more than anything else: how much I ended up missing London. The green spaces, picture-perfect architecture and that quintessential attitude Londoners possess - all things you easily take for granted.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/travel_london_featimage_large.jpg?v=1554978449" alt="photo by Scott Mead" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h5 style="text-align: center;">Photo by Scott Mead</h5>
<p> </p>
<p>Arriving back at the beginning of June and the start of what felt like a never-ending heatwave also helped the transition period. With a climate so often grey, nothing boosts our collective mood better than a spell of sunshine. Throw into the mix the excitement of the World Cup, Wimbledon, and of course, Love Island, and I found myself met with a mood of optimism and joy. Walking through Soho on a weekday evening and seeing colleagues spill into the streets, rosé in hand, and watching parks fill up on weekends with impromptu picnics, BBQs and rounders games, reminded me of why I’m so lucky to live in a city like London. In fact, it even made me think, why go on holiday when you have so much on our doorstep.</p>
<p>This summer I’m making the most of my hometown in its finest season. I’ll be cooling off in the oasis that is Hampstead Heath Ladies Pond, walking the canal with a stop for a pub garden Pimms, eating my way around the many street food markets from Brixton to Borough, and ogling antiques with a coffee on Golborne Road. As Samuel Johnson famously said: “When a man is tired of London, he is tired of life.” Sometimes you just need a little break to realise this.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/april-reads</id>
    <published>2019-04-01T17:07:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:20:26+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/april-reads"/>
    <title>April Reads</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Three books to read in the springtime sun. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/april-reads">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<h3>Text Me When You Get Home - The evolution and triumph of female friendship, Kayleen Shaefer</h3>
<p><strong><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Evolution-Triumph-Modern-Female-Friendship/dp/1101986123/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1523981755&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=text+me+when+you+get+home" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Text Me When You Get Home</a> </strong>is a meditation on female friendships and how they tend to shape our lives well beyond those we with our partners or family. While not a revelatory read, the book will make you smile and call your people, or at least text them.</p>
<h3> </h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_aprilreads_thefit-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555517116" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </p>
<h3>The Female Persuasion, Meg Wolitzer</h3>
<p>Meg Wolitzer is having a moment, not just on The Fit - in <strong><a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/winter-reading/">March</a> </strong>we recommended Wolitzer’s, The Interestings - the New York Times thinks so too. This month Wolitzer is back with <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Female-Persuasion-Meg-Wolitzer-author/dp/1594488401/ref=sr_1_1?s=books&amp;ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1523982089&amp;sr=1-1&amp;keywords=the+female+persuasion" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Female Persuasion</a>,</strong> a timely and absorbing read about power, ambition, and the complicated mentor/mentee relationship.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3>Look Alive Out There, Sloane Crosley</h3>
<p>Admittedly, we are yet to read Crosley's third foray into the personal essay (it did only come out two weeks ago). However, if <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Was-Told-Thered-Cake/dp/1846271851/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8&amp;qid=1523981575&amp;sr=8-1&amp;keywords=i+was+told+there%27d+be+cake" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">I Was Told There’d Be Cake</a> </strong>and <strong><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/How-Did-You-This-Number/dp/1846272262/ref=pd_sim_14_2?_encoding=UTF8&amp;pd_rd_i=1846272262&amp;pd_rd_r=5W6Z3E2W8HDC107GBBAW&amp;pd_rd_w=3xlX9&amp;pd_rd_wg=O5V3r&amp;psc=1&amp;refRID=5W6Z3E2W8HDC107GBBAW" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">How Did You Get This Number</a> </strong>are any indication, Look Alive Out There is worth the blind recommendation. If you’re unconvinced, here’s <strong><a href="https://www.thecut.com/2018/03/excerpt-look-alive-out-there-by-sloane-crosley.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">an excerpt</a>.</strong></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-paris</id>
    <published>2019-02-27T01:21:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:12:35+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-paris"/>
    <title>The Fit Guide: Paris</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p style="text-align: center;">For business or pleasure, the Lucas Hugh team recommends their favourite places and activities for fit and wellness travel.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-paris">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h3></h3>
<h3></h3>
<h3></h3>
<h3><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/biologique-recherche-pairs-the-fit-paris-guide-1_large.jpg?v=1552267960" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></h3>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Biologique-Recherche. Photo by Wallpaper</span></h5>
<p> </p>
<p>Designed for the editor on-the-move during fashion week or a leisure traveller in search of a wellness-focused weekend. Our team shares insights with our favourite Paris destinations for performance, style, culture, and self.</p>
<p>Whether a frequent visitor, or researching for your first trip, let this guide save you time by helping you to discover something new.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">PERFORMANCE</h3>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Kshanti-Yoga-Paris-Lucas-Hugh-The-Fit_large.jpg?v=1552268029" style="float: none; display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Photo by Kshanti Yoga</span></h5>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p><span>1. DYNAMO CYCLING LAFAYETTE</span></p>
<p><span>9TH | <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/qC4SLnkm6122" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">24 RUE CHAUCHAT, 75009</a> </span></p>
<p>Turn up your resistance with a high-intensity 45-minute spin class.  Easily accessible with four locations across central Paris and well-equipped change room facilities   Dynamo studios. For an endorphin rush, t<span>rial a class by sought after master coach Clotilde Chaumet. To secure a space, we recommend booking 1-week ahead. Book <a href="https://www.dynamo-cycling.com/studios" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>.</span></p>
<p><span>OPEN: MON-SUN | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/dynamocycling/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@DYNAMOCYCLING</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>2. L’USINE SPORTS CLUB</span></p>
<p><span>2ND |<a href="https://goo.gl/maps/oHkWi3eJmZ82" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">8 RUE DEL LA MICHODIÈRE, 75002</a> </span></p>
<p>Known for spacious clubs with sleek industrial designs, look to L’Usine for the premium gym experience.<span> </span><span>The central Opera location is a three-level club offering high-end equipment, group classes – such as cross-fit, boxing and cycling – as well as a spa. The change rooms are sleek and well stocked with Byredo products. Additional locations in Saint Lazare (new location) and Beaubourg, as well as international locations in Brussels and Genevia. Day passes available: <a href="mailto:contact@usinesportsclub.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">contact@usinesportsclub.com</a>.</span></p>
<p><span>OPEN: MON-SUN |<a href="https://www.instagram.com/lusine_sport/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@LUSINE_SPORT</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>3. KSHANTI YOGA</span></p>
<p><span>6TH | <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/do8X8zq6p562" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">13 RUE DU VIEUX COLOMBIER, 75006 </a></span></p>
<p><span>Nestled in a courtyard in a converted church, this studio offers a tranquil escape the city’s hustle. Kshanti is the ideal space to disconnect and focus (whilst your cell  phone conveniently recharges in your locker). Reset with a vinyasa or restorative class, or try a morning chromotherapy class – yoga which uses light and colour therapy to help refocus. Book <a href="http://kshanti-yoga.com/courses/planning/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a> (or through your Mindbody App). </span></p>
<p><span>OPEN: MON-SUN | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/kshantiyoga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@KSHANTIYOGA</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p><span>4. REFORMATION PILATES </span></p>
<p><span>3RD | <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/PmzJ3SccwQ92" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">175 RUE DU TEMPLE, 75003  </a></span></p>
<p>This bright and calming studio in La Marais offers group and private reformer or tower pilates classes. The studio caters to clients of all experience levels in a relaxing space filled with natural light and hanging plants. Whether you up for a 45 or 55 minute class, all sessions are designed to tone, stretch and strengthen you muscles. For a low-impact class trial ‘barre &amp; stretch’ to improve posture and flexibility or the faster-paced ‘intense’ cardio class that will have you breaking a sweat through quick transitions. Book<span> </span><a href="https://reformation-pilates.com/en/class-schedule/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>.</p>
<p><span>OPEN: MON-SUN | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/reformation.pilates/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@REFORMATION.PILATES</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
6. RUNNING ROUTE 
<p><span>CANAL ST MARTIN</span></p>
<p><span>Take in the city with a a 6km canal side run beginning at Place de la Bastille and ending at Cité des Sciences et de l’Industrie, Europe’s largest science museum.</span></p>
<p><strong><a href="http://bit.ly/2NCJfYS"><span>RUNNING MAP</span></a></strong></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">STYLE</h3>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen-Shot-2019-02-27-at-2.49.36-PM_large.png?v=1552268201" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Installation by Joana Vasconcelos February 2019. Image by Le Bon Marché</span></h5>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>7. LE BON MARCHE</span></p>
<p><span><span class="w8qArf">7TH |  </span><a href="https://goo.gl/maps/Mp1rz49RmB92" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="LrzXr">24 RUE DE SÈVRES, 75007</span></a><br></span></p>
<p><span>This historic institution continues to push boundaries by showcasing emerging designers alongside heritage brands, with site-specific contemporary art installations and experiential pop-ups. </span><span>Find Lucas Hugh located in the Galerie du Sport on the first floor. </span></p>
<p><span>OPEN: MON-SUN | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lebonmarcherivegauche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@LEBONMARCHE</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"></h3>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">CULTURE</h3>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/173445970_large.jpg?v=1552268236" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;">Image by Maison Armance</h5>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>8. MAISON ARMANCE </p>
<p class="section">1ST | <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/anQsCpp8ZkT2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">5 RUE CAMBON, 75001</a></p>
<p class="section">This 4-star boutique hotel is located in the heart of Paris. With a hidden courtyard entrance off rue Cambon and only twenty rooms located between the 3rd and 5th floors, the suites provide guests intimacy of stylish Parisian apartment. Book<span> </span><a href="https://www.paris-maison-armance.com/?gclid=Cj0KCQiAh9njBRCYARIsALJhQkFf6n3ogNOpTI-bMZxN_dzTW9danSnbQrdOm0ShfMxE_cVKIC1APfIaAts4EALw_wcB" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>. </p>
<p class="section">OPEN: MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/hotelsespritdefrance/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@HOTELSESPRITDEFRANCE</a></p>
<p class="section"> </p>
<p class="section"><span>9. HENRI CARTIER-BRESSON FOUNDATION</span></p>
<p>3RD |<span> </span><a href="https://goo.gl/maps/kRfPtCYXzPU2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">79 RUE DES ARCHIVES, 75003</a></p>
<p>While in the Marais, navigate your way to a the quite Rue des Archives to discover the work of humanist photographer Henri Cartier-Bresson and his wife Martine Franck. Known for his use of candid photography, Cartier-Bresson has shot many icons including Marilyn Monroe, Pablo Picasso, and Le Corbusier. The newly-opened 2,500 square-foot exhibition space, showcases both Cartier-Bresson and Franck’s work as well as international photography exhibitions. Book tickets<span> </span><a href="https://fhcb.tickeasy.com/en-GB/home" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>.</p>
<p>OPEN: TUES-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/fondationhcb/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@FONDATIONHCB</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">SELF</h3>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/oh-my-cream-paris-rue-debelleyme-lucas-hugh-the-fit-paris-guide_large.png?v=1552268283" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Photo by Oh My Cream!</span></h5>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>11. OH MY CREAM </span></p>
<p><span>3RD | <a href="https://goo.gl/maps/E7cRYNx6mQB2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">17 RUE DEBELLEYME, 75003</a></span></p>
<p><span>The destination for clean beauty products in Paris, Oh My Cream! takes a considered approach to product selection, offering organic and ethically sourced . W</span><span>ith five location across Paris, the boutique carries both French and international brands, offering treatments at several locations. This is the ideal store to discover new products or replenish any missing items you forgot to pack. Two products to look for: <a href="https://www.ohmycream.com/collections/cheveux/products/voluminous-shampoo-shampoing-volumateur?variant=38934955460" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rahua Volumising Shampoo</a> designed to revitalize the hair and scalp and </span><a href="https://en.ohmycream.com/products/aura-manuka-honey-mask?variant=38934760068" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Aura Manuka Honey Mask</a> offers deep-hydration ideal for dull or tired skin. </p>
<p><span>OPEN: TUES-SAT | <a href="https://www.instagram.com/ohmycream/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@OHMYCREAM</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<p>12. BIOLOGIQUE RECHERCHE</p>
<p>8TH |<span> </span><a href="https://goo.gl/maps/QG6YsEors5K2" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">32 AV. DES CHAMPS- ÉLYSÉES, 75008</a></p>
<p>French brand Biologique Recherche best known for the purifying and exfoliating<span> </span><a href="http://biologiquerechercheuk.co.uk/skincare/face/lotions/lotion-p50" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">lotion P50</a><span> </span>that has developed a cult following by skincare experts and enthusiasts. Well known for the a French clinical approach to skincare, products are fragrance free using pure and concentrated raw active ingredients. Fan of the brand can indulge and relax and enjoy customised facial treatment with the assistance of the qualified skincare team at Biologique Recherche’s Embassy of beauty on the Champs-Élysées. Book<span> </span><a href="https://www.ambassadedelabeaute.fr/en/contact-form.php" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>. </p>
<p>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/biologique_recherche/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@<strong>BIOLOGIQUE_RECHERCHE</strong></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Share your experience of the guide with <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lucashughlondon/">@LUCASHUGHLONDON</a>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-carly-wilford</id>
    <published>2018-11-06T21:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:26:15+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-carly-wilford"/>
    <title>High Performer: Carly Wilford</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>“We created a movement of women stepping up and thinking that if I can do this, if I can hang upside down by just my legs, then I can go and fulfill my dreams.”</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-carly-wilford">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<blockquote>“We created a movement of women stepping up and thinking that if I can do this, if I can hang upside down by just my legs, then I can go and fulfill my dreams.”</blockquote>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Unknown-7_grande.jpeg?v=1552860359" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Known today for her talent as a DJ, Presenter and Creator of the SISTER Collective, Carly Wilford’s journey to get to this point took some unexpected turns. I was immediately in awe of how much she has achieved in such a short time.</p>
<p>Settled in a busy role in picture syndication with Marie Claire, but exhausted by the commute, Carly’s inspiration was sparked when she took a pole dancing class at her gym. Seeing the impact it had on her body in just 6 weeks, she knew it was something more people needed to do – so Carly left Marie Claire to become a personal trainer and pole-dancing instructor.</p>
<p>At the time, pole dancing was relatively unknown. Carly launched the first ever official ‘class’ at a health club in her hometown of Northampton. With six women signed up and one pole weighed down with sand bags, even the club managers were unsure- insisting that she erect curtains during the class.</p>
<p>Yet to people’s surprise, Carly’s venture was a hit. She expanded to teach at multiple sites; eventually setting up her own dance studio and teacher training course. She led classes on syllabus at Italia Conte, Pineapple and became involved with choreography at the Royal Opera House and Royal Shakespeare Company.</p>
<p>Carly admits her success wasn’t without its bumps in the road, <em>“Whenever you’re doing something left-of-center people question it, but what I realised was that [our classes were helping these women change their lives]…We created a movement of women stepping up and thinking that if I can do this, if I can hang upside down by just my legs, then I can go and fulfill my dreams.”</em></p>
<p>Seeing her students make such positive changes inspired Carly to re-evaluate her own goals. At the back of her mind she had always wanted to be a presenter, <em>“I had to look in the mirror and be like- is this where you want to be? I’d just got married and we had this business together but I realised that [I wanted something different]- so I walked away from everything- my relationship and my business. I stopped personal training, I kept my dance school and then I decided to throw myself into becoming a presenter, which was pretty crazy.”</em></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Unknown-2_grande.jpeg?v=1552860398" style="float: none;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Photo by Jack Goodman, Lefteris Primos, Antonello Zappa, RaRa</span></h5>
<p> </p>
<p>It was a tough time for Carly, reassessing everything she’d worked so hard for. <em>“Whenever you’re going through a lot and you have a lot of time, there are two things you can do – you can sit and mull over everything that’s happened in your life or you can use it productively… I [used] it to make plans’’</em></p>
<p>She’s never looked back, going on to work with unsigned artists, interview incredible talent and DJ-ing at gigs across the world. What drives her to keep moving forward? <em>“I can see the [potential] that’s within people if they’re willing to take risks. It’s amazing when you start to see people go after their dreams, to get on that path and [watch opportunities open up] to them.”</em></p>
<blockquote>“I really think it’s what we’re all here to do, the world would be so different if everyone stopped worrying about the drama and just focused on what they love. I realised that if I could help people focus on what they love I could watch them fly, I just had to remember to do that for myself.”</blockquote>
<p>Carly’s bravery and passion shone through as we discussed how she’s been able to identify trends ahead of others and take some scary leaps. <em>“If there’s a load of people walking one way I always think ‘oh what’s going on this way’ and I kind of walk the other… I find it super fascinating, and I really believe in intuition- that instinct, it can lead you down incredible paths. I also believe in magic…. I believe in the fact that if you take a leap, a risk, and it feels right, if you feel that- just go with it. There are some incredible things you can find on the other side of that”.</em></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-london</id>
    <published>2018-09-19T12:41:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:17:54+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-london"/>
    <title>The Fit Guide: London</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><meta charset="utf-8"><meta charset="utf-8">
<p style="text-align: center;">Insider access to our city.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-london">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="padding-left: 30px;">Welcome to Lucas Hugh’s London, the best the city has to offer in performance, style, culture, and self. Let this guide save you time by helping you to discover something new for yourself.</p>
<p style="padding-left: 30px;"> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LHL_CITYGUIDE_DIGITALMAP.jpg?v=1552654235" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;"><span>PERFORMANCE</span></h2>
<h4>1. HEARTCORE </h4>
<p>CHELSEA | 6 BURNSALL STREET, SW3 3ST</p>
<p>Heartcore’s Pilates classes are the best in London for a full-body reset. With a focus on wellbeing and positivity, the studio’s dedicated instructors will guide you through an intense workout, leaving you feeling strong and refreshed.<br>OPEN: MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/heartcorelife/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@HEARTCORELIFE</a></p>
<h4>2. DEFINE LONDON </h4>
<p>FITZROVIA | 82 GREAT PORTLAND ST, W1W 7NW</p>
<p>Created by former Broadway dancer Ashley Verma, the Define method includes barre and strength building classes designed to develop a strong and sculpted body through an intimate group fitness class.<br>OPEN: MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/define.london/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@DEFINE.LONDON</a></p>
<h4>3. TWENTYTWO PERSONAL TRAINING</h4>
<p>KENSINGTON | 22A ELVASTON MEWS, SW7 5HZ</p>
<p>Discreetly located in a converted Mews house, founder Dalton Wong leads a team of skilled therapists to o er bespoke diets and training that help transform body and mind.<br>BY APPOINTMENT ONLY |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/dalton_wong22/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@DALTON_WONG22</a></p>
<h4>4. LOUISE PARKER </h4>
<p>KNIGHTSBRIDGE | HARRODS, 87-135 BROMPTON RD, SW1X 7XL</p>
<p>This dietician-led lifestyle program trains clients to build long-lasting habits. Introduce yourself to the method through their signature Transform program or trial the clinic with cardio conditioning classes.<br>OPEN: MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/louiseparkermethod/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@LOUISEPARKERMETHOD</a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span>STYLE</span></h3>
<h4>5. THE NEW CRAFTSMEN </h4>
<p>MAYFAIR | 34 N ROW, W1K 6DG</p>
<p>Spanning furniture, lighting, textiles, ceramics and accessories, The New Craftsmen’s collection is made by a growing network of exceptional craft makers across the British Isles.<br>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/thenewcraftsmen/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@THENEWCRAFTSMEN</a></p>
<h4>6. ALEX EAGLE STUDIO</h4>
<p>SOHO | 6-10 LEXINGTON STREET, W1F 0LB</p>
<p>Walking into the studio feels like you are stepping into a beautiful apartment where you can shop fashion, furniture, art and lifestyle products. Don’t miss Skinwork beauty treatments on the basement door.<br>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/alexeaglestudio/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@ALEXEAGLEOFFICIAL</a></p>
<h4>7. 5 CARLOS PLACE BY MATCHESFASHION.COM</h4>
<p>MAYFAIR | 5 CARLOS PL, W1K 3AP</p>
<p>Split over 5 floors Matches Fashion aims to bring a new retail experience, connecting the digital and physical. With floors dedicated<br>to hosting masterclasses, dinners, podcast broadcasting, live video streaming and private shopping.<br>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/matchesfashion/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@MATCHESFASHION</a></p>
<h4>8. PERFUMER H </h4>
<p>MARYLEBONE | 106A CRAWFORD ST, W1H 2HZ</p>
<p>Escape from the city streets to take-in expertly crafted scents designed by British perfumer Lyn Harris. This inspiring space is filled with rich tones and velvet textures that compliment dark hand-blown glass bottles framed along the walls.<br>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/perfumerhlondon/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@PERFUMERHLONDON</a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span>CULTURE</span></h3>
<p> </p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/GAGOSIAN_GALLERY-1_large.jpg?v=1552654417" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h4>9. THE ROASTING PARTY </h4>
<p>CHELSEA | 253 PAVILLION RD, SW1X 0BP</p>
<p>Located on Pavillion road, it’s a great stop<br>for locally roasted co ee while shopping<br>in the area, or post workout after a class at neighbouring KXU studio. Contrary to its name, the second level space is great for a calm break to enjoy a co ee, catch up on your messages or meet with a friend.<br>OPEN MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/theroastingpartyuk/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@THEROASTINGPARTYUK</a></p>
<h4>10. CHELSEA PHYSIC GARDEN </h4>
<p>CHELSEA | 66 ROYAL HOSPITAL RD, SW3 4HS</p>
<p>Founded in 1673 by Apothecaries, this is now one of the best oasis retreats in central London. Perfect for when you need to take a deep breath and tune in with nature.<br>OPEN: SUN – FRI |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/chelsea_physic_garden/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@CHELSEA_PHYSIC_GARDEN</a></p>
<h4>11. GAGOSIAN GALLERY </h4>
<p>MAYFAIR | 20 GROSVENOR HILL, W1K 3QD</p>
<p>With its dark oak doors and open glass ceiling, the 180m2 gallery is the perfect canvas for its collection of modern and contemporary art, visit for a hit of inspiration.<br>OPEN: MON-FRI |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/gagosian/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@GAGOSIAN</a></p>
<h4>12. ROGANIC</h4>
<p>PLANT-BASED FINE DINING DRYBY</p>
<p>MARYLEBONE | 5-7 BLANDFORD STREET, W1U 3DB<br>A forward-thinking dining experience that o ers a tasting menu with a new take on plant-based fine-dining and simple aesthetic. Also, try Aulis their intimate development kitchen based in Soho.<br>OPEN: TUES-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/roganic/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@ROGANIC</a></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><span mce-data-marked="1">SELF</span></h3>
<p> </p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/REMIND_STUDIO_large.jpg?v=1552654486" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/HARRODSWELLNESS_CLINIC_large.jpg?v=1552654630" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h4>13. SARAH CHAPMAN CLINIC </h4>
<p>CHELSEA | 259 PAVILION RD, SW1X 0BP</p>
<p>Understand your skin in microscopic detail through luxurious bespoke facial treatments. Leading facialist Sarah Chapman’s approach combines cosmeceutical science with pure botanicals that will leave you glowing. Try the Skinesis Overnight Facial for firming results.<br>OPEN: MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/skinesis/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@SKINESIS</a></p>
<h4>14. DR MARYAM ZAMANI </h4>
<p>CHELSEA | 120 SLOANE ST, SW1X 9BW</p>
<p>With Dr Zamani’s unique and extensive medical training she provides treatments that guarantee the most natural results. Both surgical and non-surgical procedures will leave others wondering if it’s simply down to a post-holiday refresh or a change in beauty routine.<br>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/drmaryamzamani/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@DRMARYAMZAMANI</a></p>
<h4>15. RE-MIND STUDIO </h4>
<p>BELGRAVIA | 25A ECCLESTON PL, SW1W 9NF</p>
<p>London ’s first wellness destination encompassing a drop-in meditation studio and an eco-wellness store. Offering a wealth of meditation practices from breathing exercises to the sound of a mantra.<br>OPEN: MON-SUN |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/remindstudio/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@REMINDSTUDIO</a></p>
<h4>16. DRYBY</h4>
<p>HAIR &amp; NAIL ART STUDIO</p>
<p>MARYLEBONE | 74 MORTIMER ST, W1W 7RZ<br>Set apart by its beautiful interior design and luxurious treatments, Dryby is a go-to for blowout treatments or nail-art manicures. The salon goes above and beyond to create a relaxing space in the heart of Fitzrovia.<br>OPEN: MON-SAT |<span> </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/drybylondon/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@DRYBYLONDON</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-best-of-london-design</id>
    <published>2018-08-16T12:12:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:27:49+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-best-of-london-design"/>
    <title>The Best of London Design</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Not to be outshone by London Fashion Week, London Design Festival and London Design Biennial are back this September showcasing the best and brightest design talent from around the world. Stay in the know with our edit of not-to-be-missed exhibitions and installations. </p>
<p> </p>
<h3><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LDB_lat_large.jpg?v=1554979988" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></h3>
<p> </p>
<h3>London Design Biennial</h3>
<p>For its second year, the London Design Biennial explores the theme of 'emotional states' through an exhibition of interactive design installations held at Somerset House. This year, the truly global exhibit includes works from 40 countries, cities and territories spanning 6 continents. </p>
<p>Not-to-be-missed:</p>
<p><a href="http://www.londondesignbiennale.com/countries/australia/2018" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Full spectrum</a>, Australia </p>
<p><a href="http://www.londondesignbiennale.com/countries/lebanon/2018" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Silent Room</a>, Lebanon </p>
<p><a href="http://www.londondesignbiennale.com/countries/dundee/2018" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Shpeel,</a> Scotland</p>
<p>4-23rd September, Somerset House, <a href="http://www.londondesignbiennale.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">londondesignbiennale.com</a></p>
<h3> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LDF_esdelvin_large.jpg?v=1554980787" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;">
</h3>
<p> </p>
<h3>London Design Festival</h3>
<p>Now in its 16th year, London Design Festival has long been a highlight of any design-minded Londoners diary. The V&amp;A will be the festival’s main design hub, but installations are planned to pop up across.  </p>
<p>Not-to-be-missed:</p>
<p><a href="http://globaldesignforum.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Global Design Forum</a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.londondesignfestival.com/event/henrik-vibskov-onion-farm" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Onion Farm </a></p>
<p><a href="https://www.londondesignfestival.com/event/beatie-wolfe-art-music-digital-age-series-world-first-designs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Art of Music in the Digital Age</a></p>
<p>15-23rd September, V&amp;A, <a href="http://www.londondesignfestival.com/">londondesignfestival.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LDB_Scot_large.jpg?v=1554981112" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></div>
<div></div>
<div>Off-site happenings: </div>
<div> </div>
<div>
<a href="https://www.londondesignfair.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">London Design Fair</a>, 22–23rd September, Old Truman Brewery</div>
<p><a href="https://www.wallpaper.com/design/es-devlin-trafalgar-square-installation-london-design-festival-2018" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Es Delvin x Google</a>, 18-23 September, Trafalgar Square</p>
<p><a href="https://designmuseum.org/whats-on/london-design-festival-2018/mind-pilot-installation-by-loopph" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mind Pilot</a>, 15-23rd September, Design Museum </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-august-agenda</id>
    <published>2018-08-01T12:09:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:12:48+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-august-agenda"/>
    <title>Your August Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>What to do in the capital this month. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-august-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3>WATCH: SOMERSET HOUSE, FILM4 SUMMER SCREEN</h3>
<p>The big screen returns at Somerset House! Films old and new are scheduled every evening from now until August 22nd, we recommend booking now to avoid missing out on your favourites. Sadly next Monday's screening of Call Me By Your Name has already sold out. </p>
<p>Somerset House, Strand, London WC2R 1LA <a href="https://www.somersethouse.org.uk/whats-on/film4-summer-screen" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">somersethouse.org.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3>SWEAT: THIRD SPACE FESTIVAL, HATHA YOGA</h3>
<p>Because you've probably done enough sweating due to the heatwave we've had hanging over us for the last month or so, take a more relaxing approach to exercise with Third Space's Hatha Yoga classes. The free classes, a part of their Third Space Festival series are hosted outdoors at Tower Bridge every Thursday morning through August. Grab your <a href="https://lucashugh.com/collections/technical-knit" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit</a> and meet us there!</p>
<p>Third Space Festival, Tower Bridge <a href="https://www.thirdspace.london/media/THI210_A3-Fitstival_timetable-TB_02.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">thirdspace.london</a></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen-Shot-2018-08-10-at-10.19.20_large.png?v=1556017684" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </p>
<h3>GO: BANKSY, GREATEST HITS 2002 - 2008 </h3>
<p>Don't miss viewing the famed street artists work displayed together for the first time in the UK. The free exhibit by the Lazinc Sackville gallery in Mayfair shows everything from his well-known hits, the Tesco Value Cream of Tomato Soup' is a favourite, to his lesser-known stencilled canvases.</p>
<p>Ends August 25th, Lazinc Sackville, <a class="external" href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Lazinc+Sackville/@51.5099216,-0.1409258,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x0:0x681832af53e7046!8m2!3d51.5099216!4d-0.1387371?hl=en-GB" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">29 Sackville Street, Mayfair, London, </a><a class="external" href="https://maps.google.com/?q=29+Sackville+Street+%7C+Mayfair+%7C+London+%7C+W1S+3DX&amp;entry=gmail&amp;source=g" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">W1S 3DX</a> <a href="https://www.lazinc.com/exhibitions/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">lazinc.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<h3>EAT: BOREALIS LONDON </h3>
<p>Open from breakfast through to dinner, Borealis is the new Scandinavian foodie destination from Danish-born restaurateur Soren Jessen. Positioned opposite Borough Station, the space includes a Borealis To Go, serving up coffee, pastries, salads and of course SMØRREBRØD for the time-pressed commuter.</p>
<p>Borealis London,180 Borough High St, London SE1 1LB <a href="http://borealislondon.co.uk" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">borealislondon.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-july-agenda</id>
    <published>2018-07-01T12:01:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:14:10+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-july-agenda"/>
    <title>Your July Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>With the UK in the throes of summer, we've created an agenda that focuses solely on one thing: recreation.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-july-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3>STRETCH: ROOFTOP YOGA, THE BERKELEY</h3>
<p><span>Make the most of the clear days and treat yourself to a rooftop yoga session at The Berkeley followed by half a day of sunning yourself next to the pool. What luxury. </span></p>
<p>Wilton Place, Knightsbridge, London, SW1X 7RL <strong><a href="https://www.the-berkeley.co.uk/health-club-spa/rooftop-yoga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">the-berkeley.co.uk</a></strong></p>
<p> </p>
<h3><span>SWEAT: WORK ON YOUR SERVE</span></h3>
<p>With Wimbledon just around the corner, we’re donning our <a href="https://lucashugh.com/collections/tennis" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">tennis whites</a> and pretending to be Kirsten Dunst in the classic 2004 film, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wimbledon_(film)" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Wimbledon</a>. Paul Bettany, if you’re around we can be found working on our serves at the local club.</p>
<p><span>Holland Park Lawn Tennis Club, </span><strong><a href="http://hollandparkltc.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">hollandparkltc.co.uk</a></strong></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/July_Agenda_lucas_Hugh_large.jpg?v=1556017384" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3><span>DO: ART IN THE PARK</span></h3>
<p>Raise your step count while taking in the summer installations in Hyde Park. Spend some time watching the light bend and change in <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/meet-2018s-serpentine-pavillion-architect/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Frida Escobedo’s Pavilion</a><span> and admire </span><a href="https://www.dezeen.com/2018/06/18/cristo-unveils-the-london-mastaba-floating-on-serpentine-lake/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Mastaba</a><span>, Christo’s mosaic-like pyramid of over 7,000 oil barrels floating on the Serpentine.</span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3><span>GO: FIRST OF THE SUMMER WINE</span></h3>
<p><span>School holidays are fast approaching before they hit we recommend getting in some quality adult days out. What could be better than a day trip to the countryside with a side of wine tasting? Chapel Down Vineyard near the National Trust’s Smallhythe Place in Tenterden is one of the best and less than two hours from central London. Don’t leave without a bottle (or case) of their English Rose.</span></p>
<p>Small Hythe, Tenterden, Kent, TN30 7NG <strong><a href="https://www.chapeldown.com/visit/your-visit" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">chapeldown.com</a></strong></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-june-agenda</id>
    <published>2018-06-01T11:59:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:17:21+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-june-agenda"/>
    <title>Your June Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Where to go, what to see this month.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-june-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><span>Watch: McQueen</span></h3>
<p>Spend 111 minutes emersed in the subversive, artistic and darkly captivating world of renegade fashion designer Alexander McQueen. The documentary, directed by Ian Bonhôte And Peter Ettedgui is a sensitive and moving view of the wildly creative iconoclast, following McQueen’s meteoric rise from Central Saint Martins graduate in 1992, to his appointment as creative director of Givenchy in 1997 and the final years he dedicated to his own label before his death in 2010.</p>
<p>Released 8th June, Showing at Barbican cinema until June 14th, <a href="https://tickets.barbican.org.uk/eticketing/performancelist.asp?shoID=43944,43945" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">barbican.org.uk</a>, Regent St Cinema until June 24th <a href="https://www.regentstreetcinema.com/programme/mcqueen/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">regentstreetcinema.com</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thefit_juneagenda_lucashugh_large.jpg?v=1556017034" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3><span>Go: Japan House</span></h3>
<p>Opening on Kensington High Street on June 22nd, London has been chosen as one of the three global destinations to host Japan House, a creative crossroads for Japan and the UK. Part of a global initiative led by the Japanese Ministry of Foreign Affairs Japan House London will be a home for Japanese creativity and innovation, providing authentic encounters with the very best in art, design, gastronomy, innovation and technology, allowing visitors a deeper appreciation of Japanese culture. Book now for Japan House's resident restaurant, Akira created by chef SHIMIZU Akira which promised to offer a truly immersive encounter with Japanese food culture.</p>
<p>Opens 22 June; 101-111 Kensington High St, Kensington, London W8 5SA, <a href="https://www.japanhouselondon.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">japanhouselondon.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3>Sweat: RooFIT Pop-Up Series</h3>
<p>When you live in London you have to make the most of your time outdoors. That's why this summer, we're looking to relocate our workouts to the rooftop of the Montcalm Royal London House Hotel in Finsbury Square. This month from the 21st to the 29th Triyoga will be taking over the space so you can find your centre while taking in the panoramic views. Tickets are £25, shower facilities and equipment are provided and to ensure you start the day off right, PRESS are providing the refreshing cold-pressed juices - grab your <a href="https://lucashugh.com/collections/technical-knit" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">technical knit</a> and meet us there!</p>
<p>22-25 Finsbury Square, London, EC2A 1DX, <a href="http://aviarylondon.com/Roofit/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">aviarylondon.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/may-reads</id>
    <published>2018-05-23T10:48:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:19:18+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/may-reads"/>
    <title>May Reads</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Two books to read this month and one to look forward to for next. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/may-reads">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3><span>On Chesil Beach, Ian Mcewan</span></h3>
<p><span><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/dp/B00354YA4U/ref=dp-kindle-redirect?_encoding=UTF8&amp;btkr=1" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">On Chesil Beach</a> follows a day in the life of a couple of virgin 20-somethings as they struggle to navigate the tricky circumstance that is their wedding night and the expectations that come with that time. Set in 1960s England, as the opening line of the book narrates, "they lived in a time when a conversation about sexual difficulties was plainly impossible." </span></p>
<p><span>It's a story of unsaid things, young arrogance and naivety told in Mcewan’s irresistible and elegant prose. </span><span>First published in 2007, its <a href="https://lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-may-agenda" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">feature film adaptation</a> is released this month, as always, read it before you see it. </span></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_reading_thefit-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555577093" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3><span>You Think It, I’ll Say It, Curtis Sittenfeld</span></h3>
<p><span>In summer (yes, it is technically spring but we’ve already established summer begins in May) there is nothing we like more than a collection of short stories that you can dip in and out of without feeling the guilt of abandoning one book for another. <a href="https://www.amazon.com/You-Think-Ill-Say-Stories/dp/0399592865" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">You Think, I’ll Say It</a> is a collection of 10 stories depicting human nature in all its cringe-inducing glory. To try before you by, one of the book's stories, Gender Studies, is available on the <a href="https://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2016/08/29/gender-studies-by-curtis-sittenfeld" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">New Yorker</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3><span>The Mars Room, Rachel Kushner </span></h3>
<p><span>The Mars Room is Rachel Kushner’s third novel, her previous two, The Flamethrowers (great) and </span><span>Telex From Cuba (shamefully haven't read)</span><span> were finalists for the national book award, needless to say, the bar is set high. Set in a women's prison in California, the novel tells the story of a young mother, Romy Hall, who is serving two consecutive life sentences for murdering her stalker which may sound bleak but reviews ensure us that there is with and humour in the darkness. Out in the US but not available in the UK until June 8th, we’ve already put an order in at our local bookstore.</span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-to-london-craft-week</id>
    <published>2018-05-08T10:53:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:18:45+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-to-london-craft-week"/>
    <title>The Fit Guide to London Craft Week</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Where to go, what to see. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-fit-guide-to-london-craft-week">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>This May (9th - 13th) marks the fourth year of London Craft Week, a week dedicated to showcasing established and emerging makers, designers, brands and galleries from around the world. With over 200 events on the schedule, we created don't miss list to help you make the most of the week.</p>
<p> </p>
<h3><strong>Modern Prêt-à-Couture at Delpozo</strong></h3>
<p><span>Discover Maria Svarbova’s photography series, which inspired Delpozo’s Spring/Summer 2018 collection ‘Musicalia’. Visit the London flagship to see the atelier embroiderers at work and sit down for a conversation on art, fashion and craftsmanship between Maria and Caroline Issa, Fashion Director of Tank Magazine.</span></p>
<div class="street-block">
<p class="thoroughfare">7 pm, 9 May; 134 Sloane Street, London, SW1X 9AX, <a href="https://www.delpozo.com/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">delpozo.com</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefit_LCW-1-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555577553" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3 class="thoroughfare"><strong>Jochen Holz and Flow Gallery</strong></h3>
</div>
<p><span>Glass artist Jochen Holz discusses his solo exhibition Superficies at Flow Gallery. Holz explores the rarely practiced glassblowing technique of lampworking. His work focuses on the materiality of borosilicate glass, using a unique process to produce rich textures and complex shapes. Tea is served in Jochen Holz glassware.</span></p>
<p>10 May- 30 June; 1-5 Needham Road, W11 2RP; <a href="http://www.flowgallery.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="Nofollow nofollow noopener noreferrer">flowgallery.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3><strong>British Fashion Council Panel Discussion on the Craft of Sustainability</strong></h3>
<p><span>The BFC host a panel discussion on Sustainability, a pillar of their Positive Fashion initiative. Crafting Fashion through a Sustainable Lens with fashion designers Christopher Raeburn, Bethany Williams and founder of The Sustainable Angle, Nina Marenzi chaired by Frances Corner.</span></p>
<p>6 pm — 7 pm, 11 May; 20 Upper Ground, South Bank, London, SE1 9PD, <a href="http://britishfashioncouncil.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">britishfashioncouncil.com</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefit_londoncraft-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555577554" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3><strong>Beyond Surface at the G.F Smith Show Space</strong></h3>
<p>A gravity-defying installation by architect Kody Kato that demonstrates the properties of folding and strength using Takeo paper. Explore beautiful, innovative and technically-advanced papers from G . F Smith with creative partner Made Thought.</p>
<p>9 – 12 May; 27-28 Eastcastle Street, W1W 8DH; <a href="http://www.gfsmith.com/" target="_blank" rel="Nofollow nofollow noopener noreferrer">gfsmith.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="field date-row"><strong>The Conran Shop presents a Unique Tekio Light Installation</strong></h3>
<p><span>The Conran Shop welcomes the Global Market Exhibition to its Marylebone store: a curation of handcrafted products that showcase the finest in artisanal techniques. Undergoing an enlightening transformation by Santa &amp; Cole, The Conran Shop is the first UK retailer to unveil the paper Tekio Light, with a display of innovative illumination.</span></p>
<div class="street-block">
<p class="thoroughfare">9 - 13 May; 55 Marylebone High Street, London, W1U 5HS, <span><a href="https://www.conranshop.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">conranshop.co.uk</a></span></p>
</div>
<p> </p>
<h3><strong>The Flipside at Selfridges</strong></h3>
<p><span>The Flipside is a multisensory exhibition held by Selfridges in The Old Selfridges Hotel – a vast, one-of-a-kind location. The exhibition provides a thought-provoking journey into altered states of luxury, demonstrated by Google, Loewe, Mr Lyan, Thom Browne, Gareth Pugh, Louis Vuitton and Byredo.</span></p>
<p>Until 20 May; 1 Orchard Street, W1H 6JS; <a href="http://www.selfridges.com/GB/en/" target="_blank" rel="Nofollow nofollow noopener noreferrer">selfridges.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Visit  <a href="http://www.londoncraftweek.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">londoncraftweek.com</a> for the full program of events.</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-may-agenda</id>
    <published>2018-05-08T10:45:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:12:41+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-may-agenda"/>
    <title>Your May Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Where to Sweat, Watch, Eat and Do in London in May.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-may-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3>Sweat: Lift + Row, Core Collective</h3>
<p>Rowing is one of the best exercises for all-around body conditioning, take it from an ex-rower - best shape of my life. The problem is not many of us have access to a single skull or a body of water and while most gyms have indoor rowing machines, my gosh do they get tedious. Lucky then, that west London favourite, Core Collective has come up with the goods with Lift + Row, 55 minutes of high-intensity interval training that mixes indoor rowing intervals with weights and floor exercises. It's addictive (and sweaty).</p>
<p><span>Core Collective, 45 Phillimore Walk, Kensington, London W8 7RZ, <a href="https://core-collective.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">core-collective.co.uk</a></span></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thefit_mayagenda_large.jpg?v=1556017867" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3><span>Watch: On Chesil Beach </span></h3>
<p>Directed by first-time feature film director Dominic Cooke and adapted from Ian McEwan’s 2007 novel of the same name, On Chesil Beach follows a day in the life of a couple of virgin 20-somethings as they struggle to navigate the tricky circumstance that is their wedding night and the expectations that come with that time. Set in 1960s England, as the opening line of the book narrates, "they lived in a time when a conversation about sexual difficulties was plainly impossible." It's a story of unsaid things, young arrogance and naivety. The book sets high expectations, but with Sairose Ronan in a staring role, we're excited by this adaption.</p>
<p>Released 18th May, <a href="https://bleeckerstreetmedia.com/onchesilbeach" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">bleeckerstreetmedia.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3><span>Eat: Sapling</span></h3>
<p>Go for the sustainable, organic, biodynamic wines, stay for the richly curated, beautifully plated food byJohn Beeharry, formerly at Bistrotheque. The Jersey Royals with cheese curd, monk’s beard and pangritata are especially satisfying when washed down with Sommelier, Dan Whine's expert pairings.</p>
<p>378 Kingsland Rd, London E8 4AA, <a href="https://www.sapling-dalston.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">sapling-dalston.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3><span>Go: London Craft Week</span></h3>
<p>This May (9th - 13th) marks the fourth year of London Craft Week, a week dedicated to showcasing established and emerging makers, designers, brands and galleries from around the world. With over 200 events on the schedule, we created The Fit Guide to London Craft Week - a don't miss list to help you make the most of the week.</p>
<p>9 - 13 May; Across London, <a href="http://www.londoncraftweek.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">londoncraftweek.com</a></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/march-reads</id>
    <published>2018-03-13T09:16:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:20:20+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/march-reads"/>
    <title>March Reads</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Three books to while away the last days of winter.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/march-reads">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3>Complex <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/welcome-to-the-fit-magazine/">relationships</a> are at the heart of each of these female-penned reads.</h3>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<h3><strong>Everything I Know About Love, Dolly Alderton</strong></h3>
<p>An exceptionally honest <a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Everything-I-Know-About-Love/dp/0241322715?pd_rd_wg=1LDK9&amp;pd_rd_r=07256504-7772-48f5-83d1-3a2707a4c838&amp;pd_rd_w=jDQSc&amp;ref_=pd_gw_simh&amp;pf_rd_r=9FYPB8AA1M3KQ9CHSMRP&amp;pf_rd_p=deaa5746-571c-5b3b-8d1e-7cd67d79768f">memoir</a> about being a young woman in the world. Dolly Alderton captures the full experience of growing up and getting by with eloquence and piles of wit. She also has excellent taste in music.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/MARCH_READS_LUCASHUGH-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555575475" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </p>
<h3><strong>Little Fires Everywhere, Celeste Ng</strong></h3>
<p>Everyone is telling you to read this book, but it’s for a good reason. <a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Little-Fires-Everywhere-Times-Bestseller/dp/1408709716?pd_rd_wg=1LDK9&amp;pd_rd_r=07256504-7772-48f5-83d1-3a2707a4c838&amp;pd_rd_w=jDQSc&amp;ref_=pd_gw_simh&amp;pf_rd_r=9FYPB8AA1M3KQ9CHSMRP&amp;pf_rd_p=deaa5746-571c-5b3b-8d1e-7cd67d79768f">Little Fires Everywhere</a> is a deeply complex, dynamic read centred around the intensity of youth and complicated mother-daughter relationships. It's so enthralling in fact that new queen-of-female-fronted-television, Reese Witherspoon has teamed up with Kerry Washington to executive produce and star in a limited series adaption of the title.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<h3><strong>The Interestings, Meg Wolitzer</strong></h3>
<p>A book for long, slow nights by the fire, <a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Interestings-Meg-Wolitzer/dp/0099584093?pd_rd_wg=1LDK9&amp;pd_rd_r=07256504-7772-48f5-83d1-3a2707a4c838&amp;pd_rd_w=jDQSc&amp;ref_=pd_gw_simh&amp;pf_rd_r=9FYPB8AA1M3KQ9CHSMRP&amp;pf_rd_p=deaa5746-571c-5b3b-8d1e-7cd67d79768f">The Interestings</a> is a book who’s greatness creeps up on you. An absorbing read about youthful arrogance, uncomfortable realities and the unpredictability of life – this book will get you through the last few days of winter.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-march-agenda</id>
    <published>2018-03-06T09:26:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:19:49+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-march-agenda"/>
    <title>Your March Agenda</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Your March itinerary, made. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/your-march-agenda">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<h3> </h3>
<h3>Sweat: VersaClimber, BXR</h3>
<p>Is climbing the new spinning? BXR is offering Europe’s first ever climb-focused group-training concept, utilising the VersaClimber, a curious looking machine introduced in the 80s that is experiencing something of a comeback. Hardcore HIIT-sters will relish in the challenge that is BXRs HIIT CLIMB.</p>
<p><span>BXR, Chiltern Street, London W1U 5QY, </span><a href="https://bxrlondon.com/sweat-cardio.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">bxrlondon.com</a></p>
<h3><span>Watch: I, Tonya</span></h3>
<p>For Allison Janey’s whip-sharp portrayal of Tonya’s mother, Lavonia but also for a behind the headlines look at the almost unbelievable scandal that rocked the 90s.</p>
<p><span>Electric Cinema, </span>Shoreditch from March 2nd, Portobello from March 3rd, <a href="https://www.electriccinema.co.uk/programme#/list" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">electriccinema.co.uk</a></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_watch_eat_book-768x768_1_large.jpg?v=1555575918" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<h3><span>Eat: Ikoyi, St James</span></h3>
<p>This modern west African-inspired fusion restaurant opened quietly in July of last year. Headed by former Noma and Dinner chef Jeremy Chan and his childhood friend Iré Hassan-Odukale (who hails from the Ikoyi region of Lagos, Nigeria’s largest city) Ikoyi has since received stellar reviews. We’re making a reso right this second.</p>
<p><span>1 St James's Market, St. James's, London SW1Y 4AH, </span><a href="https://ikoyilondon.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">ikoyilondon.com</a></p>
<h3><span>Book: Picasso 1932 - Love, Fame, Tragedy, Tate Modern</span></h3>
<p>Dubbed Picasso's 'year of wonders' 1932 was evidently one of note for the artist. The first ever solo Picasso exhibition to held at Tate Modern will take us through this pivotal year, with more than 100 works will be exhibited, including the famous <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Le_R%C3%AAve_(Picasso)" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Le Rêve</a> (The Dream), the painting of Picasso’s young lover Marie-Thérèse Walter, never before on display in the UK.</p>
<p><span>From today - 9th September, n</span>ow taking bookings, <strong><a href="https://shop.tate.org.uk/ticket/date?cgid=6471" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">tate.org.uk</a> </strong></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
