<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/tagged/performance.atom"/>
  <title>LUCAS HUGH - The Fit Magazine</title>
  <updated>2021-10-11T11:53:15+01:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>LUCAS HUGH</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/work-out-like-a-warrior</id>
    <published>2021-04-30T12:29:07+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:06:31+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/work-out-like-a-warrior"/>
    <title>WONDER WOMEN WARRIOR</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Jenny Pacey Olympic athlete, Hollywood personal trainer and TV Gladiators 'Enigma' was featured wearing the Lucas Hugh Axis Set on the Front cover of this months Women's Fitness Magazine. In the feature Jenny, founder of <a href="http://www.paceandgo.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Pace &amp; Go" rel="noopener noreferrer">Pace &amp; Go</a>, talks about her journey to becoming the lead cast trainer on the Hollywood movie Wonder Woman 1984, what it was like training Kristen Wigg for her role and reveals the Amazon warrior's work out.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Make sure you grab your copy of </span><a href="https://womensfitness.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Women's Fitness Magazine link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Women's Fitness magazine</a><span> this month to see the full workout and article!</span></p>
<p> </p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Jenny_Pacey_cover_600x600.png?v=1619523098" alt="Jenny Pacey Front cover of Women's Fitness Magazine wearing Lucas Hugh Axis Set in Garnet"></div>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em>On the front cover Jenny is wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-sports-bra-garnet" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Sports Bra in Garnet" rel="noopener noreferrer">Axis Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-leggings-garnet" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Leggings Garnet" rel="noopener noreferrer">Axis Leggings</a> in Garnet.</em></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2021-04-27_at_12.25.43_600x600.png?v=1619522774" alt="Women's Fitness Magazine Warrior Work Out wearing Lucas Hugh"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2021-04-27_at_12.27.48_600x600.png?v=1619522906" alt="Jenny Pacey wearing Lucas Hugh Axis Set in Women's Health Warrior Workout"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2021-04-27_at_12.27.58_600x600.png?v=1619522956" alt="Jenny Pacey wearing Lucas Hugh Axis Set in Women's Health Warrior Workout"></div>
<p style="text-align: center;"><em> Above Jenny is wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-sports-bra-cobalt-blue" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Sports Bra in Cobalt Blue" rel="noopener noreferrer">Axis Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/axis-leggings-cobalt-blue" title="Lucas Hugh Axis Leggings in Cobalt Blue">Axis Leggings</a> in Cobalt Blue.</em></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jenny-wordsworth</id>
    <published>2021-02-12T11:00:50+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:07:36+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jenny-wordsworth"/>
    <title>High Performer: Jenny Wordsworth</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Last February we interviewed endurance sports athlete <a href="http://jennydavis.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Jenny Davis/ Wordsworth website link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jenny Wordsworth</a> who had just completed a gruelling 700 mile solo expedition to the South Pole. Here we share our interview with the corporate lawyer turned professional athlete on what motivates her. </p>
<hr><meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong>You have taken part in some amazing challenges, what experiences led you to leave the world of corporate law to become an elite athlete?</strong> </p>
<p>I've been fortunate to have worked for some excellent firms as my career in corporate law progressed, they were always so supportive of my extra curricular activities of mountaineering, ultra running and skiing. I think it was also of great interest to our clients and they'd usually support my expeditions in the form of sponsorship. I started doing well in ultra  running races (so races of 35miles and over), I took part in a 5 day race through the Dasht-e-Lut desert in Iran and after winning the race returned home to the offer of a pro contract. My boss tells me he knew it was coming, and within weeks I'd signed the contract and resigned from my role as in-house legal counsel. I do still work as a freelance lawyer, especially on projects I find interesting as I found I really missed it.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/A7_08841_480x480.jpg?v=1613035992" alt="Jenny Wordsworth in Antarctica" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></strong></p>
<p><strong>You encountered challenges whilst on your trip, how did you mentally stay strong to be able to push through the physical challenges?</strong></p>
<p>Suffering from a painful open ulcer reperfusion injury on my leg known as 'Polar Thigh' with about 150 miles to go from the South Pole was one of the hardest thing I have ever done. Months later I am still not sure how I was able to keep that mental strength and push on through that level of pain. Until that point I had been on track to break the world speed record but after that leg injury simply reaching the Pole felt like the biggest achievement of my life. I did need two surgeries and a skin graft the week I returned to London, but I'll wear the scars with pride. </p>
<p> What really keeps me going in an expedition is my 'why' - why am I here at all and why am I even attempting to do this in the first place. If your 'why' is genuine and strong enough, you'll get through the tough times. That isn't to say it's easy and this expedition was one of the hardest things I've ever done.</p>
<p><strong> </strong></p>
<p><strong>What advice would you give to those wanting to elevate their fitness routine and to those who are even considering taking on an extreme challenge? </strong></p>
<p>If you’re new to adventure it’s great to approach others with more experience and ask for help, just don’t forget that your unique background and experiences will bring something to the table that those experts won’t have thought of before. Don’t be so intimated by the experience of others that you forget or downplay your own ideas or approach. I mentor several women and it's the most enjoyable aspect of what I do - everyone is willing you on and only want to help you succeed, take advantage of that and get the help where you need it.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<blockquote>
<p><span>"What really keeps me going is my 'why' - If it's genuine and strong enough, you'll get through the tough times".</span><span> </span></p>
</blockquote>
<p><strong>What keeps you going and entertained during your challenges? i.e any podcasts etc.</strong></p>
<p>I mostly train without any form of external stimulus, especially for an expedition like the one in Antarctica. This was recommended to me by my coaches and it's also a great way to develop your mental strength. Imagine if your AirPods or iPhone stopped working halfway through your challenge, race or expedition? Then what? I don't like to become reliant on stimulus like that, just in case it isn't then available to me during the event itself. I probably do 80% of my training sessions with no music or podcasts, just focusing on the task at hand and entering into a form of flow state. </p>
<p> For the 44 day expedition in Antarctica though, I did save up podcasts featuring people I find inspirational and so the real treat was being able to listen to them whilst there. My friends also surprised me with a full length recording of The Odyssey by Homer! That kept me going for the whole trip as I'd listen to a small section each day.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What is next on your agenda? &amp; how do you decide on your challenges?</strong></p>
<p>I was due to be mountaineering in Nepal followed by a ten day mountain bike race through the mountains of Kyrgyzstan, those were both cancelled of course due to COVID-19. In the future I hope to complete an ocean row, precisely because I know absolutely nothing about ocean rowing and that's exactly what draws me to it. I also have a fear of the sea after a friend passed away at sea when I was younger, I'd like to face that fear and love the sea again. </p>
<p> For me the physical challenge is because I love finding out what my body is capable of, then the mental challenge is always where it gets most interesting and, importantly for me, it's an opportunity to visit parts of the planet I'd never normally set foot on.  </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/TNF_High_Res_480x480.jpg?v=1613036138" alt="Jenny Wordsworth in Antartica " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><span></span><br><strong>How do you take time for yourself and recuperate from training?</strong> </p>
<p>Sleep! Rest days and enough sleep are a life priority for me, although it took me years to really learn and respect that. The more I look after my body, the more I get out of it. I often get more than 9 hours sleep a night and I couldn't go without it. </p>
<p> </p>
<p><strong>What do you look for in your workout gear?</strong></p>
<p>High quality and design. I live in workout gear, day in and day out. It needs to last and it needs to look good, Lucas Hugh has been my go-to for years now as the pieces are simply beautiful, the cut is like no other and I've been unable to destroy any of it which given my training is quite something. They are just the most beautiful pieces and I'm in love.</p>
<p><br><strong>Any recommendations of places to work-out or that you love to refuel/ eat in London?</strong></p>
<p>I still love a good Barry's Bootcamp class, I remember when they first opened in London there wasn't anything like them in town and I love popping by for a seriously hard workout. Otherwise I love any of the group classes at KX in Chelsea, they have a great restaurant there too.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-future-of-wellness-2021</id>
    <published>2021-01-15T12:44:55+00:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:07:52+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-future-of-wellness-2021"/>
    <title>New for 2021</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>2020 has been an interesting year and many of us have had to find new ways to adapt and evolve in one way or another. At Lucas Hugh we're all about looking to the future, here's what we have got into for 2021. </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/COBALT_BLUE_AXIS_FRONT_WFH_l_480x480.jpg?v=1610119227" alt="Lucas Hugh Work Out From Home" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW ONLINE CLASSES</p>
<p>We are kick starting our year with Heartcore who offer a great range of classes from wake up and wind down to their signature Heartcore class designed to build strength and help you flow through your day. Their unlimited live-stream and on-demand pass has something to suit all schedules, with a new online platform coming soon. </p>
<p>Monthly access £55 a month | <a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" title="Link to Heartcore website">Weare</a><a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" target="_blank" title="Link to Heartcore website" rel="noopener noreferrer">heartcore.com</a><a href="https://weareheartcore.com/en-gb/at-home/" title="Link to Heartcore website"></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>JANUARY CLEANSE</p>
<p>Rebooting our systems after an indulgent holiday season with a Radiance Juice Cleanse. They offer a range of cleanse options delivered to your door with guidance and support pre and post cleanse. </p>
<p>Winter Cleanse from £65 | <a href="https://radiancecleanse.com/programmes/classic-cleanses/" target="_blank" title="Radiance Cleanse website" rel="noopener noreferrer">Radiancecleanse.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/a59e6e815efbf14f069b58a78225e333_3fd50abe-4f83-4df6-b6f8-93cc4d6dcd48_480x480.jpg?v=1610118118" alt="Eat Green" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW GREAT COOKBOOK</p>
<p>With more time spent in our home offices a great way to reconnect with family and loved ones at the end of the day is over a delicious healthy meal. Eat Green by Melissa Hemsley contains a variety of seasonal, sustainable flexitarian recipes to suit the whole family. </p>
<p>Eat Green by Melissa Hemsley | <a href="https://melissahemsley.com/eatgreen/" target="_blank" title="Eat Green Link" rel="noopener noreferrer">Melissahemsley.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW PODCAST</p>
<p>Our favourite investigative journalist took the podcast world by storm last year with Grounded. Now back for a second season we can expect to listen to Louis Theroux speak to high-profile people from a variety of backgrounds. We're enjoying his recent interview with Sia. </p>
<p>Listen now | <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p08ybsww" target="_blank" title="BBC Radio 4 Louis Theroux Grounded ep12. Sia" rel="noopener noreferrer">Grounded with Louis Theroux 12. Sia</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/About-Us-Homepage_copy_480x480.jpg?v=1610550508" alt="Black Tomato Villa" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CURATED ESCAPES</p>
<p>With so many travel restrictions last year many will be looking to find the perfect get away this year. Look no further than Black Tomato who are award winning creators of unique and tailored travel experiences and have a team of experts on hand to create your very own 'bubble' get away. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>Jetty, Joali Maldives</span> | <a href="https://www.blacktomato.com/" target="_blank" title="Black Tomato" rel="noopener noreferrer">Blacktomato.com</a></p>
<p>   </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LH-Sustainability-2600x1733-1_480x480.jpg?v=1607096722" alt="Lucas Hugh Sustainability Page Image" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>NEW LUCAS HUGH</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>We are driven to advance the future of activewear, and that means protecting our planet and making sustainable choices for our future world. Since launching in 2010, we have sourced premium Italian fabrics to ensure designs of the highest quality that last, </span>as well as producing in limited quantities to reduce excess. We select sustainable or recycled materials where possible, and from 2021 we plan to increase our use of these materials across all of our collections, with a focus on recycled yarns. As of 2020 all of our Technical Knit will be made with Q’NOVA recycled yarns – an environmentally-sustainable nylon fibre. </p>
<p>New collection launching soon. Follow us on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/lucashugh/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Instagram" rel="noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a> and sign up to our newsletter for exclusive access to the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/collections/new-in" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh New in page" rel="noopener noreferrer">latest drops</a>.</p>
<p>Treat yourself to some new Lucas Hugh | <a href="lucashugh.com/new-in">Lucashugh.com</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/august-art</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T16:30:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T16:30:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/august-art"/>
    <title>AUTUMN ART</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Autumn is upon us. Here's our round up of the best art exhibitions in the UK, as well as a new online class recommendation to boost your own creativity.</p>
<p>ANISH KAPOOR AT HOUGHTON HALL</p>
<p>One of the most influential sculptors still working today and well known for his adventurous take on modern sculpture. Featuring 24 sculpture and numerous other works by the artist, this exhibition is set across the beautiful grounds and within the house itself.</p>
<p>From now until 1st November, Houghton Hall, Norfolk, PE31 6TY | <a href="https://www.houghtonhall.com/art-and-exhibitions/anish-kapoor-at-houghton-hall/" target="_blank" title="Link to Anish Kapoor at Houghton Hall exhibition tickets." rel="noopener noreferrer">houghtonhall.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/03-Anish-Kapoor_large.jpg?v=1599651738" alt="Anish Kapoor Exhibition" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>ANDY WARHOL AT THE TATE MODERN</p>
<p>Iconic and instantly recognisable the Tate Modern has extended its retrospective Warhol exhibition till mid November. The exhibition features iconic pop works such as Marilyn Monroe and Campbell's soup cans as well as works never before seen in the UK. Alternatively, the Tate has also published online an exhibition guide for you to enjoy from the comfort of your home. </p>
<p>From now until 15th November, Tate Modern, Bankside, London, SE1 9TG | <a href="https://www.tate.org.uk/whats-on/tate-modern/exhibition/andy-warhol?gclid=EAIaIQobChMIi53Hifrb6wIVWeJ3Ch1YewlBEAAYASAAEgKxvPD_BwE" title="Andy Warhol at the Tate Modern">tate.org.uk</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ANDY_WARHOLE_large.jpg?v=1599652363" alt="Andy Warhol Exhibition image, Tate Modern. " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>BREATH IS INVISIBLE </p>
<p>A public art project in Notting Hill acknowledging the ability of art to say things we cannot express with words, addressing issues of inequality and injustice. The third instalment, opening on the 15th September, is featuring works from photographer and artist Joy Gregory, who will be exploring the narrative and origins of plants and their relationships with humans and ecology. </p>
<p>From now until 16th October, 236 Westbourne Grove, London, W11 2RH | <a href="https://breathisinvisible.com/" target="_blank" title="Breath is Invisible website" rel="noopener noreferrer">breathisinvisable.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>FEELING INSPIRED?</p>
<p>There is said to be a link between creativity and exercise. We recommend trying out Heartcore's newest online class 'The Heartcore Class' hosted by founder Jess Schuring. It's a great way to get your body moving, build your inner strength and get your creative thinking flowing. </p>
<p>Various dates and times available to book online | <a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Heartcore website" rel="noopener noreferrer">heartcore.co.uk</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Pilates-Stuido-in-Chelsea-Heartcore_large.jpg?v=1599658005" alt="Heartcore Studio Class" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/genius-design-transcends-time</id>
    <published>2020-09-09T16:23:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-09-09T16:31:36+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/genius-design-transcends-time"/>
    <title>PODCAST</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Anjhe Marcus, CO-CEO and Creative Director of Lucas Hugh, speaks to Andrea Alexa Smith about advanced technical fabric application and designing to enhance and envelop the female form.</p>
<p>Available on a variety of podcast apps &amp; online |<span> </span><a href="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1128056/5315833-anjhe-marcus-of-lucas-hugh-the-future-forward-visionary-behind-the-training-uniforms-for-the-hunger-games-catching-fire" target="_blank" title="Podcast Link to Genius Design Transcends Time, Anjhe Marcus of Lucas Hugh" rel="noopener noreferrer">Listen here</a></p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Lucas_Hugh13_large.jpg?v=1599649064" alt="Lucas Hugh Genius Design Transcends Time Podcast" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home</id>
    <published>2020-04-07T11:26:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2020-04-07T11:26:10+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home"/>
    <title>Workout at Home</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Lucas Hugh share the home workout's they are tuning into.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/workout-at-home">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>RELAX YOUR MIND</p>
<p>Re:Mind Studio is living streaming a range of their classes daily. A great way to calm the mind. View the timetable<span> </span><a href="https://remindstudio.com/timetable#/schedule/site/1" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Re:Mind Studio" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</p>
<p>£11 per session |<span> </span><a href="https://remindstudio.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, home workouts, remind studio" rel="noopener noreferrer">Re:mind studio</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/REMIND_STUDIO_b4d3d934-410c-45e0-8dff-9e9de60196d2_large.jpg?v=1585915157" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Re:Mind Studio " style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>IF YOU LIKE TO SWITCH UP YOUR CLASSES</p>
<p>Heartcore is offering up everything from Yin Yoga to HIIT, so matter what your feeling there is guaranteed to be a class to suit you. </p>
<p>Live Stream passes available from £5 | <a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Heartcore" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heartcore </a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-04-03_at_15.00.06_large.png?v=1585922631" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Heartcore" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>PERSONAL TRAINING</p>
<p>If personal training is your preference take advantage of Twenty Two Training's virtual consultation and training sessions, tailored to you. </p>
<p>A variety of block options available from £40 per session | <a href="https://twentytwotraining.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit magazine, Twenty Two Training, Home Workouts" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twenty Two Training</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/maxresdefault_large.jpg?v=1585920852" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home workouts, Twenty Two Training" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>EQUIPMENT AT THE READY</p>
<p>If you have a set of dumbbells (or even just bottles of water), a pilates ring, exercise band and resistant bands then you're ready to take on Epoch's <span>Online </span>Dynamic Mat Pilates Class. </p>
<p>Classes daily from £10 | <a href="https://epochfitness.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Workouts, Epoch Fitness" rel="noopener noreferrer">Epoch Fitness</a></p>
<p>THE STREAMING EXPERTS</p>
<p>Liz &amp; Clary from Hilliard Studio Method are no strangers to online classes and their online streaming service boasts over 3,000 minutes of video. Watch anytime, anywhere; perfect if you require a little more flexibility in your daily routine.</p>
<p>Subscribe from $20.38/ per month | <a href="https://stream.hilliardstudiomethod.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit magazine, Home workouts, Hilliard Studio Method" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hilliard Studio Method</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/hilliard2-770x513_large.jpg?v=1585921715" alt="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Fit Magazine, Home Work out, Hilliard Studio Method" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted</id>
    <published>2020-03-23T10:17:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2020-03-23T10:22:37+00:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted"/>
    <title>STAYING LIFTED</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lucas Hugh</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>The Lucas Hugh team shares a round up of how they are keeping spirits lifted this month.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/staying-lifted">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Some online resources for keeping spirits lifted this month from our team at Lucas Hugh. </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>LEARN: HIGHBROW</p>
<p>At Highbrow you can find dozens of topics<span> </span>to learn about such as personal growth, history and coding. Learning comes in the format of a short daily email, over the course of 10 days. </p>
<p>Offer a free 30-day trial or sign up from $10 a month |<span> </span><a href="https://gohighbrow.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The fit, blog, Highbrow, learning" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gohighbrow.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p>LISTEN: THE TONY ROBBINS PODCAST</p>
<p>Tony interviews some of the most successful people in the world, sharing their individual insights into what it means to be successful. We recommend 'Start small, think big, scale quickly'<em> </em>with SPANX founder Sara Blakely. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.tonyrobbins.com/podcasts/start-small-think-big-scale-quickly/" target="_blank" title="Sara Blakely, Tony Robbins, Spanx, lucas hugh, the fit, fit magazine" rel="noopener noreferrer">Listen here in conversation with Sara Blakely</a> | <a href="https://www.tonyrobbins.com/podcasts/" target="_blank" title="Tony Robbins, Podcast, Lucas Hugh," rel="noopener noreferrer">Tonyrobbins.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/FEATUREDQUOTE-1200X628-copy-550x288_large.jpg?v=1584958298" alt="Tony Robbins, Sara Blakely, Spanx founder, Podcast, Lucas Hugh The Fit Magazine"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>FOOD: GREEN KITCHEN STORIES</p>
<p>A vegetarian focused food blog with a vast range of nourishing and delicious looking recipes to choose from.  </p>
<p><a href="https://greenkitchenstories.com/" target="_blank" title="Food, blog, Lucas Hugh, Health, Wellness, Green Kitchen Stories" rel="noopener noreferrer">Greenkitchenstories.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Cauliflower_pasta_pesto_1-800x533-1_large.jpg?v=1584449750" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p> </p>
<p>HEALTH: CONTENT BEAUTY &amp; WELLBEING</p>
<p>This specially curated department store prides its self on finding the best natural, organic, sustainable products to enhance health &amp; wellbeing. Their website clearly talks through all certifications to help demystify the the wellness world. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.contentbeautywellbeing.com/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Content, Content beauty &amp; wellbeing, Health, wellbeing, " rel="noopener noreferrer">Contentbeautywellbeing.com</a> </p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen_Shot_2020-03-17_at_12.43.31_large.png?v=1584450286" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>EXERCISE: HEARTCORE</p>
<p>Workout Studio's may have had to temporarily close their doors however you can still enjoy your favourite studio's work out's from the comfort of your home. We are keeping an eye-out on Instagram for great tips from the team at Heartcore. </p>
<p><a href="https://www.heartcore.co.uk/" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh, The Fit, Heartcore, Workout, health, wellness, fitness" rel="noopener noreferrer">Heartcore.co.uk</a></p>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Tech_Knit_Leggings_Black_2204_large.jpg?v=1584451003" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;">Above Lauren is pictured wearing the <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-sports-bra-white" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit Sports Bra" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit Sports Bra</a> and <a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/products/technical-knit-7-8-leggings-black" target="_blank" title="Lucas Hugh Technical Knit 7/8 Leggings" rel="noopener noreferrer">Technical Knit 7/8 Leggings</a>. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-little-black-book-of-health-and-fitness</id>
    <published>2019-06-24T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2021-09-29T15:09:06+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-little-black-book-of-health-and-fitness"/>
    <title>The Little Black Book of Health and Fitness</title>
    <author>
      <name>D&amp;E</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>BEAUTY EDITOR </span><a href="https://www.lucashugh.com/meet-susannah-taylor/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">SUSANNAH TAYLOR</a><span> REVEALS THE WELLBEING EXPERTS WHO HELPED HER STAY ON TOP OF HER GAME. </span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/the-little-black-book-of-health-and-fitness">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>BEAUTY EDITOR SUSANNAH TAYLOR REVEALS THE WELLBEING EXPERTS WHO HELPED HER STAY ON TOP OF HER GAME. </p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>The boom in all things fitness and health in the last 5 years has meant a recent explosion of wellbeing ‘experts’. Thanks to social media, everyone can build a public profile now which is a wonderful empowering tool. However I would advise against taking every ‘expert’s’ word as Gospel – someone may have 100k followers, but their advice may not be 100% correct.</p>
<p>Thanks to my job, I have access to many wellness gurus, and below are the ones that I really trust, who have invaluable experience under their belts and whose advice and training is researched, thorough and relevant. Some may not have a huge following on social media, but that’s because a true pro isn’t about Instagram stats, flashing a six pack, or taking Belfies, it’s about knowledge, experience and how they translate it to you.</p>
<p>These people, in my opinion, know their stuff:</p>
<p> </p>
<p><span class="s1"><b>FITNESS</b></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Joslyn Thompson-Rule</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">A Nike Global Master Trainer for good reason - what Joslyn doesn’t know about fitness or fuelling for fitness isn’t worth knowing. Someone who puts her knowledge and integrity above creating ridiculous poses on Instagram, she is one of the most knowledgeable people I know in the fitness world. Creator of the Women in Fitness Summit which she hosted last year, her aim is to bring proper expert knowledge and advice to the wellness industry. A badass herself, she is a Crossfit competitor, strength coach, mama and all-around cool chick.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/joslynthompsonrule/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@Joslynthompsonrule</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><strong><span class="s1">Dalton Wong</span></strong></p>
<p class="p1">Dalton Wong started out his career in rehabilitation so he, therefore, understands the functioning and structure of the human body like no one else. A stickler for good form whilst exercising, he is often called upon by Hollywood stars, whipping them into shape for demanding roles with his calm, un-shouty manner.</p>
<p class="p3"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/dalton_wong22/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s2"><span class="s1">@dalton_wong22</span></span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s2"><a href="http://www.twentytwotraining.com"><span class="s3">www.twentytwotraining.com</span></a></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>David Kingsbury</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Lululemon ambassador David Kingsbury is an excellent personal trainer and Pilates specialist. A keen sportsman, David’s rugby career was struck by injury, but rehabilitation taught him the importance of a structured training regime and led him into the world of personal training (lucky us!). David’s approach is extremely thorough and his knowledge of the body, how to strengthen it and how to prevent or work with injury is exceptional. Today he works out of his studio near Notting Hill.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/dk_opus/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@dk_opus</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s2"><a href="http://www.opusfitness.co.uk"><span class="s3">www.opusfitness.co.uk</span></a></span></p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/LBB__1_large.jpg?v=1555428260" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"><br>FITNESS AND NUTRITION</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Louise Parker</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">I have personally witnessed the transformative effects of the Louise Parker Method with friends of mine that have done it. It uses a four pillar approach: Think Successfully, Eat Beautifully, Workout Intelligently and Live Well to get results. The go-to trainer for many a film star (and some say the Royal family) Louise has a real, common sense, no gimmicks approach to transforming your body and health and a deep understanding of the female body and the demands on us ladies (she has had three children herself). With trainers and nutritionists in-house that can liaise with you wherever you are in the world, she also has two books so you can learn about her method for a fraction of the price. The Louise Parker Method: Lean for Life and The Louise Parker Method: Lean for Life cookbook</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/louiseparkermethod/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@louiseparkermethod</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s4"><a href="http://www.louiseparker.com">www.louiseparker.com</a></span></p>
<p class="p1"><strong><span class="s1">James Duigan of Bodyism</span></strong></p>
<p class="p1">James Duigan is one of the best-known names in health and fitness. A gentle but clever man whose motto is ‘Be kind’, he and his Bodyism team place as much importance on positivity and your mindset as getting your body in shape. Having first arrived from Australia homeless and sleeping on London’s night buses, he has come a loooong way to the Bodyism home where he now resides in Notting Hill. James’ Clean and Lean books are, in my opinion, the original and still the best, simplest way to eat and exercise for good health.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/jamesduigan/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s2">@jamesduigan</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s4"><a href="http://www.bodyism.com">www.bodyism.com</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>NUTRITION</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Amelia Freer </b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Nutritional therapist Amelia Freer has a refreshing view on how we eat. Firmly anti-diet, she encourages people to nourish themselves, rather than restrict. Well known for Sam Smith’s makeover, Amelia is hugely knowledgeable about the human body and how eating the correct foods can change how we feel and function, working with other experts to test for dietary deficiencies as well as a psychotherapist who specialises in food-related issues if you need it. Above all Amelia loves fresh, nutritious food, straight from the ground (you should see her veggie patch!) to feed the body mind and soul and her books, Eat Nourish Glow, Cook Nourish Glow and Nourish &amp; Glow: the 10 Day plan all reflect that.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/ameliafreer/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@ameliafreer </span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="http://ameliafreer.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1"><span class="s3">amelia</span>freer.com</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>James Collins</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">James is a leading sport and exercise nutritionist and is President of the Royal Society of Medicine’s Food and Health Forum. Currently working as a consultant with European football, James also applies his knowledge of the sporting elite to non-athletes especially those of us with a fitness or health goal in mind. A regular columnist for the Telegraph, he speaks a lot of sense.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/jamescollinspn/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@jamescollinspn</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="http://jamescollinsnutrition.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">jamescollinsnutrition.com</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Anthony Warner – aka The Angry Chef</strong></p>
<p>Fed up of reading about nutrition from people in a g-string bikini or a pair of Speedos? The Angry Chef has your back. A chef for 25 years, the Angry Chef is not a nutritionist and nor does he pretend to be but he writes absolutely brilliant articles questioning the truth about peoples claims surrounding food. Things that make him angry: people making unscientific claims about the health benefits of diets, recipes and ingredients, people who present themselves as experts without the qualifications to back themselves up, and food manufacturers making false claims about their products etc. His hilarious, no bullsh*t writing is much needed in our ‘everyone is an expert’ age.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.angry-chef.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.angry-chef.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>YOGA</b></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Mercedes Sieff</b></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Mercedes is one of the UK’s leading Vinyasa Flow Yoga instructors and one half of the award-winning Yeotown Retreat and Yeotown Kitchen on London’s chic Chiltern Street. Teaching a popular weekly class at London’s Triyoga, her classes involve bold, creative sequencing, and encourages students to explore more contemporary, challenging asanas. A wise soul who is authentic in everything she does she is also a qualified positive psychology coach.</span></p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/mercedessieff/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@mercedessieff</span></a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.yeotown.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">yeotown.com</span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Tara Lee </b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Tara has been practising yoga for over 20 years, and if you know yoga, you’ll know that experience means a lot on the yoga mat. Specialising in Vinyasa Flow, pregnancy and postnatal yoga, Tara is also a teacher of teachers and runs intensive courses for teachers a few times a year. Teaching a dynamic form of yoga Tara is influenced by many styles including Ashtanga, Sivananda and Para yoga, and her students rave about a stronger, leaner, more flexible body as well as an increased sense of well-being as a result. I have found her postnatal DVD invaluable post birth.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/taraleeyoga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@taraleeyoga</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s2"> <a href="http://www.taraleeyoga.com"><span class="s3">www.taraleeyoga.com</span></a></span></p>
<p><strong>Tass Cambitzi</strong></p>
<p>If you think Yoga is all about lying on the floor taking a few easy stretches and a few deep breaths, then get yourself to Tass Cambitzi’s Power Yoga class at Triyoga in Shoreditch or Soho Farmhouse in Oxfordshire. In this tough Vinyasa Flow workout, Tass will challenge you way beyond your personal limitations. With a strong, precise flow of sun salutations, core work, inversions (she’ll have you attempting head and handstands in no time), Tass is a stickler for correct form and function, believing that building a stronger body will create a steady mind. One of the most exhilarating classes I have ever been to (all set to a great new soundtrack every time) it has become a highlight of my week and has done more for my body than any gym workout ever could.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/alignedwith/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@alignedwith</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.alignedwith.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.alignedwith.com</a></p>
<p><strong>Nicole Page-Croft</strong></p>
<p>There is a magnetic aura of worldly-wise spirituality that surrounds Oxfordshire-based Nicole. Originally from Australia but brought up in South-East Asia she has been practising yoga for 20 years and teaching for more than 12. With a degree from Oxford University and two Diplomas in Buddhist philosophy under her Yogi belt, she is adept at translating her learnings into practical teachings for modern life (I have been on Nicole’s retreats and we all hang on her every word). A fountain of knowledge in pre and postnatal yoga and birth, her book The Good Birth Companion is a must for expectant mothers and her Dynamic Flow class is playful, challenging and cleverly suits everyone from beginners to the very advanced.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.nicolecroftyoga.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.nicolecroftyoga.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3>PILATES</h3>
<p><strong>Chloe Hodgson</strong></p>
<p>Visit Soho Farmhouse in Oxfordshire on a Friday morning at 10.25, and you can expect to be mown down by a small army super chic, legging’d ladies all making a beeline for Chloe Hodgson’s 10.30amPilates class. Packed out every week, the Stott trained, steel-stomached Chloe delivers impeccably precise instructions guaranteed to strengthen nearly every muscle in your body. The results are a firmer bod and stronger core which will not only enhance your usual fitness regime (and create a tight, toned body) but will prevent injury and help bolster your body to bear the brunt of everyday life.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/chloespilates/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@chloespilates</a></p>
<p><a href="http://www.chloespilates.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">www.chloespilates.com</a></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>MEDITATION</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Jillian Lavender</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">If you want to learn how to meditate, forget the books and the apps, just speak to Jillian Lavender from the London Meditation Centre who is a total authority on the subject. Back in 1995 Jillian once had a job as the CEO of a publishing company so she knows what it’s like to live a manic lifestyle. Close to burnout, Jillian started meditating and felt her anxiety fall away, so she decided to train as a teacher. Having dedicated her life to teaching Vedic meditation (the oldest form there is), Jillian’s course will help you understand very clearly how to do meditation and what it can do for you. It’s the best 8 hours I ever spent.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.instagram.com/londonmeditationcentre/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@londonmeditationcentre</span></a></p>
<p class="p3"><span class="s4"><a href="http://www.londonmeditationcentre.com">www.londonmeditationcentre.com</a></span></p>
<p> </p>
<h3 class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>LIFE COACHING</b></span></h3>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><b>Jacqueline Hurst</b></span></p>
<p class="p1">Jacqueline will fix you. Having struggled in life when she was younger with drugs, alcohol, anorexia and anxiety, she went on a mission to change her mindset and in the process transformed her life. Today, as a life coach and hypnotherapist she sees clients with all manner of problems, from weight issues, eating/ body image issues, to addictions, and low confidence. Straight talking and to the point, she has an innate understanding of people and pour psyche and is on a life mission to help people turn their lives around. She rocks.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.instagram.com/jacqueline_hurst_/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">@jacqueline_hurst_ </span></a></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="http://www.jacquelinehurst.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s1">www.jacqualinehurst.com</span></a></p>
<p> </p>
<p>For more insight on health and beauty in London, follow <a href="http://www.instagram.com/susannahtaylor_" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@susannahtaylor_</a></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-ella-wroath</id>
    <published>2019-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-31T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-ella-wroath"/>
    <title>High Performer: Ella Wroath</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Founder of Soul Circus, the annual yoga and wellness festival based in the Cotswolds.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-ella-wroath">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Breezing in from France in floaty florals ahead of a pop-up event at Equinox Kensington, I couldn’t have foreseen the open-hearted insights <a href="https://www.soulcircus.yoga/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Soul Circus festival</a> founder Ella Wroath was about to share.</p>
<p>Moving to Cheltenham after a break-up, Ella spotted a gap in the market to build a community around hot yoga and so, along with her sister, she founded Ella and Fleur Hot Yoga.</p>
<p>From there, she and husband Roman went on to create Soul Circus three years ago, the first UK festival to fuse yoga and music now held annually in the Cotswolds.</p>
<p>Hearing the story of her journey to this point, I was struck by the bravery it took for Ella to go with her gut feeling and make some tough decisions, not least to run the first Soul Circus festival just 6 weeks after the birth of her first son.</p>
<p>How did it all start? Well, ‘I got sacked basically’, Ella confesses, ‘I got fired pretty much from everywhere because I couldn’t work for other people – I kept thinking what’s wrong with me? …It transpired that I needed to go and do my own thing’.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/EllaWroath_TheFit_large.jpg?v=1555423982" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Realising the need to find a career that made her happier, Ella discovered yoga. With a background in dance, yoga offered the balance she was seeking between an innate need for movement and the desire to help people; a deep-seated feeling she uncovered whilst working in a role in welfare.</p>
<p>Winding back further, the turning point for Ella was taking a job dancing in the parade at Disneyland Paris aged 18. A bold decision given that work relocation and travel was much less common amongst her peers at the time.</p>
<p>‘I got back from that and I thought – if I can just go to Paris and work at Disneyland, then I can go anywhere. That changed my mindset’ she says thoughtfully.</p>
<p>Ella went on to work a ski season in Europe, teach English in Japan and then move to London. ‘If an opportunity arises, I just go for it,’ she enthuses, ‘I like the unknown and there’s also that innate feeling that everything will always be alright’.</p>
<p>What drives her to keep facing new challenges? As the eldest of five siblings and now a mother of two, Ella wants to show her children ‘that you don’t have to be scared of things. You can be brave and positive and try new things because you’ll always be fine - watch mummy and daddy do ridiculous things and figure it out as we go!’</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/soulcircus_large.jpg?v=1555423980" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>‘The chance to try something new, to learn, to create something that’s never happened before’ gives Ella purpose. Watching Faithless DJ live during a yoga class at Soul Circus last year, Ella was struck by the special moment they had created finding joy in the excitement of their guests, and the thought that ‘this has never happened anywhere else in the world’.</p>
<p>Just as things began to feel comfortable in Cheltenham, last year Roman and Ella decided they needed a change and so moved to rural France. ‘We’re encouraged to grind, grind, grind and then retire, but by that point you’ve missed your entire life – so we decided we’d try to have mini-retirements along the way’.</p>
<p>Ella’s sense of courage and adventure is infectious; I have a feeling that whatever she goes on to do next, it certainly won’t be boring!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/running-well</id>
    <published>2019-05-23T11:18:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-23T11:18:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/running-well"/>
    <title>Running Well</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>How keeping a regular running schedule helps journalist Rosie Green.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/running-well">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Thud, thud, thud. I can feel the mud underfoot, the gentle mist on my face, the welcome sunlight on my skin.  I can feel the ache in my legs and the blood pounding in my ears. Running is when I am most connected to, and most in awe of, my body. </span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">The link between running and mental wellbeing has gone from hokey to hard fact. Research now shows physical activity 100% improves our mood. It certainly improves my relationship with myself. On, and after, a run I am charged with possibility.  I can write the novel, set up the business, deal with that deadline! Self-doubt is quashed, anxiety contained.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_running_thefit-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555577665" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">If I don’t run I’m generally cross with myself. I start berating myself for being lumpen and lazy. I feel less attractive. When I look in the mirror I am disappointed. It’s taken me a decade to realise that skipping one run doesn’t have any real effect on my appearance, but that self-dissatisfaction clouds how I view my reflection.  It would take longer than we have here to untangle all my self-esteem issues, but when the feel-good exercise hormones are circulating in my body, there’s little room left for any self-loathing. Put simply, if I run I like myself better. End of.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Running is the only time I really think deeply, where there’s enough space and silence for thoughts to fully form and evolve. I don’t run with music, I don’t want another person’s viewpoint to cloud my thoughts. Even when I think there is no time for a run, if I go, the world somehow keeps turning and I feel a million times brighter at the end of it.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Truth is, I’ve never regretted a run.  And how many things can you say that about?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Now, if you’ll excuse me…</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-mimi-xu</id>
    <published>2019-05-22T00:00:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-22T00:00:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-mimi-xu"/>
    <title>High Performer: Mimi Xu</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>"I get bored if I just do one thing – there are so many layers of things you can do in life."</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-mimi-xu">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p>Wide-eyed and effervescent, even before coffee, I’m immediately in awe of <a href="https://www.instagram.com/mimixumusic/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mimi Xu’s</a> passion and drive. DJ, producer, composer, artist - Mimi has become a respected name in fashion, music and art around the world.</p>
<p>During her teens, Mimi rejected her background in classical piano realizing that ‘it was about playing what you’ve been told to well’, but limits creativity. ‘Only later I realised I could use what I knew from before, but I needed to liberate myself from that to see it.’</p>
<p>Stepping into the unknown and seeing purpose with hindsight was a theme apparent in all we discussed.</p>
<p>Mimi stepped away from classical music and into fashion, later combining her passions for fashion, music and composition. She moved cities several times, curating shows for top designers around the globe, never knowing the outcome but always taking the leap. Does she ever get scared? ‘Not really. There are so many fears, but if you keep thinking about things you’d never do anything’</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/thefit_mimixu_profile-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555576702" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>There’s not a hint of self-importance to Mimi, she continually shifts the focus from herself to her work, lighting up as she discusses the purpose behind her projects.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>That’s the beauty of experimentation – start with a frame and see what comes.</p>
</blockquote>
<p>By her own admission, Mimi is a workaholic. ‘I get bored if I just do one thing – there are so many layers of things you can do in life you just have to be very organized’.</p>
<p>Mimi divides her time between commissioned work and creative projects. One such project is<a href="https://www.instagram.com/awkwardmoments_series/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Awkward Moments</a>; a mixed media series with the intention of ‘breaking barriers between audience and performers, getting people involved to feel what we feel’.</p>
<p>In the second instalment, much to her surprise, all 50 performers and guests ended up naked. She shared a story of a friend battling cancer who left having forgotten his anxiety with new-found body confidence. The whole group felt empowered. ‘I never thought I was capable of doing that’ she says, the excitement of the unknown spurring her on.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/mimi_xu_-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555576738" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>‘That’s the beauty of experimentation – start with a frame and see what comes… Art is not about certainty, that’s cinema, experimentation is what I like – living in the moment is what interests me in live performance’</p>
<p>For Mimi, success is not about being popular, ‘I’m not making mainstream work, it’s not for everyone’ she explains, ‘for me, success is about feeling I’ve pushed boundaries and made the next step.’</p>
<p>‘I think you have to see outside of the box even if you work a 9-5, do your own thing and make it interesting, otherwise, your life can pass by really fast.’</p>
<p>It’s clear that Mimi grasps opportunities with both hands, and enjoys every step of the journey.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-lady-emma-weymouth</id>
    <published>2019-04-17T11:31:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:24:07+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-lady-emma-weymouth"/>
    <title>High Performer: Lady Emma Weymouth</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>"You feel much more capable when you challenge yourself, you then realise how strong you are."</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-lady-emma-weymouth">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Within minutes we’ve discussed a manner of topics from hippos in the snow at Longleat, to walking in the recent D&amp;G show in Milan – such is the varied life that Lady Emma Weymouth leads. "It’s a full schedule, no question, but I like it," she says with a smile.</p>
<p>We’re speaking mid-blizzard, Emma snowed in at Longleat and me at home post-flu. She quickly offers her go-to ginger tea recipe, and it’s apparent that this generous spirit of sharing is from where many of her work ventures have stemmed.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefit_emmaweymouth1-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555500188" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Emma grew up baking with her mum. She became curious about nutrition in her teems through efforts to improve her skin and began sharing recipes as her passion for ingredients grew. She went on to present for the Food Network and developed her own <a href="http://emma-weymouth.com/." target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">platform</a>.</p>
<p>Her enjoyment of food is palpable, seeing food as central to wellness. It’s clearly central to her personal relationships too as she talks excitedly about baking carrot cakes for friends and cooking with her children.</p>
<p>Living by the tagline she coined over 10 years ago, Moderation, not Deprivation, Emma balances food with a healthy love of exercise.</p>
<p>Despite core muscle challenges post-partum needing continual focus, she’s proudly "fitter now than I have been in my entire life. Having a baby made me appreciate my body (so much more) in terms of what it can do".</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/llucashugh_thefit_emmaweymouth_3-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555500151" alt=""></p>
<p>Dedicating at least 30 minutes to training 6 times a week, from Tabata sessions to treadmill or barre classes, Emma feels that high-intensity training ‘gives you confidence and strength beyond just the gym. You feel much more capable when you challenge yourself, you then realise how strong you are… it makes you feel able to cope with everything else’.</p>
<p>Emma’s devotion to her passions is infectious. Giving credit to supportive relationships with her husband, mother, sister, children and teams at work; her generosity shines through like the love she puts into her home-cooked meals.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/balancing-act</id>
    <published>2019-04-16T15:03:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:25:11+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/balancing-act"/>
    <title>Balancing Act</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>In our 24-7, social-media-driven world, it can be hard to press pause. Bridget Arsenault connects with three incredibly diverse and accomplished women on how they balance it all.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/balancing-act">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>From one of America’s youngest-ever news anchors to an under 30 whose accessories line boasts an annual turnover of over £350,000 to the youngest-ever woman to sit on the board of a London Stock Exchange-listed company - Bridget Arsenault ascertains their tips for slowing down and decompressing.</p>
<hr>
<p>Launching her career as a news anchor at the age of 19, solidified <a href="https://www.instagram.com/navaghaliliwuorenma/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nava Ghalil</a>i as one of the youngest correspondents in the history of American television. Seeking more, Nava later created, produced and hosted her own human-interest series called Pay It Forward, for which she received an Emmy nomination.</p>
<p>I remember once having to swing open my car door, jump in and plough through waist-deep floods with a heavy beta video camera on my shoulder, alone as a new reporter in an unfamiliar town. I coped by throwing paralysing perfectionism and other people’s opinions in the trash. I reminded myself that I was there for a reason. What makes us doubt our abilities? If I am there, doing it, then it’s possible. Also, I try with all my might to find some element of joy in every task; I call it the “tactics of self-trickery”.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Nava-Ghalill_large.jpg?v=1555422106" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Since founding her eponymous accessories brand, <a href="https://www.instagram.com/elizabethscarlett/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Elizabeth Scarlett Elsey</a> has collaborated with the likes of Estée Lauder, Bobbi Brown and Livia's Kitchen. She’s sold over 10,000 products - including pillowcases, candles and beach bags - around the world and in 2017 became the first homeware brand to be stocked by ASOS. Elizabeth Scarlett launches in John Lewis this October.</p>
<p>Talking to an audience about my brand and what we do, whether that is at a business conference or speaking to a live audience on Sky News Business, I always have to push myself through the confidence barrier to communicate what I want to say effectively. But over time I’ve learned not to be frightened to promote what I do and stand up and talk about what I am passionate about, as it inspires others. I've learnt to go with the flow and take what each week throws at me with an open and logical mind. But to really relax, I love being at home, surrounded by all my comforts and hanging out with my husband. I light candles and incense, have a bath, and make a nutritious home-cooked meal. Or perhaps, I head to a spinning or HIIT class at Sweat Room. And I balance out the high-energy classes with a calming session at <a href="https://triyoga.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Triyoga</a> or a walk up Primrose Hill.</p>
<p><a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/research/stocks/private/person.asp?personId=264150809&amp;privcapId=37528715&amp;previousCapId=37528715&amp;previousTitle=S%20W%20Mitchell%20Capital%20LLP" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nadia Manzoor’s</a> appointment as Non-Executive Director at J. P. Morgan American Investment Trust in 2016 made her the youngest woman in history to sit on the board of a company listed on the London Stock Exchange. A Cambridge-educated lawyer, Nadia’s is also currently a partner at the boutique investment management firm S. W. Mitchell Capital.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/ES_NadiaManzoor_large.jpg?v=1555422118" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>My day-to-day includes everything from running pitches and raising assets to brand building and thinking about the how firm communicates with the outside world. (Everything from what our website looks like to investment thought-pieces.) But my toughest project by far is the relationship I have with myself. I’ve spent far too long in my life (not just my career) reflecting on negative remarks, worrying if what I did was good enough and generally over analysing. Of course, it’s important to be able to take criticism and learn from mistakes to become the best version of yourself, but it’s also important to be able to “let go of things that no longer serve you” - that’s a phrase I learned from yoga. Yoga and meditation have really helped me to find equanimity. Yoga isn’t about being able to touch your toes (I still can’t touch mine!), but for me, it’s a practice for my soul. Every time I leave a class I feel calmer, more focused and stronger.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/meet-michelle-kennedy</id>
    <published>2019-04-08T15:29:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:22:00+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/meet-michelle-kennedy"/>
    <title>Meet Michelle Kennedy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>The mother of the App world.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/meet-michelle-kennedy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/michellekennedylon/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Michelle Kennedy</a> is the CEO and co-founder of <a href="https://www.peanut-app.io/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Peanut</a>, an app that works to bring together like-minded mothers through connection and conversation. Dubbed the app for “women who missed out on Tinder” by The New York Times, since it's launch in 2017, Peanut has become a prominent voice for modern motherhood, garnering a community of over 300,000 women. We spoke with Michelle about her journey so far.</span></p>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_magazine_michellekennedy-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555511300" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p><span>WHERE DO YOU CALL HOME?</span></p>
<p>Hampstead, London</p>
<p>BEFORE LAUNCHING PEANUT, WHAT DID YOU DO?</p>
<p>I was Deputy CEO of Badoo, and board adviser and director for Bumble, so dating! Before that…I was an M&amp;A lawyer!</p>
<p>WHAT EXPERIENCES DROVE YOU TO LAUNCH PEANUT?</p>
<p>Peanut was born out of 2 main issues.</p>
<p>The first was the emotional aspect of becoming a mother. Before Fin arrived, I felt prepared. I had bought everything I needed, I'd read a few books. Turns out, the arrival of a baby isn't just about planning. There are feelings and demands that you can't plan for. My girlfriends weren't at the stage in their life where they were yet having children, and even if some of my wider friendship group were, we all lived in different parts of the city (and leaving the house to go anywhere further than 10 minutes from home with a newborn felt like a military operation). I suppose what I felt most prominently, which isn't particularly comfortable for a 30 something woman to admit, is that I was lonely. I had lots of friends, I was successful professionally, and yet, when I was at home, I felt lonely. This was further compounded by the fact that I was working in an industry (dating), where it was my day to day to produce products people could use to find a match or a date, and I was struggling to find a woman who was like-minded to go for a coffee with. A little like dating, I also experienced a lot of "I have to introduce you to my friend, she's a new mommy too", only to go through an awkward date where you realize the only thing you have in common is the fact that you both have a child. You don't share the same outlook on life, values, interests. That's actually even more isolating to be honest.</p>
<p>The second was my frustration with the existing products on the market aimed at Mothers. I didn't recognize the tone of voice the products used or the look and feel of the products. They felt outdated, old-fashioned, and in some cases patronizing. To me, I didn't feel like I'd suddenly aged, or become less modern, less cool, just because I'd become a mom, and yet, the products seemed to have that expectation. I found that confusing. I still had an expectation of great user experience, from products like Uber, or Instagram, but I wasn't getting that.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_magazine_peanutapp_michellekennedy-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555511328" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>WHAT ARE SOME OF THE CHALLENGES YOU'VE ENCOUNTERED ALONG THE WAY?</p>
<p>The stark reality is, 2% of venture-backed business last year were founded by women. 2%. And yet, we’re 50% of the population. It’s terrifying and frustrating in equal measure. Particularly because we KNOW businesses which are led by, or have senior women at the helm perform better. We KNOW therefore that women have a tremendous impact on business. Yes, I’ve encountered challenges. I’ve been asked whether I’ve wanted to do something “sexier” than an app for modern motherhood, or the ever-frustrating “you know, I’m not sure, I need to ask my wife/sister/daughter/niece/assistant”. That is infuriating. You want to scream, “no, you just need to look at the business, I am presenting you with a business proposal”. But, to say that is every VC is reductive. There are brilliant VCs out there, men and women, who are gender blind. Who are only interested in business opportunities, who are feminists. Do your research, take references from other founders, and you will find those people. I did. And the more conversations you have, the more successful your business is, the easier that will become. I spoke to an investor just today, who said: “Women never want to over promise and under deliver, and yet, I’ve never met a male founder who doesn’t overpromise, and yet, we know the guys are getting the funding”. Her point wasn’t too over promise, her point was, women have to be more confident. We must be, and we can be if we support each other.</p>
<p>HAS YOUR EXPERIENCE IN THE TECH WORLD CHANGED SINCE YOU LAUNCHED PEANUT?</p>
<p>I think we’re having more conversations around women in tech, which can only ever be a good thing. We’re focused on highlighting issues, whether that is the funding gap, right through to inappropriate behaviour/power imbalance. There are incredible women who are supporting female founders and having “Women’s hour” drop-ins. There are women in tech initiatives in the workplace. The more we have conversations about women in tech, women in any industry where they are a minority, the easier women in the future will find it to enter these industries. That is the key.</p>
<p>WHAT ADVICE WOULD YOU GIVE TO WOMEN STARTING OUT IN THE TECH INDUSTRY?</p>
<p>Be at peace with failure. Failure is good. It’s how you get to the correct answer, it’s how we all improve. Be tenacious in your research to understand every area you want to be involved in. Seek out mentorship, approach people you admire and don’t be afraid to ask for their help-what is the very worst that can happen?! They say no! No big deal, on to the next. When you connect with people who are helpful, inspiring, kind, keep in contact with those people. You never know when you will need their help again in the future. Test every new product which is interesting to you. Work out why you like it, why you don’t. Watch people. What are they using, how, why? Go for it, you might just build something which changes someone’s life. How cool is that?</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_magazine_peanutapp-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555511330" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>DO YOU BELIEVE IN WORK/LIFE BALNCE?</p>
<p>NO! It’s a myth! There is no such thing as balance. We juggle. Sometimes we’re brilliant at work, sometimes we’re brilliant at home life, sometimes, very rarely on the same days, do these collide. If we tell women there is a balance, and they don’t have one, they feel they are failing, and that, is fundamentally wrong.</p>
<p>WHAT KEEPS YOU GOING?</p>
<p>My son. My desire for him to see how hard mommy works, what you can achieve from hard work, that if you see a problem, you can be the one to fix it. It might not be easy, but you can. I want him always to question things in the world, particularly if there are things which aren’t right.</p>
<p>WHAT'S NEXT FOR PEANUT? HOW DO YOU CONTINUE TO BUILD A COMMUNITY THAT'S EMPOWERING?</p>
<p>More growth! More features! I continue to spend countless hours speaking to the women who use Peanut. To understand what they want. I continue to spend time using other products too. What works? What doesn’t work? Why? Is there something there which Peanut can help with or develop? Problem-solving I suppose, that’s how.</p>
<p>HOW DO YOU DEFINE SUCCESS?</p>
<p> </p>
<p>Peanut becoming synonymous with Modern Motherhood. Just that little thing.</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/mirror-mirror</id>
    <published>2019-04-01T13:32:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:22:20+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/mirror-mirror"/>
    <title>Mirror Mirror</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Francesca White discusses how an emerging attitude to fitness is reshaping our minds as well as our bodies.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/mirror-mirror">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>BY FRANCESCA WHITE</p>
<p>Whether it’s barre or boxing that has you swapping your weekend lie-in for a fitness blast, there’s no denying the effects of a good workout. But it’s not just our bodies that are being reshaped – it’s our minds.</p>
<p>Cardio raises your heart rate – cue oxygen, and lots of it, ricocheting around your body. As a result, we push harder. Weight-based workouts create microscopic tears in our muscles, forcing our body to release reparative proteins. The result is denser muscles and improved strength.</p>
<p>But whether you’re rowing or downward-dogging, the psychological effects of exercise are always the same: a rush of endorphins, which leaves you sky-high. Add to this the mindfulness element that many gyms promote (yogic postures, meditation, a final “Shavasana”) – and whereas once we were crawling out of the gym sweaty and exhausted, we’re now walking out feeling taller, mentally and physically.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_vestige_technicalknit-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555504176" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>The mood-boosting music (Psycle), eucalyptus-scented towels (Equinox) and motivational mantras (Bodyism) help. But these are more than the trappings of a burgeoning, boutique fitness industry. They feed into our self-esteem - and with 36% of young adults in possession of a gym membership, their effect, though subconscious, is widespread.</p>
<p>What’s more, our bodies are becoming stronger. Resistance-based workouts are on the rise, and the discipline required to hoist a 20kg barbell brings new focus to gym sessions, where once we would simply sit on an exercise bike for half an hour. Gone, too, are the days where we would stumble into the gym in an old t-shirt. Today’s gear is <a href="https://lucashugh.com/collections/bonded-performance" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">high-performance stuff</a> designed to shape waists, sculpt bottoms and lengthen legs (also useful when it’s being worn for the rest of the weekend).</p>
<p>The combination of a strong body and a strong mind is a powerful one. Hopefully, that’s what we all see when we look in the mirror today.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lcuashugh_aircuttank-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555504220" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-laura-weir</id>
    <published>2019-03-11T00:44:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:27:29+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-laura-weir"/>
    <title>High Performer: Laura Weir</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p style="text-align: center;">Editor of Evening Standard Magazine Laura Weir shared insights on her career, creative approach and the art of comfort with contributor Vicky Ellison.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-laura-weir">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p>Accompanying the interview are select illustrations by Rose Electra Harris who created the illustrated for Laura’s book Cosy: The British Art of Comfort.</p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Laura-Weir-768x1151_grande.jpg?v=1552790783" style="float: none;"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<p>YOU’VE WORKED YOUR WAY INTO SOME INCREDIBLE ROLES – CAN YOU TELL US HOW YOU FIRST GOT STARTED? WAS JOURNALISM ALWAYS THE PLAN?</p>
<p class="text-indent">I am very lucky that it was always the plan, other than dreaming of becoming a vet as a teen, being a journalist after my work experience at the Guardian aged 16 gave me the bug; I was intoxicated by the taste of adrenaline, the thrill of a news room and the power of print. Not to mention the camaraderie between the colleagues that I saw, and the variety of things that these journalists tackled every day, from press conferences to court reports and beyond.</p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span class="s3"><b><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen-Shot-2019-03-04-at-14.35.14_grande.png?v=1552791005" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto; float: none;"></b></span></p>
<p>  </p>
<p><span>WERE THERE EVER MOMENTS OF DOUBT AS YOU WENT FOR NEW ROLES? AND IF SO, HOW DID YOU OVERCOME THEM?<br></span></p>
<p><span>I have been incredibly lucky to be head hunted or poached for all of the more senior jobs I have been given. I [know] that this is rare and not the experience of most. I have had doubt in other parts of my career, and my day to day experience is full of them! I tend to rely on my gut, I have a strong instinct that has only failed me a handful of times since I started working aged 23. I appreciate and value the counsel of others; there are a few people in my professional circle who I look to for guidance and sense checking on creative visions or judgement from time to time. I think not being reluctant to ask for advice is important; getting rid of the idea that you have to ‘own’ your ideas, success and creativity in its totality in order to get credit. The best way to achieve the optimum outcome of any project is to surround yourself with talented people.<br><br>WHAT DO YOU ENJOY MOST ABOUT YOUR CURRENT ROLE AND WHAT ARE THE BIGGEST CHALLENGES?<br></span></p>
<p><span>I love the magazine, and I love my job. I truly believe that London deserves an outstanding, extraordinary magazine and I feel proud that we deliver that every week. I value the fact it is free, it’s essentially a bit of a gift and there’s no reason it shouldn’t be as interesting or beautiful as the magazines or content people pay for. My team are the best in the business, they are clever, sensitive, bright, talented and tenacious, every single one of them. I enjoy working with people who are really good at what they do, and I have that pleasure every day. I enjoy the creative freedom that I have at the magazine, my bosses trust me and I never take that for granted. The challenge is making sure that each issue is better than the last, which when creating a magazine each week is a tough bar to set, but thinking I have to top it each week is what drives me on to create the best product we can, one that’s both commercially and editorially at the top of its game.<br><br>YOU HAVE REALLY CAPTURED A LONDONERS VOICE THROUGH ES MAGAZINE – WAS THAT A DIFFICULT THING TO DO?<br></span></p>
<p><span>I make a magazine that I want to read, which sounds like a bizarre approach, but I think I relate to lots of Londoner’s. I’m born and bred in this city, I work hard, I have frustrations with the capital and a deep love for the place. I want to understand people in the public eye and get to know strangers. I want to know what’s going on, I want to feel informed, to feel inspired. I want to feel transported to somewhere else at the end of a busy week, and I want to read witty copy and to feel surprised by the content. That’s the recipe!</span></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucas-hugh-the-fit-laura-weir-high-performer_grande.png?v=1552791199" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s3">HOW DO YOU APPROACH RUNNING THE TEAM AND EMPOWERING TEAM MEMBERS BOTH INDIVIDUALLY AND AS A COLLECTIVE?<br></span></p>
<p class="p1">It is challenging catering for individual personalities and their needs, especially in a busy high-pressured environment, but I think the key is to try and play to the individual’s strengths. Remember you’re only human and that the most important thing is that people know they need to take care of themselves because none of us are any use if we are burnt out. Remember you’re only human and that the most important thing is that people know they need to take care of themselves because none of us are any use if we are burnt out.</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><br></span><span class="s3">WHERE DOES THE INSPIRATION COME FROM FOR THE COLUMNS YOU WRITE AND FEATURES YOU INCLUDE?<br></span></p>
<p class="p1">I read the weekend papers, listen to what my friends are talking about, bookmark articles and Instagram posts, listen to what my gut is telling me and take notice of ideas that strike – try and write them down no matter how small because small gripes can become good columns!</p>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1"><br></span><span class="s3">AS A TRUE LONDON TASTEMAKER – CAN YOU SHARE ANY TOP PICKS FOR RESTAURANTS, SHOPS AND PLACES TO SPEND TIME IN THE CAPITAL?<br></span></p>
<p class="p2">I love<span> </span><a href="http://www.lemercury.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">Le Mercury</span></a><span> </span>on Upper street as an old classic,<span> </span><a href="https://www.quovadissoho.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">Quo Vadis</span></a><span> </span>has a special place in my heart, I am a Soho girl through and through. I used to love the stockpot but that’s closed now. China Town for noodles,<span> </span><a href="http://www.rivarestaurants.com/riva/menus.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">Riva</span></a><span> </span>in Barnes for good memories of a loved one.<span> </span><a href="https://brunswickhouse.london/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">Brunswick House</span></a><span> </span>so I can buy some stuff for my house on the side, I could go on…</p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Screen-Shot-2019-03-04-at-14.40.17_grande.png?v=1552791303" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">IF YOU GET ANY DOWNTIME, WHAT’S YOUR FAVOURITE WAY TO RECHARGE?<br></span></p>
<p class="p1">A long hot bath with oils and candles. I love<span> </span><a href="https://trudon.com/eu_en/home-fragrances/candles.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">Cire Trudon</span></a><span> </span>candles, Votary oils,<span> </span><a href="https://www.aromatherapyassociates.com/bath-shower-oils.html" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">Aromatherapy Associates oils</span></a>, there are so many brands I love!</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><br></span><span class="s3">IF READERS ASPIRE TO WORK IN A ROLE LIKE YOURS – WHAT ADVICE WOULD YOU GIVE THEM?<br></span></p>
<p class="p1">Take good care of yourself – your body, mind and spirit; you’re all you’ve got.</p>
<p><span class="s1"><br></span><span class="s3">WHAT INSPIRED YOU TO WRITE COSY?<br></span></p>
<p>A column that I wrote about the joy of being cosy sparked the idea, it’s always been a real cornerstone of my life and the idea of an ode to tucking in and softening life’s edges when my day to day is so hectic really appealed!</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><br></span><span class="s3">CAN YOU SHARE ANY TIPS/EXCERPTS FROM THE BOOK?<br></span></p>
<p class="p1">My favourite is the chapter on cosy holidays, the walks and secret spots recommended by the National Trust.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucas-hugh-rose-electra-harris-illustration-the-fit-laura-weir_grande.png?v=1552791388" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><span>To hear more from Laura follow her on Instagram </span><a href="http://instagram.com/laura_weir" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">@laura_weir</span></a><span> or learn more about her book Cosy: The British Art of Comfort </span><a href="https://www.amazon.co.uk/Cosy-British-Comfort-Laura-Weir-ebook/dp/B07HFC5PK6" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span class="s4">here</span></a><span>. To enjoy more of Rose Electra Harris’ beautiful illustrations follow </span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/roseelectraharris/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@roseelectraharris</a><span>. </span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jo-ellison</id>
    <published>2019-02-14T09:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:25:59+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jo-ellison"/>
    <title>High Performer: Jo Ellison</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;"><em>Contributor Vicky Ellison sat down with Financial Times fashion editor Jo Ellison to discuss her career journey, sharing insight on the role of an editor, dressing for fashion week and the power of persistence</em>.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-jo-ellison">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Jo Ellison - Lucas Hugh - THE FIT" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/JO-ELLISON_LUCAS-HUGH-_THE-FIT.jpeg?v=1550434261" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Preparing to meet Jo Ellison, fashion editor at the <a href="https://www.ft.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Financial Times</a> and former features director at Vogue, many questions came to mind – what to ask someone who’s interviewed global A-List talent? What to wear to meet one of London’s most fashion savvy editors?</p>
<p>Thankfully Jo’s down-to-earth humility and the fact that we spoke on the phone allayed all fears. We quickly got to chatting about her career path.</p>
<p>A move to Ireland saw Jo unexpectedly take her first steps into journalism. With a degree in history and no journalistic experience, London had felt like a ‘closed shop’ while Ireland presented an opportunity with a national paper ‘so I trained through from the bottom up doing night shifts on the subs desk [moving into features] and learning the ropes as I worked,’ Jo explained.</p>
<p>Relocating to London, Jo stepped into the role of Features Editor at The Independent, before moving on to Vogue and now the FT. With such an impressive career path I was surprised to hear that Jo, like many of us, still has moments of uncertainty.</p>
<p>‘I think there’s always a little bit of that fear… the feeling that I’m slightly unqualified to do this as a journalist – because I think we’re generalists, that’s the whole point. We try and explain things to people that they may not have heard of or may not understand, and you’re just trying to filter it through a kind of prism of language that makes it understandable to someone that doesn’t know anything about it; so our job is sort of a little bit like a translator, that’s how I like to think of it.’</p>
<p>No two days are the same in Jo’s world, she shares with refreshing honesty, ‘obviously you’re learning all the time, but your brain is going in 5000 different directions, I’m writing a piece today that’s making me feel sick.’</p>
<p>The variety and opportunity to meet incredible people motivate Jo in her ‘all-encompassing job’. ‘I’ve got quite a low boredom threshold, so I love the idea that I can get up, get something done and finish it and that’s it, it’s off the plate – I’m quite a deadline-oriented person, so I like that.’</p>
<p>The hardest part is dealing with feedback, ‘you get a lot of comments and reactions…you’re accountable for everything you write and that can be very wearing’ Jo explains, ‘you’re a voice out there and sometimes that can be a bit overwhelming.’</p>
<p>I’m curious how a fashion editor packs for the relentless schedule of global fashion weeks. ‘It’s a bit of a weird one,’ Jo discloses ‘I think about it for ages before I go and I bring all of these clothes…and then of course by day 3 …you haven’t slept, you’re trying to write 1800 words on different subjects every day and all you can think about is where are my jeans and a t-shirt?’</p>
<p>‘Some people are amazing at it, they plan for what they want to wear and they wear it, but I’m the sort of person who wakes up in the morning and although I thought about what I wanted to wear the night before, invariably it’s like no I don’t want to wear that at all, I want to wear this – so it’s quite difficult to predict.”</p>
<p> </p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Jo Ellison - Lucas Hugh - THE FIT" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/JO-ELLISON_LUCAS-HUGH_THE-FIT_2-1-768x1020.jpeg?v=1550432098" style="float: none;"></div>
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Photo by Rokas Darulis, Jason lloyd Evans</span></h5>
<p> </p>
<p>I had to ask about Jo’s go-to designers and outfits. A well-known Celine fan and lover of tailoring, Jo explains that having suits made is an ‘expensive new habit… I don’t have a go to designer as such, but I sort of have go to outfits, which is a blazer and pair of trousers usually.’</p>
<p>When it comes to recharging, like many of the high performers I’ve spoken to, Jo loves to walk outdoors, ‘We got a dog about 7 years ago, and walking the dog makes me so much more aware of the seasons. I think you learn to appreciate your environment and look around you a bit more, so that’s been a good thing.’</p>
<p>I ask how she manages a busy work and family life, Jo responds that ‘I just think it’s all a bit of a nightmare really, I can’t even pretend to have an answer to it all, if anyone has one let me know!’</p>
<p>We finished our chat touching on advice for anyone striving for a career like Jo’s; ‘I think the most important thing is just to listen and ask lots of questions but make sure you listen to the answers’ she says, ‘do a lot of reading around something and be as prepared as you can.’</p>
<p>‘In terms of getting into the fashion industry, I think you’ve just got to be really persistent…don’t give up after the first email, make sure you go back and follow up. [Don’t be annoying, but] don’t assume things will happen, you have to bring something to the table. I think persistence is a hugely important factor in getting your foot in the door.’</p>
<p>For more fashion and business insights follow Jo on Instagram <a href="https://www.instagram.com/jellison22/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@joellison22</a></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-lorraine-pasccale</id>
    <published>2019-01-30T09:58:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:25:49+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-lorraine-pasccale"/>
    <title>High Performer: Lorraine Pascale</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p style="text-align: center;">Acclaimed culinary author and TV host, Lorraine Pascale shares her career journey and speaks to the importance of mental health both personally and as the subject her upcoming book.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-lorraine-pasccale">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p>Perhaps best known as a model, celebrity chef and author, Lorraine Pascale has had numerous careers including hypnotherapy and car mechanics, in addition to a host of charity work. However, this year will see her move into a new area – wellness.</p>
<p>I was curious to hear what has sparked Lorraine’s various career changes; ‘I’ve always gone with my gut’ she explains, ‘so if I’m doing something and it doesn’t feel right, I always look to change it. It’s important for me to do things that I’m passionate about and that have a purpose. Modelling was good when I was younger, and then I really wanted to be in London more so I found a course I liked and that happened to be baking. Now I’m getting into wellness and writing my 8<sup>th</sup> book which is not a cookery book so that’s quite exciting.’</p>
<p>Undoubtedly there have been naysayers, but Lorraine has risen above any negativity to forge ahead along her path. ‘People have told me along the way – be it well-meaning friends or other people, to manage my expectations, but normally when people do that it’s a reflection of what’s going on inside them, their limitations coming out. It can knock your confidence, but you just have to have positive people around you that keep you up and keep you going, so you’ve just got to ignore them.’</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lorraine.pascale_large.png?v=1554972952" alt="Lorraine Pascale, culinary author and tv host interview with lucas hugh" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Often easier said than done, we discussed how Lorraine deals with negativity from others, especially in such a social media focused world, ‘I think there’s a sort of arch from being immature to hopefully being mature, although that doesn’t always go with age’ Lorraine muses, ‘from blaming [others] and thinking everything else is at fault, to being accountable for yourself. When you’re younger maybe you need to be fixed and you look outside for answers, and then there comes a time for some people that you realise it’s all up to you. So I do a lot of positive self-talk, I do therapy, the gym is a big type of therapy for me as well, [as is] cooking, and really only having a small circle of friends around me that I can 100% trust and feel safe and encouraged by.'</p>
<p>Sharing a sneak peek into the focus of her new book, Lorraine shares ‘it’s all about mental health being a good word, a word we should all use, being open and honest about how we’re feeling because I don’t think there’s a single person on the planet who hasn’t had a bad day, or bad half day at least… the problem is when [mental health is] mentioned people think of being sectioned… and that does happen with some people but there’s a whole spectrum under mental health. There are so many days lost to depression and most people probably don’t say that when they’re ringing in because it’s frowned upon. You can say that your arm hurts but you can’t say that you’re in pain in your head, so I find it a bit strange, but hopefully I can start to make a difference with that.’</p>
<p>Refreshingly down to earth in her approach, Lorraine admits that on her bad days she’s more likely to order Deliveroo than cook or go for a walk along the water to recharge.</p>
<p>I’m inspired by her drive to use her position to help others. ‘I think it’s rude not to, if you’re given a platform and you can influence a lot of people then it’s part of the duty to do that.’ I’ve no doubt her new book will be another bestseller.</p>
<p>_</p>
<p>Discover more about Lorraine through her recipes, workouts and motivational quotes <span><a href="https://www.instagram.com/lorrainepascale/?hl=en" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">@lorrainepascale</a>.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kate-bosomworth</id>
    <published>2018-12-12T10:15:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:28:28+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kate-bosomworth"/>
    <title>High Performer: Kate Bosomworth</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>“I have also learnt that it’s good for the soul to have a go at something else, and not be afraid of that skills transfer moment, because life’s really short, and in order to keep that level of energy and motivation you have to keep being hungry"</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kate-bosomworth">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p>As we talked through Kate’s career path, I realised how rare it is to hear a successful woman speak proudly of her skills and achievements.</p>
<p>Kate Bosomworth has every right to be proud. As CMO of M&amp;C Saatchi- one of the world’s most successful advertising agencies, Kate’s journey has seen her create, grow and sell her own successful PR agency, be invited onto the board of Sport England and launch one of the UK’s best known campaigns – ‘This Girl Can’, among numerous other achievements.</p>
<p>It struck me that Kate’s career has involved many of her own personal “this girl can moments”, each one spurring her on to the next move…</p>
<p>Starting her career in sales, she went from client to agency side early on and was asked by the experiential agency to move to London and set up a new office.</p>
<p>Despite a lack of experience, Kate said yes. <em>“That was my first winging it moment. I came to London with this slight fake it till you make it approach. I found an office, hired a team, rented photocopiers and thought well, that wasn’t that hard was it?”</em></p>
<p> </p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img alt="kate bosomworth interview with lucas hugh " src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Kate_Bosomworth_2_large.png?v=1554974006" style="float: none;"></div>
<h5 style="text-align: center;"></h5>
<p> </p>
<p>From there, Kate took an unexpected step into PR. Invited into the role by an agency she had hired, Kate’s initial skepticism subsided when she sold in her first piece of coverage to The Telegraph during a trial week. “<em>That feeling of opening a newspaper and thinking I made that- it was the thrill of selling again. The thrill you get from speaking live on stage, it’s amazing. So, I literally jacked in my job at the [experiential] agency and went to work in PR.”</em></p>
<p>After two years with the PR agency, Kate felt she needed a change. Her attention was captured by a newspaper advert for the toughest yacht race in the world.</p>
<p>While many would shy away from such a challenge Kate faced it head on.<em> “I kind of fancied myself as being tough, I used to sail as a kid so I [figured] how hard could it be. I applied and managed to ‘blag’ my way onto the race really late.”</em></p>
<blockquote>“I learnt loads about myself on that race,” she reflects “I learnt my appetite for risk is quite high. I had a frightening moment on the boat [where I thought I might die] – so I came off the yacht thinking ok, well if I can do that I can do anything.”</blockquote>
<p>Returning to London and noticing a gap in the market for a knowledgeable, dedicated sports PR agency at a time when mass participation events were taking off, Kate set up KTB. Before long, their client roster included GSK, Technogym, Adidas and the Flora running event portfolio.</p>
<p>Fast forward a few years and Kate had sold her agency twice with a sell-to-grow strategy, as well as having two children. Being invited onto the board of Sport England shortly before the second sale of her agency was, unbeknownst to Kate at the time, the next step in a new direction.</p>
<blockquote>“I discovered that I had a real [passion] to work on Sports participation for women. I had worked in the women’s space for a long time through the agency but had not really gone beyond brand”.</blockquote>
<p>Launching the globally recognised campaign This Girl Can’ was a pivotal moment. “<em>The success of ‘This Girl Can’ in 2015 was probably, without me realising, the start of the “I can do something else and I’m really good at this” [feeling]. I’m really good at understanding behavior – it almost revealed some stuff about me that I didn’t know.”</em></p>
<p>Not long after that, Kate left her own agency, took a year out completing work with UEFA and Landrover, and then joined M&amp;C Saatchi at the start of 2018.</p>
<p><em>“My career [has had] a number of zig zags”</em> Kate muses. “<em>That was interesting, now I’m going to try over here, that was interesting, now I’m going to go here. I am a very high energy person and I like working at a certain level of energy and intensity, so I suppose when I don’t have that anymore I really seek it somewhere else.”</em></p>
<p><em>“I have also learnt that it’s good for the soul to have a go at something else, and not be afraid of that skills transfer moment, because life’s really short, and in order to keep that level of energy and motivation you have to keep being hungry – it sounds a cliché but you know what I mean. I’ve never over-analysed it…it’s a gut feeling”</em></p>
<p>Touching on her drive, Kate shares how she inherited a need for self-sufficiency from her mum. “<em>My mum was really brave. She was a single mum, bringing up 4 kids, during which time she went to Africa, she had balls the size of the Albert Hall, and I think if I could be half the woman she was then I’m doing her credit.”</em></p>
<p>Given the confidence and passion Kate exudes, I wondered whether she had ever felt uncertain? And somewhat surprisingly, she had. ‘<em>When I had my first board meeting at Sport England I had the biggest dose of imposter syndrome known to man. I sat there [thinking] what am I doing [at] this table – there were athletes, the Chief Exec of Accenture and the RFU- really impressive people ,and me! I just ran a sports PR agency… but then I thought hang on a minute, we’ve all been through the same interview process, I’ve earned my position [at] this table in the same way that they have….The reason you’re somewhere is because people want you, you have to remind yourself of that. I think if it feels right then do it, and if it doesn’t then don’t –it sounds cliché but it’s just simple.”</em></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kelly-anna</id>
    <published>2018-12-01T13:36:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:22:14+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kelly-anna"/>
    <title>High Performer: Kelly Anna</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>"You’ve got to be fearless."</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-kelly-anna">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<p>Artist <a href="http://www.kellyannalondon.com/shop/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Kelly Anna</a> is known for her bold prints, and covetable client list featuring Beyonce and Nike among others. The captivating South Londoner’s print work exudes confidence, something she attributes to her family.</p>
<p>Both her inspiration and toughest critic, her father passed on his artistic skills through a combination of support and criticism. His direction that one should ‘never hesitate’, or be ‘shy about your mark making’ comes through in her approach to life as much as art.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/KELLY_ANNA_INTERVIEW-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555504496" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Kelly Anna’s blend of fortitude and humility is infectious. ‘You’ve got to be fearless’ she asserts, believing that we should all be a ‘bit vulnerable’ but not ‘shy away, or you’ll get nowhere’.</p>
<p>Conscious of the role that strong women like her mother have played in her life, she promotes surrounding yourself with ‘confident, incredible people’ who challenge and inspire. ‘You think, wait they’re doing it, I’m going to do it’ too, she enthuses.</p>
<blockquote>
<p>‘We’re thrown into this world and it’s how we play with it’ that matters.'</p>
</blockquote>
<p>Despite her self-assured demeanour she admits to feeling a ‘twist’ in her stomach if a pitch is rejected; the tough side of her industry not often discussed.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/KELLY_ANNA_LUCASHUGH-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555504516" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Her advice for dealing with rejection? Avoid self-blame. ‘We’re thrown into this world’ and ‘it’s how we play with it’ that matters, she asserts, discussing her respect for anyone committing time to something they love.</p>
<p>Her dedication to a healthy mindset is evident, believing that ‘mental attitude is key to being your best.’</p>
<p>‘People underestimate how exhausting it is to be creative’ she says. Crediting her family background in dance for putting fitness in her ‘DNA’, she prioritises exercise as a way to recharge.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/KELLY_ANNA_WORK-1-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555504528" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Challenging herself to try ‘new, weird things’ helps Kelly Anna stay motivated. Joining a book club is her latest venture, ‘you never know what it can spark’ she gushes. ‘Looking at new things and pushing myself’ is key, ‘if you have an itch for something, do it.’</p>
<p>If there’s one lesson to take away from this vivacious artist, it’s to remember that ‘life is supposed to be fun’.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/meet-eve-gabereau</id>
    <published>2018-11-23T10:39:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:27:34+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/meet-eve-gabereau"/>
    <title>Meet Eve Gabereau</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Bridget Arsenault sits down with Eve Gabereau, who founded Modern Films, a female-driven film company with a purpose.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/meet-eve-gabereau">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Eve Gabereau started her career studying politics and languages, which took her to working in cultural affairs in Japan and China, before moving into film festivals and journalism. Next, in 2002, Eve co-founded Soda Pictures, a London-based independent film distribution company that now releases more than 25 films a year and boasts a library of over 300 titles. In 2017, Eve left Soda to setup <a href="https://www.modernfilms.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Modern Films</a>, a female-driven film company with a purpose. We spoke with Eve about her commitment to telling women’s stories, to promoting films with a purpose, and how she’s recalibrating the way films are released in the UK.</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>YOU DESCRIBE MODERN FULMS AS AN ALTERNATIVE TO THE TRADITIONAL MODEL OF TILM DISTRIBUTION. EXPLAIN?</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>I'm not sure we're reinventing the model, but I do feel our approach is fresh and driven by having fewer but strong films on our slate, innovation in our campaigns and strategic partnerships tailored to each release. Our team is made up of a range of people from different backgrounds, all focused on bringing culture and commerce together and balancing aesthetics and ethics. We are working to create dialogue around important social issues of our time through critically acclaimed films and impassioned discussion at events and online - using the theatrical space as a springboard for the film's identity and building audiences across other viewing platforms.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Three_Days_in_Quiberon_large.png?v=1554975436" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CAN YOU TALK TO ME ABOUT YOUR COMMITMENT TO INDEPENDENT CINEMA THROUGHOUT YOUR CAREER?</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>I am firmly committed to independent cinema and its place in the world to bring light to social issues, expand people's world views through good storytelling and build art appreciation through a well-crafted film. I want people to want to go to the cinema and to feel like they are part of a greater story afterwards. For me, releasing the German break-out hit and Oscar-nominee <em>Toni Erdmann </em>was the epitome of this and the best example of why I do what I do. </p>
<p>CAN YOU ALSO SPEAK TO YOUR COMMITMENT TO SHARING WOEMN'S STORIES AND WOMEN'S VOICES AS YOU GROW MODERN FILMS?</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>We are committed to showing and telling women's stories through film because there is so much great writing out there and so much incredible talent who we want to work with. But our commitment is also to quality and strong voices, and the possibility of a film breaking out to audiences. We are also committed to speaking out to younger, particularly female, audiences, to encourage them to watch more, go out more in groups and talk as much as they can about issues that matter to them and to the wider world out there.</p>
<p> </p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Utoya_large.png?v=1554975471" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>CAN YOU REVEAL ANYTHING ABOUT THE FILMS YOU ARE SET OT RELEASE OVER THE NEXT FEW MONTHS?</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Upcoming we have films from two films from extraordinary female voices in cinema: <em>3 Days in Quiberon </em>by Emily Atef and <em>Happy as Lazzaro</em> by Alice Rohrwacher. <em>3 Days </em>is the story of a tell-all interview at a spa hotel in Northern France in 1981, with the legendary actress Romy Schneider. She sadly could never escape her personal demons, despite her beauty and success. This film shows a glimpse of hope and promise in her life. while also revealing the darker side of her sadness and trauma. <em>Happy as Lazzaro </em>is Rohrwacher's third feature and it won Best Screenplay at Cannes this year under the jury headed by Cate Blanchett. It is a time- and space-travel tale of a friendship spanning traditional countryside and contemporary urban culture in Italy. </p>
<p>In February, we have the Scandi genre-bending romantic thriller <em>Border </em>by the writer of <em>Let the Right One In</em>, which is Sweden's entry for the Oscars this year. We are particularly excited about this film and the way audiences react to its commitment to questioning notions of beauty, love and immigration, while at the same time indulging in the tropes of Nordic Noir that people have come to follow and be crazy about.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-carly-wilford</id>
    <published>2018-11-06T21:00:00+00:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:26:15+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-carly-wilford"/>
    <title>High Performer: Carly Wilford</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>“We created a movement of women stepping up and thinking that if I can do this, if I can hang upside down by just my legs, then I can go and fulfill my dreams.”</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-carly-wilford">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<blockquote>“We created a movement of women stepping up and thinking that if I can do this, if I can hang upside down by just my legs, then I can go and fulfill my dreams.”</blockquote>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Unknown-7_grande.jpeg?v=1552860359" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>Known today for her talent as a DJ, Presenter and Creator of the SISTER Collective, Carly Wilford’s journey to get to this point took some unexpected turns. I was immediately in awe of how much she has achieved in such a short time.</p>
<p>Settled in a busy role in picture syndication with Marie Claire, but exhausted by the commute, Carly’s inspiration was sparked when she took a pole dancing class at her gym. Seeing the impact it had on her body in just 6 weeks, she knew it was something more people needed to do – so Carly left Marie Claire to become a personal trainer and pole-dancing instructor.</p>
<p>At the time, pole dancing was relatively unknown. Carly launched the first ever official ‘class’ at a health club in her hometown of Northampton. With six women signed up and one pole weighed down with sand bags, even the club managers were unsure- insisting that she erect curtains during the class.</p>
<p>Yet to people’s surprise, Carly’s venture was a hit. She expanded to teach at multiple sites; eventually setting up her own dance studio and teacher training course. She led classes on syllabus at Italia Conte, Pineapple and became involved with choreography at the Royal Opera House and Royal Shakespeare Company.</p>
<p>Carly admits her success wasn’t without its bumps in the road, <em>“Whenever you’re doing something left-of-center people question it, but what I realised was that [our classes were helping these women change their lives]…We created a movement of women stepping up and thinking that if I can do this, if I can hang upside down by just my legs, then I can go and fulfill my dreams.”</em></p>
<p>Seeing her students make such positive changes inspired Carly to re-evaluate her own goals. At the back of her mind she had always wanted to be a presenter, <em>“I had to look in the mirror and be like- is this where you want to be? I’d just got married and we had this business together but I realised that [I wanted something different]- so I walked away from everything- my relationship and my business. I stopped personal training, I kept my dance school and then I decided to throw myself into becoming a presenter, which was pretty crazy.”</em></p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/Unknown-2_grande.jpeg?v=1552860398" style="float: none;"></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<h5 style="text-align: center;"><span>Photo by Jack Goodman, Lefteris Primos, Antonello Zappa, RaRa</span></h5>
<p> </p>
<p>It was a tough time for Carly, reassessing everything she’d worked so hard for. <em>“Whenever you’re going through a lot and you have a lot of time, there are two things you can do – you can sit and mull over everything that’s happened in your life or you can use it productively… I [used] it to make plans’’</em></p>
<p>She’s never looked back, going on to work with unsigned artists, interview incredible talent and DJ-ing at gigs across the world. What drives her to keep moving forward? <em>“I can see the [potential] that’s within people if they’re willing to take risks. It’s amazing when you start to see people go after their dreams, to get on that path and [watch opportunities open up] to them.”</em></p>
<blockquote>“I really think it’s what we’re all here to do, the world would be so different if everyone stopped worrying about the drama and just focused on what they love. I realised that if I could help people focus on what they love I could watch them fly, I just had to remember to do that for myself.”</blockquote>
<p>Carly’s bravery and passion shone through as we discussed how she’s been able to identify trends ahead of others and take some scary leaps. <em>“If there’s a load of people walking one way I always think ‘oh what’s going on this way’ and I kind of walk the other… I find it super fascinating, and I really believe in intuition- that instinct, it can lead you down incredible paths. I also believe in magic…. I believe in the fact that if you take a leap, a risk, and it feels right, if you feel that- just go with it. There are some incredible things you can find on the other side of that”.</em></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-rachelle-ann-go</id>
    <published>2018-10-04T18:18:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:26:21+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-rachelle-ann-go"/>
    <title>High Performer: Rachelle Ann Go</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><span>“In the industry in the Philippines I felt a bit like a robot, they tell you what to do. At that time I didn’t think it was for me, I wanted to challenge myself more.”</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-rachelle-ann-go">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<blockquote>“In the industry in the Philippines I felt a bit like a robot, they tell you what to do. At that time I didn’t think it was for me, I wanted to challenge myself more.”</blockquote>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/RAG-file-2_grande.jpeg?v=1552855033" style="float: none;"></div>
<p> </p>
<p>With a speaking voice as melodic and energetic as her stage appearances, West End star Rachelle Ann Go is a performer at her highest.</p>
<p>Her big break came when she won talent contest Search for a Star at the Philippines Music Festival in 2004. She went on to record a string of award-winning albums, and perform live both at home in the Philippines and internationally for 10 years.</p>
<p>Coming from a musically inclined family, singing was always her passion, but she began to realise she needed something different.</p>
<p>‘In the industry in the Philippines I felt a bit like a robot, they tell you what to do. At that time I didn’t think it was for me, I wanted to challenge myself more’ she explains.</p>
<p>Coincidentally a musical was opening in her hometown. Despite her lack of theatre experience and concerns about her ability to play the role, a Director’s belief in her encouraged Rachelle to try. She landed the part and in that lead role as Ariel in The Little Mermaid, her love of theatre began.</p>
<p>Her next role, another career catapult, took her to London as the lead in Miss Saigon. Despite perpetually missing home, Rachelle forged ahead to play Fantine in Les Miserables in London, the Philippines and on Broadway before moving back to London for her current role as Eliza in Hamilton.</p>
<p>I was struck by the number of moments when Rachelle overcame her fear and self-doubt, time and again making the brave decision to keep trying for new roles.</p>
<p>‘There are always moments I think I just want to go back home as I really miss my family. I was really homesick,’ she recalls, ‘but then I think what am I going to do there? I always feel like there’s something more for me, something more that I can do. I don’t want to be stuck in a box and regret it for the rest of my life. When I moved here a lot of doors and opportunities opened which I wasn’t expecting and I just took them. I felt like I came here as a baby and grew as a woman, being brave enough and bold enough to think you know what, I can do more.’</p>
<p>It may be surprising to hear that despite her experience and talent, Rachelle feels nervous before every performance. ‘I think it means that you care,’ she considers, ‘I’m not taking it for granted. It’s not just about the show, for me there’s a purpose behind why I’m doing this’. </p>
<p> </p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/RAG-file1-2_grande.jpeg?v=1552855100" style="float: none;"></p>
<p> </p>
<p>The importance of the story she’s telling gives Rachelle her sense of purpose. Her deep belief in the need to let the audience feel what she’s feeling comes across so strongly, in both our interview and her performance.</p>
<p>Preparation for this process is something Rachelle takes very seriously. ‘I am a very spiritual person so (before going on stage) I play some worship music just to calm my spirit and prepare my soul, because on stage you bear out – you open your heart and soul for all to see, so you have to prepare for that, your mind, soul and body.’</p>
<p>Delivering this level of production through 8 shows a week takes its toll. How does she recharge? ‘I’m learning how to switch off now I’ve been doing this kind of job for a few years’. Rachelle got married earlier this year and is grateful to share her frustrations and excitement with someone she loves. Despite the fact that ‘it’s hard as he’s tired at the end of the day and I’m full of energy’, she finds it much easier to unplug than when she lived alone. Post show Rachelle eats dinner, as it’s hard to eat before the show, and winds down by playing relaxing music or taking a bath.</p>
<p>Her dedication and gratitude are apparent throughout, ‘I play music the whole day and I sing. Sometimes when I’m too relaxed and then do the show I find it hard to sing, my voice feels tired – it’s like stretching when you go to the gym, for singers you have to keep using the muscle so you’re ready for the show’.</p>
<p>If there’s one thing I took away from Rachelle’s story, it’s the importance of self-belief, hard work and overcoming your fears; especially in a competitive industry.</p>
<p>‘I just have to trust and believe in myself and know that I’m unique,’ she asserts, ‘I can’t compare myself to other people because God created me to be this person and there’s no one else like me, so I just have to focus and tone what I can do – and I think that’s what I did. Just focus on my strengths, fix my weaknesses and embrace that, and just audition and audition.’</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/turn-up-the-heat</id>
    <published>2018-08-03T12:50:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:28:49+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/turn-up-the-heat"/>
    <title>Turn Up the Heat</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Four tips for working out in a heatwave.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/turn-up-the-heat">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>HYDRATE </p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Sounds like common sense but the hotter it is, the more you sweat, the more you need to drink. Guidelines say the average person should drink 6-8 glasses of water per day. In summer, when the heat is on, up this to ten.</p>
<p>BE AN EARLY RISER</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>As you may have noticed, the evening is often the hottest time of day. Set your alarm for an hour earlier in the morning and get out there while it’s cool. Summer evenings should be reserved for relaxing anyway.</p>
<p>INVEST IN THE RIGHT KIT</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Choose <a href="https://lucashugh.myshopify.com/collections/performance" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">lightweight, breathable materials</a> that wick sweat away. These both help you stay cool and prevent any possible skin irritation.</p>
<p>SLOW DOWN</p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>A heatwave is not the time to beat your personal best. Break your workout into intervals with 5-minute breaks in between to rest and re-hydrate.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-farrah-storr</id>
    <published>2018-06-03T15:53:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:24:30+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-farrah-storr"/>
    <title>High Performer: Farrah Storr</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>"There’s nothing nicer than going to bed having had quite a hard day and thinking do you know what, I’m amazing I didn’t realise I could do this."</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/high-performer-farrah-storr">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>Join columnist Vicky Ellison every month as she meets with inspiring women from the worlds of wellness, business, fashion and art to bring you a snapshot of their story and advice to take into your day.</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8"><meta charset="utf-8">
<p>The buzz of the Hearst office hummed away outside as Farrah and I sat in her glass corner space, tea in hand, focused on our chat despite her demanding schedule. I could see that this focus and ability to handle multiple projects have helped Farrah reach the impressive achievements she’s known for.</p>
<p>Award-winning editor-in-chief of Cosmopolitan, founding editor of Women’s Health UK, the most successful women’s magazine launch of its decade, releasing her first book this Autumn; Farrah Storr is a publishing powerhouse.</p>
<p>Inspired by her accolades I had to ask what continues to drive her forward after so much success? ‘I think I live by, and it’s the mantra for Hearst now but has always been one of my mantras – Never Settle’ she explains, ‘success looks like you’re never quite finished.’</p>
<p>Admitting that at first, her perfectionism could cause some anguish, she’s realised that sometimes 90% is enough. A lesson she has taken from her leisure time and a new found love of gardening. ‘Gardening is a constant struggle, you’re trying to build something but you can’t control it’ she admits, sharing a story of squirrels eating her newly planted tulips, Farrah has come to realise that in gardening as in life and work, ‘what will be will be’ and sometimes you have to be ok with less than 100%.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/farrahstorr_large.jpg?v=1555426344" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>Farrah’s upcoming book focuses on the importance of being in your ‘Discomfort Zone’, a space she’s become familiar with, inspired by the feeling of overcoming a challenge.</p>
<p>‘Periods of feeling uncomfortable test who you are as a person. I think a lot of people go through life not quite understanding what their true potential is… you have to push yourself into your discomfort zone as that’s when you realise the horizon of your potential. There’s nothing nicer than going to bed having had quite a hard day and thinking do you know what, I’m amazing I didn’t realise I could do this.’</p>
<p>Is anything too far out of reach? ‘I don’t think you should think anything is outside of your discomfort zone’ she says thoughtfully, ‘Be realistic, but once you start encasing things in language like “that’s out of my limits”, it becomes a certainty that you can’t do it. I say yes to everything and then figure out how it can happen.’</p>
<p>This can-do approach, combined with hard work and a deep understanding of her personal motivations and need for time to recharge, have brought Farrah the successes she so clearly deserves.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/chelsea-rebels</id>
    <published>2018-05-23T10:28:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:24:17+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/chelsea-rebels"/>
    <title>Chelsea Rebels</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Five minutes with Catherine Rice from Hackney-based florist Rebel Rebel, the creator of our dynamic, and award-winning, window display for Chelsea in Bloom. </p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/chelsea-rebels">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>With the launch of our London boutique, <a href="https://lucashugh.com/pages/our-store" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Fitting Room</a>, coinciding with the RHS Chelsea Flower Show we jumped at the chance to be a part of <a href="http://www.chelseainbloom.co.uk/participants-voting/lucas-hugh" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chelsea in Bloom</a>. As newcomers to the Kings Road, we sought to pay homage to the Chelsea in Bloom theme, The Summer of Love, while looking to showcase the DNA of Lucas Hugh. As a brand, we seek to change the lens through which the world sees activewear, pushing the boundaries of design and style. Powerful, angular lines and high contrast colour are indicative of LUCAS HUGH making this kaleidoscopic concept engineered with the structural Strelitzia the perfect fit.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/CIB_CONCEPT_INSPO_large.jpg?v=1555493283" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>The idea for the kaleidoscopic concept came from Pink Floyd's iconic album, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Piper_at_the_Gates_of_Dawn" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Piper at the Gates of Dawn</a>, released in August 1967 - the titular summer of love. The album's artwork, a vibrant, kaleidoscope image of the band members shot by photographer Vic Singh using a prism lens, served as the final inspiration for the display. Designer <a href="https://www.instagram.com/juliancarterdesigns/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Julian Carter</a> built the metal frame on which Rebel Rebel artfully placed the Strelitzia to create the dynamic, kaleidoscope arrangement.</p>
<p>It was a joy to work with such a talented team and watch our idea go from concept to creation. We were beyond delighted to receive the Innovation Award from the RHS and Cadogan! We spent five minutes with <a href="https://www.rebelrebel.co.uk/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rebel Rebel's</a> Catherine Rice to learn more about the woman behind the talent.</p>
<p>WHAT IS REBEL REBEL'S STARTUP STOR?</p>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1">Athena and Mairead were friends who worked together in television and they just decided it was time for a change.  </span><span class="s1">They started off just doing flowers for events and then moved into Broadway Market just as Hackney was becoming groovy.</span></p>
<p class="p2"><span class="s1">HOW DID YOU COME TO WORK WITH REBEL REBEL?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Initially, I studied theatre design and worked as a scenic artist and prop maker for many years, finally taking those skills over into events and then floristry. I started doing work experience with Rebel Rebel when I was changing my career, freelanced for them for a number of years and then they offered me my present role 3 years ago.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT ATTRACTED YOU TO FLORISTRY?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Working with natural beauty.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/CIB_CONCEPT2_THEFIT_large.jpg?v=1555493288" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">WHAT HAS BEEN THE HIGHLIGHT OF YOUR CAREER SO FAR?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Working with a diverse range of amazingly talented people.</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">DO YOU HAVE A FAVOURITE FLOWER TO WORK WITH?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Every season brings a new favourite flower!</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">DO YOU SEE FLOWER TRENDS COME AND GO? WHAT, IN YOUR OPINION, IS THE FLOWER THAT WILL ALWAYS BE IN STYLE?</span></p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">Yes, a trend comes and everyone does it for a while and then something new comes in and its all change! I think the classic English seasonal flowers will always be in style, Rose, Peony, Dahlia.</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/pace-yourself</id>
    <published>2018-04-22T10:51:00+01:00</published>
    <updated>2019-05-20T11:18:52+01:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/pace-yourself"/>
    <title>Pace Yourself</title>
    <author>
      <name>Anjhe Mules</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Marathon training can actually be fun.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.lucashugh.com/blogs/the-fit/pace-yourself">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Women’s Health Digital Editor, PT and first-time marathon runner Amy Hopkinson shares how she’s trained for the long run.</p>
<hr>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>One look at my <a href="https://www.instagram.com/wellness_ed/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Instagram</a> and you might assume that running races comes naturally. But until 2018, I was much like the 75% of women who – according to Sport England’s This Girl Can campaign – <strong>want</strong> to be more active but aren’t, because of a fear of not being fit enough. I was afraid that even if I conquered 20 gruelling weeks of cardio training I might not complete the 26.2 miles. At least not in the average time of 4 hours 17 minutes.</p>
<p>I’ll openly admit that I was scared of being a Women’s Health editor whose running stats didn’t stack up with her CV. So, what changed? I committed to training for the joy that’s in it. And with that, I refused to run for a time.</p>
<p>When competition and clock watching goes out the window you zone in on how you feel. It no longer matters how fast you move but <strong>how</strong> you move. And this, in my mind, is the most important aspect of any training plan.</p>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0030/0158/1668/files/lucashugh_thefit_running-768x512_large.jpg?v=1555577228" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p>But, re-wind to 2017 for a moment. This was the year that I focussed my fitness on learning how to move; I built a strong, stable body and ironed out any imbalances and kinks that put me at risk of injury. I mastered moving well, which really did set me up for moving more in 2018. With that in mind, here are my marathon non-negotiables. Embrace these now and you’ll be ready to race come 2019:</p>
<h3><strong>Get strong for speed</strong></h3>
<p>The easier running feels the more you enjoy it, so embrace strength training. Weighted single leg strength exercises build muscle and improve neuromuscular coordination and power where you need it most. You’ll notice the benefits as better coordination, less wobbling and increased stride efficiency.</p>
<h3><strong>Podcast pace</strong></h3>
<p>A typical running cadence, that’s your number of steps, is somewhere between 145-185 per minute. But fast tempo music can alter this and without realising, you begin to run more like Radcliffe. This is fine on 5KMs but hard to maintain over long distances. My hack? Switch to podcasts. They still entertain (and distract when things get tough) but are less likely to play with your pace.</p>
<h3><strong>Buy a ball</strong></h3>
<p>Feel-good endorphins are hard to find when everything hurts. But a thrice-weekly session with a tennis ball changes this. Roll it on your calves, glutes, hips and hamstrings for self-style myofascial release, which reduces soreness.</p>
<h3><strong>Rehydrate right</strong></h3>
<p>Tiredness and headaches from dehydration are the fastest way zap a Sunday Runday high. So start hydrating the night before by sipping a pint of electrolytes. Do the same straight after your run when stretching. The potassium and magnesium in these tablets (that you add to water) ease muscle cramps, while brands with added Vitamin B12 boost energy too.</p>
<p>Now, as running begins not with the feet but with the mind get inspired by this year’s runners – a quick scroll of #LondonMarathon2018 should help.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
